Chapter 412: Survivor

Hu!

An old-style small spaceship slowly landed on the devastated gray surface of Fawn-122. The air stream blew out from the bottom of it, stirring up rings of airwaves. The engine produced a buzzing noise from its plain and simple thruster. Its speed, noise reduction, and shock reduction were all very low performance, considered as a technology that was going to be eliminated very soon. In the galactic trade markets, only poor people with very shallow pockets would buy such simple spaceships.

Yet, this antique was equipped with top-level stealth devices—optical invisibility, sound reflection, gravitational force penetration, quantum network shield, and many more. A few DarkStar members disguised as travelers got off the spaceship and placed a special signal spreader on the ground. The invisible electric wave passed through the gaps on the surface of this planet at an unbelievable speed and entered the underground.

It continuously went deeper along the twists and turns in the gap. Inside a dark and narrow space, a pair of long-asleep eyes suddenly opened. The back of his palm was giving off a dim light. A microchip was planted inside, which received the signal and vibrated softly. The vibration happened in the vessels and bones, awakening this person from his sleep.

"Finally..."

After a while, the wait for the spaceships on the surface finally ended—their target had appeared. In the fissure far away, a man climbed out and slowly walked over. It was an Esper indeed. He looked terrible, and his face was bony. He was the only survivor of the Sarota fleet. Before the Dragon Emperor arrived, Sarota had given the retreat order. However, when Esper knew the enemy was Ames, he knew that the mothership would most likely not be able to escape, so he had taken a risk. He had decided to stay underground. In a deep cave, he had formed a carbon structure with his power and sealed himself, controlling his heartbeat and blood flow, entering a fake death state. As he expected, these allies that boarded the fleet to retreat were all killed by the mercenary fleet, Holy Stone, and Black Raven, turning into fireworks in space and becoming dust.

After Sarota's fleet was demolished, the mercenaries had caught the mothership's highest commander, Sarota. Therefore, they did not bother to search the entire planet for a possible survivor. This DarkStar team had been completely defeated, so there was no need to waste more time. Therefore, Ember had survived. Important officers like him all had a location microchip planted in them. After everyone left this planet, a rescue spaceship came to pick him up.

At that time, Han Xiao was also more inclined to believe Ember died, although he still had a small doubt in his heart. After all, characters with legendary characteristics should not die that easily. However, he had no way to search the entire planet. The other mercenaries had been in a hurry to head to Godora and would not help. With his manpower, God only knew how long it would have taken him to search the entire planet. There was no need for that. Plus, it was not worth it from a probability perspective. Hence, he did not think too much about it. Regardless of whether Ember was dead or alive, Han Xiao could accept it.

The DarkStar warriors wanted to support him, but they were swept away by Ember. He did not need anyone to support him. With a cold face, he said in a low voice, "Tell me, what's the situation now! Did Sarota and the rest all die?"

"Ames slammed Sarota's mothership down. We received attacks from both Holy Stone and Black Raven, and the fleet was completely defeated. A part of the members of the ship survived, including Sarota. They were transferred to Godora; this was just reported by the Colton News. They were all sent to the Rainbow Prison."

Every mothership was a moving stronghold of DarkStar, and losing any of them was a heavy blow.

Ember clenched his teeth and said, "What about the Secret Message Bead?"

"We heart that the Secret Message Bead was picked up by a Floating Dragon guard, then given to the Holy Stone Civilization, which then gave it to Godora.

Ember's body shook, and he growled in a low voice, "So, you're saying, our sacrifices were completely meaningless and did not make any impact at all. We suffered such a catastrophic loss. How can it just be over? Even if we cannot beat the Dragon Emperor, she has to pay the price! She attacked us to save Black Star, so we shall find an opportunity to kill Black Star, showing her that we're not easy to mess with."

This time, a heavy and powerful yell stopped Ember's words. "In important times like this, it's unwise to mess with a strong enemy. Remember, Godora is our true enemy."

A hologram appeared in front of Ember. It was a hybrid Godoran with light gold skin. On his skin were some strange scales and beast hide like wrinkles. His forehead was covered in markings of a mysterious pattern, extending down to his eyebags and nose, like the war paint of savages. This man was rather old, but his eyes were very sharp, and he gave off a steady aura like the mountains.

The anger in Ember's eyes was suppressed as soon as he saw this man. He lowered his head and said respectfully, "Teacher."

The other DarkStar members beside him also lowered their heads in fear and said, "Your Excellency Anur."

Anur was the mentor that developed the potential of Ember's power and guided his path. He was a high ranked officer in DarkStar, one of the few grade A individuals in the organization. His position was above all and only below the leader.

He looked down at Ember and said in a low voice, "I can see you're resentful. Tell me, who is the source of your anger?"

"Black Star... He's a mercenary group captain under the Dragon Emperor. I failed against him twice... no, thrice. Ever since I started working for the organization officially, these are the only three failures I've ever experienced. He's caused me great shame, and he has special abilities that counter my power... Only his death can brush away my shame!"

Anur intercepted and said coldly, "Childish! Narrow-minded! The organization has spent an enormous amount of resources on you and raised you to be a strong warrior, not to let you fight irrelevant people. The organization has a lot of hope for you. The responsibilities that you bear are beyond your imagination. A small mercenary is not someone that you should concern yourself with. Focusing your thoughts on him is a waste of time!"

After a pause, he added, "Furthermore, Black Star is under the Dragon Emperor. Now is not the time to provoke them. When the bigger matters are dealt with, you can settle such issues."

Ember lowered his head and asked, "What should I do?"

"Anger has affected your sanity. This is an unforgivable mistake. For the next year, you're not allowed to carry out any missions. Stay in the base, focus on training and self-reflection."

"Understood." Ember nodded. He respected Anur a lot. His mind calmed down, and he accepted the arrangement. The hostility toward Black Star was pressed down to the bottom of his heart... His teacher was right. He was destined to be an ace of the organization; what they planned for was much bigger. He should not spend energy on irrelevant people.

After pondering, Ember asked the last question, "Teacher, what about the Secret Message Bead?"

"Godora has the Secret Message Bead. Sooner or later, they will know what's inside. The newest seventh-generation Mutation Source is in Godora's hands, and the organization's plan faces the risk of being exposed. This matter needs to be discussed again. In a few days' time, the leader will host a high-ranking meeting to discuss this. The strategic planning afterward will all have to consider this as a factor, and we will need to make some adjustments.

Having received the answer, Ember did not waste any more time. He boarded the plane and took off.

Ten days passed in no time. The players were standing by in the stronghold and had nothing to do. They spent most of their time in the dungeons.

They tried [Warfare: Power of the Dragon Emperor] many times, discussed and exchanged experiences, and found a possible way to clear the dungeon.

Firstly, they had to choose the reinforcement faction. The countdown clock was the same as the DarkStar faction, three hours. Between the three factions, this was the easiest choice. Then, they had to get lucky and meet a main character—specifically, Goa of the Sky Ring Army—within the first twenty minutes and follow her for two hours without doing any side missions.

Next, they had to pay close attention to the time and leave before meeting the next enemy that would cause the players to be wiped out. This way, two hours and twenty minutes would have already passed. The difficult part was the last forty minutes. If everything went well up to this point, there should be at least six to eight players left. By using the method of leaving teammates behind one by one, there was a chance for the last person to clear the dungeon. Doing this would cause the reward to be reduced by ninety percent, but at least it could be cleared.

However, although there was a theoretical method, most of it relied on luck. So far, no one had succeeded.

Initially, these pro players thought that if they chose the mercenary faction and met Han Xiao, they would be able to live. However, this was just what they thought. No matter what faction they chose, it was certain death once they met Han Xiao. Not mentioning the DarkStar faction, in the case of the mercenary faction or the reinforcement faction, after meeting Han Xiao, they would be able to pass a long time safely, but they would definitely meet Ember in the end. When that happened, everyone would be killed in an instant. Even if they left Han Xiao in advance, they would still meet Ember.

The pro players placed their focus back on the level 60 Germinal Organization dungeon. Its level was suitable and much easier. No matter how rich the level 90 dungeon's rewards were, they could only look at them for now.

With this failure, Bun-Hit-Dog was not able to record materials about the Dragon Emperor. He had no choice but to do another episode about the past. He recorded parts of the level 60 Germinal Organization dungeon and continued on the previous Black Phantom Series. This series had yet to arrive at its ending, and most of the players had only heard of Han Xiao's past but never seen it.

Bun-Hit-Dog's video included the dungeon process. The Germinal Organization dungeon was a large team dungeon extending from Han Xiao's infiltration into the Germinal Organization headquarters to the end of the Germinal Organization. The story built up very well and was very interesting.

Initially, Bun-Hit-Dog just wanted to use this episode as a filler, but the response after he posted the video far exceeded his expectations. It was just as popular as the Black Star Series, which really surprised him.

Through the influence of the Black Star Series, more players from other planets came to learn who Han Xiao was and knew that he was the first NPC to bring the players off their planet. The players from other areas were very curious about his history, and the Black Phantom Series happened to be Han Xiao's origin story. Many new viewers were attracted by it.

Chapter 413: New Combat Style (1)

No matter how popular Ames was, it was impossible for Han Xiao's place to be threatened. After all, she was just a newly introduced character, whereas everyone was very familiar with Han Xiao. His image would not be impacted by this. The Dragon Emperor being beautiful was one thing, but Han Xiao gave a lot of rewards.

What was the point of just being beautiful? An NPC was only good when could make the players money!

Furthermore, according to the progress of Bun-Hit-Dog's Black Star Series Episode Three, Han Xiao and the Dragon Emperor belonged to the same faction. The influence of these two was combined, which made the players have more anticipation. As Bun-Hit-Dog used the drama style to edit his Black Star Series videos, Han Xiao and the Black Star Mercenary Group were the audience's first-person perspective, which gave them a sense of immersion. They felt like they were part of Black Star, and seeing the faction made them feel happy.

This episode was the latest episode of Black Phantom Series, the end of Germinal Organization. Han Xiao stole intel from the Germinal Organization headquarters, escaped and battled over hundreds of miles, met with the reinforcements from the Six Nations, and fought his last battle in the encirclement. The convoy rode across the yellow desert, stirring up dust and sand. The sky was dyed yellow, and it was filled with the murderous intent from both sides. Bullets and cannons rained down like a metal storm while the thunderous sound of explosions swept across the sand.

The video followed Bun-Hit-Dog's perspective, taking part in the battlefield recreated by the dungeon. In order to show a stronger impact, he chose the Germinal Organization side. From the video, the audience could see Han Xiao dashing across the battlefield in an unstoppable way, moving like lightning. One moment, he was demolishing a few Germinal Organization Executive Officers—the next, he would be hundreds of meters away, flipping vehicles over with his shoulder.

In Bun-Hit-Dog's video, Han Xiao was like a BOSS. The Germinal Organization's leader fought him head-on. Every time they clashed, the ground shook, and the soundwave trembled in the air. The impact was almost overflowing from the screen as if the screen would shatter like a mirror at any second!

Their fight was like a flying dragon that extended across the entire battlefield. Just the aftershock from their battle was able to send the soldiers and vehicles in their path flying. The viewers could not take their eyes off. It was like they were there themselves; they were nervously holding their breath.

Boom!

With the last thunderous hit, the image trembled!

The viewers finally took a deep breath.

Blood splashed out from the Germinal Organization leader's mouth as he was blown away, flying backward, rolling on the sand for almost a hundred meters, and leaving a marking behind. He fell onto the floor and vomited blood non-stop. On the other side, Han Xiao stood in the middle of the shattered mechanical suit pieces on the ground, unveiling his face. Bun-Hit-Dog was blown onto the floor by the shockwave, and he was looking up. The dust and sand settled, like a yellow curtain being pulled open. Han Xiao stood under the scorching sun, above the yellow sand and between the cannons and bullets, covered in twisting bolts of lightning, expressionless.

At this moment, his coolness level was at the max!

Even for Planet Aquamarine players who knew that Han Xiao was powerful, they could not help but feel emotional. This was perhaps the first time that the players from other planets had seen Han Xiao's performance, and it happened to be his most impactful scene. They were immediately stunned with excitement and trembling.

"Wow, this man is so powerful!"

"So, he had this kind of past..."

Every novice planet had main characters. In comparison, Han Xiao received the most attention. Many new viewers attracted by the Black Star Series were shocked and more interested; they wanted to find Bun-Hit-Dog's previous videos and find out more about Han Xiao's past.

The video continued. The last scene was the cutscene of the nuclear explosion in the Germinal Organization Headquarters.

A mushroom cloud rose from the ground, and the dark red light in the thick smoke was like the boiling lava from hell!

The world trembled!

Just as the viewers were stunned by the image, the noise from the explosion suddenly disappeared. Only the image of the nuclear explosion remained. At the same time, a man's voice appeared in the background.

"The clouds of war obscured the blue skies like the wings of death, and the scars of the previous war have been torn open again before they could even heal..."

At the end of the video, Bun-Hit-Dog had the genius idea of putting in Han Xiao's speech from before.

The image was the end of Germinal Organization—the Six Nations launched a nuclear missile to end the war. The background was Han Xiao's speech when he created the Sanctuary. The image of the nuclear explosion complemented and explained the content of the speech. The Six Nations started a war for their own benefit, and the Sanctuary was built to save the tinder of civilization. When putting everything together, the contrast was very strong, and it felt completely different.

After the video ended, the viewers could not have enough of it. It was like they had watched a short legendary drama. Thinking back to the storyline on Planet Aquamarine as a whole, they were feeling sentimental.

Although Han Xiao did not speak throughout the entire video, with the speech that Bun-Hit-Dog added at the end, the level of class that he had was off the charts!

Some audiences imagined his thoughts and analyzed his actions. When this event happened in real time back then, there had been players who did a similar thing. Now, the topic became heated up once again.

"Real men don't talk, they use actions."

"Black Phantom cares about the world and fights for the weak, so he wanted to destroy the evil Germinal Organization. Not bad, he's my husband after all."

"Black Phantom: Bullsh*t, I just wanted to run away with girls. Do you think my nickname 'Women Lover Great Mechanic Han' has no meaning?"

The players made full use of their creativity and discussed excitedly.

Although this video was rushed, Bun-Hit-Dog did a very good job, and it received a very positive response. Han Xiao's sense of presence and influence was increased largely. Originally, Han Xiao had already given the players a rich impression. Now, with this video about the end of the Germinal Organization, his impression in the players' mind evolved and became clearer. He became legendary, and his unique characteristics started to shine through, which differentiated him from all the other characters.

He was the one and only.

This was exactly why Han Xiao had brought Bun-Hit-Dog along, and from the current situation, Bun-Hit-Dog was doing very well. In between building machinery, Han Xiao took a break and watched the video. He was very satisfied.

A few days later in the machinery modification room, the air was filled with a certain stench. The results of these few days' work—hundreds of small orbs—were arranged neatly on the table.

"It's finally done. A little earlier than I expected."

This was the new machinery that he had created by taking the advantages of the same type of low-level blueprints. Their performance and attributes were far superior. Before he started building, he had spent two to three million experience and leveled up these blueprints to the max level. The more he built, the more familiar he was with them, and the faster he built.

Han Xiao took off the protective suit and counted the numbers. He then separated the small mechanical orbs into different types.

A method was needed to use the compressed small orbs as well. Usually, Mechanics would carry a portable small bag and store these small orbs inside, or they might make these small orbs into jewelry, such as a necklace, bracelet, or earrings. Sometimes, they might also tie them at the end of their hair like the Godora Observer or place them into the combat suit.

As the compressed structure was very tight, there could not be any extra parts in them. Therefore, compressing a compressed orb into another one would not work, or it would have been able to be expanded infinitely. Only a complete machine or an individual part could form a compressed orb.

Han Xiao compressed the mechanical suit, so in normal daily life, he used a black tactical belt to store the compressed orbs. This had originally been designed to store magazines. It had a metal button in the middle, and the belt was split into two and formed an 'X' shape. It was slotted on his waist to increase the number of items that he could bring. Inside this belt were weapons that were relatively less important. For core machinery such as the mechanical suit, it was made into jewelry.

Han Xiao wore a necklace made from three compressed orbs, bracelets on both his wrists, and two small orbs as his earrings on both his ears. His hair now was rather long, so it could be tied and let down behind him. At the end of it were some compressed orbs as well.

Han Xiao walked over to the mirror and looked at himself. He was entertained by his new look.

"Tsk, what a unique style I have."

Chapter 414: New Combat Style (2)

Han Xiao appeared satisfied with it. When practicality was concerned, he did not care much about the look. Although being handsome was an eternal thing for him, he chose to be strong.

Other than the belts and the jewelry, there were also some compressed orbs in his clothes.

Usually, this was what he looked like. Once he entered a battle, he would then activate the mechanical combat suit. He had added slots in the mechanical suit to store and release compressed orbs. Once he equipped the mechanical suit, the magnetic connection would suck the compressed orbs on him into these slots, like reloading bullets. These compressed orbs could be shot out any time, making it more convenient to expand his machinery.

There were hundreds of compressed orbs, and part of them were backup equipment.

After arranging the results of his hard work, Han Xiao pushed the door open and walked out of the machinery modification room. Herlous was waiting at the door. When he saw Han Xiao come out and approach him, he said, "Captain, Lerden and the others arrived at Juberly Hub two days ago. They're waiting to meet you."

"Lead the way."

Han Xiao adjusted his clothes.

The two of them left the stronghold, boarded the Hub Center's hovering carriers, and mixed among the others. After a while, they landed on the middle level of a building at the end of the Hub Center. All the rooms on this level were resting rooms, and one of them was the temporary mini stronghold that the Sunil mercenaries had rented. It was at the corner and had a very narrow space, the cheapest room. They were money-saving as always.

Ding dong.

The bell was pressed, and the silver alloy door slid open. The two of them walked in. Inside the tight and narrow room, more than fifty people had somehow squeezed in. The people there made up half the number; the other half were in the room next door. They heard the news and came over as well. Han Xiao saw that it was too cramped, so he asked everyone to talk outside on the public rooftop. The rooftop also acted as a parking area for flying carriers, like a mini dock. At the back of it was the city-like Hub Center, filled with tall buildings. Flying carriers were everywhere in the sky, landing and taking off from buildings from time to time. A warm wind blew across the rooftop ... a product of the air coming from the carriers.

"Black Star."

"Captain."

The Sunil mercenaries greeted Han Xiao. Lerden was sent out as the representative to express their appreciation.

Han Xiao sized these people up. Many Sunil mercenaries were disabled and had mechanic prosthetics. He had read the resumes of these mercenaries earlier; more than half of them were grade C Supers, and a small portion were grade D. It was not suitable for grade D Supers to become mercenaries—it was simply too dangerous. However, the Sunils were facing very tough times, and they needed every bit of help they could get. So, they had no choice but to let stronger mercenaries help the weaker ones.

"Here's what's going to happen. I will choose missions that are suitable for you, then you can decide whether or not to accept them. Since you have joined me, you have to listen to orders. Let's be clear about one thing first. You can have objections to my orders, and we can make negotiations. However, if you disobey my orders behind my back, I will stop working with you immediately. Of course, I don't wish for that to happen. You're facing a tough time, and I understand it. After all, I was there for the recent Sunil Catastrophe. You don't have to worry about me giving you missions that are impossible for you to complete..."

Since he was the leader of the faction, he had to ensure his absolute control. Although the Sunil mercenaries were valuable to him, Han Xiao was not going to completely compromise for them.

The Sunil mercenaries nodded and agreed without any objection. In their eyes, Han Xiao being willing to share his influence with them was already a huge help.

Han Xiao opened the mercenary panel and picked out a few missions to let them choose. These hiring missions were not open hires given by the alliance that were available to everyone; these were private request from other partners that had very rich rewards. The difference was that when normal mercenaries requested missions, they were the one making the request, and they were the ones being picked. However, the private hires that he got were requests from others, inviting him to work together. This was the benefit that the Black Star Mercenary Group received after making a name. The partners were all large mercenary groups, so they might not really need help, but they were willing to share the profits, which was actually to build a better relationship, mainly because of his identity as part of Floating Dragon.

Most of the Sunil mercenaries operated individually. They had to go through life and death situations only to get very small rewards. They had never seen missions that were safe yet had such rich rewards. Naturally, they were overjoyed. Although there were only a few missions to choose from, they still took their time choosing. After quite a long discussion, they finally chose to accept the cooperation request sent by Sky Ring Army, to escort a resource scouting team to an unpopulated planet in the north of the Garton Galaxy.

When they were picking, Han Xiao did not speak. He leaned against the glass panel on the rooftop and played with a compressed orb in his hands. After they made their choice, he then said, "Although this is quite an easy mission, I need to test your combat abilities just in case. Let's go to the Battle Simulation Room."

The Sunil mercenaries thought that this was unnecessary, but they could only obey the captain. They left the rooftop and came to the Battle Simulation Room.

Han Xiao rented a large room, walked in, and stood opposite everyone.

The Sunil mercenaries exchanged looks. Lerden coughed, took a step forward, and said, "I shall be the first one to test then."

"No need, all of you together. Saves time," Han Xiao said.

The people were stunned. We have a hundred people here, and you want us to attack together? Isn't that too arrogant even for a grade B Super?

A sense of anger surfaced in their hearts; they felt they were being underestimated. Although we are here to work for you, you'll regret taking us lightly!

With anger on their faces, the Sunil mercenaries spread out and drew their weapons, preparing for battle.

The team of a hundred men slanted forward slightly, ready to charge forward. Their united presence was like a lion that was about to attack its prey.

Opposing them, Han Xiao looked so solitary.

Only if they were taken seriously would they get better treatment. They decided to go all out and showcase their full power. Since you want to be beaten up, we will give you a good beating!

Herlous turned on the Stimulation Room. The white room turned into a flat, stone plane, very wide and spacious. He looked at the warriors of his race and shook his head.

Over the past few days, Han Xiao would call him to test the power of his weapons from time to time. He knew full well how powerful Han Xiao was. He was just hoping that his friends would not get beaten too tragically.

Han Xiao moved his shoulder and felt the compressed orbs on his belt. At this moment, he suddenly felt a sense of déjà vu, like he had gone back to the first time that he used the Mechanic class to shine in the arena and demolished kids from everywhere. From that time, his path as a booster had started, and he had never looked back.

This was not just to test the Sunil mercenaries—he was also testing his actual strength and earn their respect.

The Sunil mercenaries had joined him purely for his influence; they actually did not look up to him for his strength. Most of the mercenaries now looked at the Black Star Mercenary Group this way. Many people were jealous—they felt like Black Star had become related to Dragon Emperor out of pure luck, otherwise they would just be a third-tier group. They would be able to do it too if they were that lucky.

This was a disadvantage of becoming popular too quickly; people doubted his strength. Han Xiao had expected this from the start, but when comparing the pros and cons, what he was doing now was definitely more beneficial. It was normal to have some side effects. Mercenaries always respected the strong, and he did this to beat them face to face so that they would respect him.

The corners of his mouth rose, and the desire of battle appeared on his face.

"Come."

Boom boom boom!

The Sunil mercenaries took a step forward and started charging forward right away. The ranged warriors fired cannons and lasers that approached very quickly.

Han Xiao stood on the spot without moving. A flash of lightning appeared on his body. The two earring orbs flew up into the air and quickly turned into two Hovering Shield Shuttles, forming two purple-blue shields, blocking above his head and before him. All the ranged attacks exploded on the thin and mirror-like energy shields, causing ripples.

Buzz!

The sound was continuous. Compressed orbs flew out of his belt one after another and floated around him.

Magnetic energy activated immediately, and these compressed orbs were spread out by the energy and hit the ground as fast as bullets with a clank, expanding instantly!

The setup was complete in an instant!

The next second, twenty-two ground artilleries and fourteen hovering artilleries appeared, firing at the hundred opponents simultaneously.

Tu tu tu tu tu!

The flashes from the muzzle were one meter long. Some of them were high caliber gunpowder artillery that used special magazines, and some were electromagnetic artillery. The firepower coverage of thirty-six artilleries did not have a blind spot. The formation of the Sunil mercenaries was broken immediately. Their speed decreased, and they had difficulty dodging the hail of bullets.

The artilleries were located beside or behind Han Xiao. The area within about a hundred meters outside was covered in mechanical traps and obstacles, limiting his movements and preventing enemies from getting too close. Every trap was one to two meters tall, and their triggering range was much larger than their size. Electric sparks were flashing on these traps, dissuading people from daring to even step on them.

In the blink of an eye, a formation expanded right beside him!

The Sunil mercenaries had trouble taking a single step, and they were immediately disadvantaged and struggling.

On the other hand, Han Xiao was standing still with hands in his pockets and a calm face, like the extremely violent explosions happening at that moment had nothing to do with him.

Chapter 415: New Combat Style (3)

After gaining the compression technology, both the depth and breadth of a Mechanic's combat abilities would drastically increase. They would gain the ability to take control of the situation or even turn the tables immediately. The focus was to deploy the machinery as fast as possible and the right combination of machinery at the right place. The speed of deploying that machinery would have a very large impact on the outcome of the battle.

After the version of Mechanics rising, the method that other Supers used was mostly striking and charging before the Mechanic could deploy their machinery fully. If a Mechanic was allowed to deploy their weapons freely, the situation would be irreversible, and the enemy would slide down the abyss of failure. Of course, this was in the case of normal situations, not considering some special abilities or items.

In the case of battle tempo, Mechanics always had the upper hand. The enemies were forced to follow it and stop Mechanics from deploying their machinery. This was a very big advantage. Furthermore, even if the Mechanic's tempo was broken temporarily and they did not have the time to deploy the machinery fully, the enemies could not let their guard down. If the Mechanic caught their breath and deployed the machinery afterward, the tables would turn in an instant, and the enemies' effort before would all go to waste.

Han Xiao's Mechanic class was now beginning to take shape and possessed this tough ability. He was also very experienced, so it was impossible for his speed of deploying the machinery to be slow. This time, cannons and fire covered the entire place, so the Sunil mercenaries inevitably fell one after another. This was just a spar, so the Sunil mercenaries who fell onto the ground were dragged off the battlefield by Herlous, who stood on the side. Ever since the battle started, he had been kept busy by doing this continuously. He had never been given a chance to even rest.

A Pugilist mercenary flexed his legs, then jumped up into the air, drawing a parabola in the air, wanting to jump over the floor filled with traps and reach Han Xiao.

At this time, a metal trap that he jumped over was suddenly triggered. A grenade shot up into the air and exploded with a bang. A blue, net-shaped current extended out from the center of the explosion. This was a capturing trap formed by long, thin metal cables with a high voltage running through it. It shrouded the Pugilist mercenary who was still in midair.

Buzz!

This guy screamed in agony as his skin was burnt black by the current, then he fell down to another repulsion trap. An invisible force pushed this guy up into the air again, and a few artilleries turned toward him and focus fired. The bullets pushed him out of the area.

He fell to the ground, unconscious.

This stopped the other mercenaries from wanting to jump up.

"It's not so easy to jump across all that." Han Xiao smiled. There were landmines in the traps, and there were also traps that could sense objects above them and attack accordingly to prevent enemies from getting close in midair.

Within the range of his Mechanical Force, any machinery received bonuses from him. Some artillery was placed beside him, and its power was enhanced multiple times. Whoever was at the front would face the most violent and heaviest attacks. Because of this, the mercenaries spread out and charged from all directions, diverting the firepower from the artillery.

Lerden was covered in a green shield that was flickering under the rain of bullets as he charged forward. In other directions, there was quite a number of mercenaries who were equipped with shield generators. The colorful shields charged through the cannons and traps, approaching quickly.

Han Xiao formed a hook with his fingers. Another batch of compressed orbs flew out and dropped beside him, expanding into twenty or so beast shaped robots. Their size was about the same as medium-sized dog breeds, but they were covered in black armor and had a streamlined body like cheetahs, like armored panthers. There was an opening on both of their shoulders, exposing the triple mounted gun barrels from the machine guns inside. Their tails were very swift and looked like a scorpion tail, at the end of which was a sharp alloy blade.

Han Xiao had prepared three combos. One was the Multi-Turret Firepower Coverage Style, which did not require any technicality. Another was the Trap Style, which required a little bit of control, mainly regarding where to place which traps and whether these traps could protect him and limit the enemies' movement. The last was the Hound Style.

The Hound Style was controlling a group of small mechanic beasts, entangling, harassing, and culling the enemies like hounds. As the basic machinery that formed this style was called Mechanical Hounds, hence the name. This blueprint was rather easy to obtain. Han Xiao was using an enhanced version of mechanical beasts.

['Black Panther' Combat Mechanic Beast] was a new blueprint that he had created after combining numerous low-level mechanical beast blueprints. One 'Black Panther" had 2,700 points of armor, and the basic mechanical hound only had 1,500. Its attack was also increased by around seventy percent. It had more functions and better performance. Of course, it possessed the essential self-destruction ability.

"Go," Han Xiao said. The twenty or so mechanical Black Panthers dashed out extremely quickly as the barrels on their shoulders opened fire. They swiftly moved across the battlefield between the gaps of the traps, attacking from the rear and the sides of the enemies. These were the weak points of their defense, and their speed was immediately slowed down.

As soon as any mercenary got close to the mechanical Black Panther, it would jump away, always keeping its distance and only going closer to the enemy when attacking.

Sometimes, three or four mechanic Black Panthers would cooperate with each other, diverting the enemies' attention from different directions while one of them attacked from the back, slashing with its tail and dealing quite an amount of damage.

Mechanical Black Panthers were equipped with smart chips, and four of them formed a group. They could only carry out some simple tactical strategies in fours. Han Xiao's ability to build chips was still at the basic level, so the mechanic Black Panthers' combat ability was not independent enough. The number of orders that they could recognize and carry out was limited, so they could only be used to harass.

With the combination of artilleries, traps, and mechanical beasts, it was as if the Sunil mercenaries were walking in a quagmire; every step forward was difficult. Han Xiao observed the effect and nodded.

"This combination is not afraid of being outnumbered and can easily crush Supers that are weaker than me. Even when used against Supers of the same grade, it can also restrain and harass... Of course, it will be heavily damaged as well."

Bang!

As he was thinking, a mechanical Black Panther was blown away and smashed into an artillery, bending its barrels.

Han Xiao looked over. Finally, someone passed through the lockdown. Lerden was covered in a green light. Having finally arrived before Han Xiao, he growled, and the green light turned into a spear in his hands, which he strongly thrust forward!

Clank!

In the blink of an eye, the compressed orb on Han Xiao's necklace expanded, and a white mechanical suit covered him instantly!

The spear stabbed at his chest but was unable to move even an inch forward through the bone-white mechanical suit. Without saying anything, Han Xiao raised his hand and slapped down.

Boom!

Lerden was smashed onto the floor by the slap, facing downward. His face was planted into the ground instantly, no match for Han Xiao at all.

The people's faces changed. Han Xiao's appearance had changed—he was in a white combat suit, the armor texture looked like bones, yet it was unbelievably strong and hard. It looked like a knight's armor made of bone.

Its shape was gorgeous. The shoulders were carved to look like dragon heads, and the chest and the waist pieces were had highly-flexible joints to allow swifter movement, complementing the streamlined body shape. Not knowing if it was an illusion, the people present felt that this mechanical suit was giving out a very mysterious aura.

[Void Dragon] Single Unit Mechanical Suit.

Compared to the snake series mechanical suits such as Python and Amphiptere, this dragon series mechanical suit had stronger capabilities. It was not because it involved more advanced technologies but because its material was rare. It was made from the Void Dragon Bone that he had obtained on Floating Dragon Island. It was light yet durable, and it had special energy within. This mechanical suit did not have that many weapons; it was used specifically for hand to hand combat. Its armor was a horrifying amount of more than 30,000 points. Furthermore, the Void Dragon Bone granted the mechanical suit extra abilities.

Han Xiao had three compressed orbs on his necklace, and all of them were mechanical suits. One was Void Dragon, and the other two were the backup Amphipteres. Whether a Mechanic was strong or not depended on the number and attributes of their equipment. He had both the number and the attributes, and that was because he had enough money.

Seeing this, the other mercenaries stopped moving forward and said with a bitter smile, "We admit our loss."

The difference in strength was too vast. They had battled through all the obstacles and finally gotten close only to realize that Han Xiao himself was stronger than all his machinery. It was a completely impossible battle to win. There were around a hundred of them, so originally, they had thought that Han Xiao was outnumbered, but now, they felt that they were the ones that were outnumbered.

They clearly surrounded Han Xiao, yet it felt like Han Xiao surrounded all of them by himself.

Han Xiao had yet to finish testing all his weapons, so there was still a huge cannon that he did not deploy. He wanted to continue, but seeing that the mercenaries had given up, he could only collect all his machinery, disappointed.

After cleaning up the battlefield, these Sunil mercenaries gathered in front of Han Xiao. They were only lightly injured. Their eyes were now filled with respect and fear.

The strong is always respected.

Han Xiao said a few words, mostly saying that they had passed his test and that their ability was not bad. Then he got rid of the Sunils and told them to start doing their missions.

Han Xiao returned to the stronghold alone and went to the machinery modification room. He pondered and concluded his experience.

"According to the current effect, the strategy that I planned is now mostly ready. My level 95 class advancement requirement is rather difficult, so I might be stuck at this level for quite some time. This combination of styles is very strong at the current stage, so it can be used as a filler before class advancement. Plus, there are many ways to enhance it..."

He took out the weapons that he had recently built and observed the item attributes on the interface once again.

The variety of artilleries and traps was very rich—mostly made out of new blueprints that he had obtained from combining several blueprints—and their various performances were all 25% – 40% better in comparison.

He looked at Void Dragon's data. Amphiptere was a very well-rounded mechanical suit, so he did not build another one of the same style. Void Dragon was focused on melee battles. As its material was rare, it had very strong additional abilities.

[Void Dragon]

Type: Single Unit Light Mechanical Combat Suit

Grade: Purple

Requirements: LV 90, Mechanic Class, >4000 Energy, >200 END

Basic Attributes:

- Armor: 30400/30400

- Defense: 375

- Power Level:1360

- Energy: 9000

- Height: 1.91m

- Weight: 143 lb

Control Method: Low-Class Smart Chip + Nerves Connection (Extra +10 DEX)

Power Source: Portable Stable Mini Nuclear Reaction Furnace—Self Charge. Recovers Energy at 120/min. Energy conversion rate from user: 30:55

Stationary Mode Energy Usage: 25/min

Combat Mode Energy Usage: 48/min

Core Power Capacity: 775/1200

[Skeleton Module: TM1.50 Nano-Biological Muscle Fillings]

Enhances the power of movements and body capabilities.

+57 STR, +45 DEX.

Power Output: 150.

Muscles can be enhanced by energy.

Energy cost: 40/min.

Effect: All Attributes +33%

[Armor Module: Void Dragon Bone (Pink Rare Material)]

+28,000 Armor, +320 Defense.

[Hand Module: Vibration Converter (Purple)]

Generates vibration, 11% of melee damage is counted as armor-piercing damage.

Power Output: 50

[Wrist Module: Wrist Force Enhancer]

+10 STR

Power Output: 30

[Leg Module: Pressure Enhancement Circuit]

+8 DEX

Power Output: 30

[Thrusting Module: Mini Maneuvering Equipment (Purple) x 12]

Total Power Output: 240.

[Survival Module: Body Signs Monitor, Thermostat Life Support System, Oxygen Filtering, Gravity Stabilizer, First Aid Injection Device, High-Pressure Resistance Device...]

Total Power Output: 150

[Chip Module: Damage Detection, Database Analysis, Trajectory Prediction, Remote Control, Combat Assistance, Neuronal Signal Transformation...]

Total Power Output: 110

[Subsidiary Module: Electromagnetic Pulse Controller (Purple)]

Applies [Excitement].

All Attributes +7%

Duration: 15 mins

Energy Cost: 5 per use

Power Output: 15

[Subsidiary Module: Compressed orb storage and ejection pipes]

[Additional Ability: Strong Capability]

During combat, distributes energy to Biological Muscle, increasing power.

Effect: +45 STR, +35 DEX

[Additional Ability: Indestructible Toughness]

Void Dragon Bones have unbelievable durability.

Effect: -20% Physical Damage received, -18% Magical Damage received. When armor is lower than 40%, this effect is doubled. After getting out of combat, armor recovers at 3% per minute.

[Additional Ability: Mysterious Power]

Void Dragon Bones possess mysterious powers.

Effect: +15 STR, +11 DEX, + 34 Melee Damage, +16% Attack Speed. 40% of Melee Damage will be dealt as splash damage.

Energy Cost: 60 per use

Duration: 1 min

Cooldown: 75 s

[Additional Ability: Void Jet Spray]

Void Dragon Bones possess extraordinary magic. After it dies, void magic precipitates inside its bones.

This equipment is able to convert energy into Void Jet Spray.

Damage: 278 – 1790

Energy Cost: 50 – 300 (Controllable)

Cooldown: 0

If used again in the next 10 seconds, the energy cost will increase by 30%. If not used in 10 seconds, the energy cost will reset.

Side Effect: This equipment is enhanced by void energy; it has a very high load. When equipped, -3000 Health Limit.

Remarks: When you stare at this mechanical suit, you can almost feel the remaining soul inside.

Chapter 416: Conclusion and the Next Stage of the Plan

The requirements are rather high. It's very difficult for normal level 90 Mechanics to have 200 points of Endurance, and even if they do, it just converts into 8,000 health points. Wearing this and losing 3,000 health points will be losing almost half of their health. Plus, psychic abilities can easily go through the armor. But for me, that's only one-fifth of my health, so I'll still be very tanky when I'm wearing this. 3,000 health for 30,000 armor is completely worth it.

Han Xiao nodded.

Void Dragon was the strongest combat suit that he could build at this moment. All the materials for it were used up, so he could not build another one. Be it toughness or damage output, it was top-notch in its level. The two core additional abilities were [Indestructible Toughness] and [Void Jet Spray]. The former increased its durability and gave it the ability to self-recover, while the latter had a very strong explosive damage and came from the precipitated magic inside the Void Dragon Bone. Although Han Xiao was a Mechanic, due to the uniqueness of the material, the Void Dragon mechanic suit that he had built could be considered half-magic and half-mechanic equipment.

There were quite a few ways to build self-recovering equipment through mechanic methods, such as nanotechnology repair robots, which required the high-class knowledge of the Energy Branch [Nano Energy], or to build it with shape-memory alloys, which required the Armed Branch ability [High-End Material Technology].

Speaking of magic...

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled. He called the three Volga brothers. These three looked very similar, and they were hard to differentiate. Usually, the oldest brother would speak for the three of them.

"Captain, what is the reason for calling us?"

"What kind of spells do you guys know?" Han Xiao looked at the oldest Volga brother.

"I'm a specialized mage in water spells," the oldest Volga said. "My second youngest brother is good at shape manipulation spells and enhancing auras. My youngest brother is a Psychic. Actually, when the three of us were younger, we applied for the Phill Mage Academy, and only my youngest brother was rejected. I still remember that recruitment instructor said this to him. 'Give up on magic, your talent is not suitable for it. To you, magic is like the Varisel Mountain; you will never be able to climb it'. Do you know the Varisel Mountain? That's the tallest mountain on our home planet..."

The eldest brother was very talkative and could not stop talking. He diverted from the topic in the blink of an eye. Han Xiao was only dazed for two seconds, and the topic was already on how their first childhood pet died.

"Stop..." Han Xiao hastily stopped the oldest Volga brother, coughed, and said, "I called you here to enchant some weapons."

He pointed at the machinery on the table as he spoke.

The three of them had no objections to the captain's request, but their faces turned bitter when they turned and saw the machinery.

So many machineries... the workload was way too large.

"I wrote the specific requirements on paper, and it's on the table. You can do it slowly when you don't have missions." Han Xiao waved and walked out with big steps, leaving the three of them there looking at each other.

The youngest Volga brother was very happy. He was not a mage, so it had nothing to do with him. He looked at the two older brothers with glee in his eyes and left joyfully. The other two looked at his cheerful departing figure and almost wanted to gift him a magic beam.

Theoretically, most inanimate objects could be enchanted, including machinery of course. Enchanting was also a career that the Mage class players had by default. In his previous life, most of the mages provided enchanting services to earn some extra money. Water-type enchantment increased physical damage reduction, and shape manipulation type usually gave bonus damage.

Han Xiao's ability to enhance weapons through his mechanic methods was already at his limit, so he sought new ways to enhance. Since there were mages in his team, he might as well make full use of them.

I'm now level 95, five levels away from the level 100 promotion limit. However, the Mechanic main class is stuck at the class advancement requirement, which requires me to learn two high-end knowledges... Sigh, I have yet to even finish learning all the advanced knowledges...

Han Xiao shook his head in frustration. His main class was at the fifth stage, which made up 65 levels. When players had such a high level in their main class, it would already be long past Version 2.0, and the next class advancement would only be possible to complete in Version 3.0, as that was when they could get their hands on high-end knowledges. Even in Version 3.0, the cost of learning high-end knowledge was still very high. They would basically only be exchangeable in faction stores, and the players would have to spend a lot of time farming favorability and money for them.

The class advancement that he had received randomly was quite difficult. Just advanced knowledge already cost him so much effort to obtain—high-end knowledge was even harder to get. The area exchange center in Garton Galaxy only had one high-end knowledge for sale, and it was a rather unimportant knowledge. Even so, its price was a hundred times more expensive than advanced knowledges. He had about a hundred thousand Enas in his account, but he would still not be able to afford it.

There were two difficulties with this class advancement requirement. One was money, and the other was channels. The former required time and effort to earn, and the latter required him to look through various galaxies in the Shattered Star Ring to find a seller. Very few Mechanics were willing to share their knowledges. Therefore, Han Xiao felt that he would not be able to advance class in a short time, even with his Floating Dragon Faction background.

There will be more promotion requirements once I reach level 100. I might as well find a new subclass first, level up to level 100, and take a look at the promotion requirements. If convenient, I can complete both of them together.

The Secret Message Bead triggered three large missions for me, all related to Godora and DarkStar. I need to plan it slowly. It's better not to make any moves before the next version... Wait, counting in the hidden mission from Aroshia, I have four high difficulty missions.

Aroshia was very mysterious. She had awakened her Esper power to turn into energy, and it seemed like it made her curious about Esper powers. Han Xiao had told Herlous to teach her how to use her energy, and he also guided her himself sometimes. He realized that Aroshia was very talented and improved extremely quickly. She had extraordinary potential inside her like a sleeping treasure. Her power received fertilizer from her potential and became stronger very quickly. Han Xiao estimated that she would officially reach grade C within a month.

He opened the forums and browsed through what the players were up to as usual. He saw that among the Black Star Mercenary Group players, someone had posted the process and difficulties of the level 90 dungeon. This was the first time that any players had seen a dungeon that exceeded the level limit of the current version. This post sparked very heated discussion.

Han Xiao looked through, and only then did he know about what it was like inside the dungeon. He estimated in his mind, and from his experience, level 60 players should have a chance at slipping through the dungeon and completing it with a very low rating.

Bun-Hit-Dog released a new video again?

He noticed Bun-Hit-Dog's new video, the fourth episode of the Black Star Series.

Han Xiao was surprised. He opened the video and glimpsed through.

This episode continued from the last episode, the second half of the hiring incident. From Floating Dragon Island to DarkStar's chase to the Dragon Emperor appearing. Bun-Hit-Dog still had yet to beat [Warfare: Power of the Dragon Emperor]; he had given up and drawn this image himself. Hence, what the viewers saw was a slideshow of a kindergarten child's drawings. That, accompanied by Bun-Hit-Dog's rich and emotional description, felt like a salesperson trying to sell a piece of cr*p while insisting that it was a treasure.

"... DarkStar's mothership saw that the situation was very, very bad. They yelled 'we've got to run' then started running immediately. Ames stared at DarkStar and yelled, 'Hey! No running!' She then activated her power and grabbed Floating Dragon Island like it was nothing, then threw it at the DarkStar mothership! The sky trembled as the two of them clashed, and like an egg smashing against a rock, the mothership crashed down to the ground..."[1]

Bun-Hit-Dog's description was full of ups and downs like he was on steroids. His tone was more excited than a salesperson, like he was casting a fight of the century. However, the image was extremely humble and poor—it was a black stickman throwing a golden ball that dragged a dotted line behind to represent its movement. The ball then hit onto a big patch of black, which represented the DarkStar mothership. A "BANG" then appeared beside the image, in bold and red.

This guy really is a genius...

Han Xiao's mouth twitched. As he expected, the comments during this scene were like a rampage, and the audiences' desire to mock it was at its maximum.

Luckily, other than this scene, the images after this went back to recordings. The video ended when they returned to Juberly Hub, and the incident ended. The players only saw what was on the surface, so they did not know about the conspiracy DarkStar had, only Han Xiao did.

Other than the 'images' emphasizing the Dragon Emperor's powers, another focus of the video was Black Star Mercenary Group's new officer—Aroshia. Compared to her, the Volga brothers became transparent and were completely ignored. Following the craze brought by Ames last time, Aroshia stirred up another frenzy. Her looks were superior to Ames' and were almost perfect. Although she did not possess the strength, power, temperament, and other bonuses that Ames boasted, she had her own charm. Her amnesia made her pitiful and mysterious, and most importantly... she had breasts, very big breasts!

Unsurprisingly, the war between the Flat-Chest Faction and Huge-Breast Faction broke out once again!

"The Dragon Emperor is very strong, beautiful, and has long legs, but... she's flat!"

"Pale skin covers ugliness; flat chests destroy everything. Sorry, my love now belongs to someone else."

"I don't want to say this, but you people are really terrible. Your brains are filled with breasts, what's so good about being big?"

"Big is beauty!"

These people were split between the Ames faction and Aroshia faction. Han Xiao was happy to see this. The more they argued, the more popular the topic would be. As a male, he would never get dragged into the argument anyway.

After closing the forums, Han Xiao started to think of the next step of the plan.

I have gone through quite a few big events this time and have been dragged into battles of a higher level, entering DarkStar's sights. It'll be best to keep a low profile from now for some time, accepting requests peacefully and stabilizing my current position. At the same time, I'll save some money as well.

He had been through quite a lot this time for the compression technology, so temporarily, he was not going to take risks. He had made a name for himself, increased his abilities, and also formed some connections. The partners provided many rewarding missions, so he decided to finish these requests one by one. There was no need to hurry.

Furthermore, the players played a huge role in his growth too. It was now only Version 1.0, so the players' abilities were very limited. When the players grew again in the next version, the benefits that he would be able to obtain from the players would multiply many times over.

He returned to the stronghold hall. All the players were there. They saw that Han Xiao had appeared and all surrounded him.

"Black Star, when will we be going for the next mission?" Frenzied Sword asked.

These players were fighting dungeons all the time, so they were extremely bored in the stronghold. Their faces were filled with anticipation.

"Pack up, we will leave today."

On the way there, Han Xiao had accepted the hiring requests from his partner allies. The missions were not difficult, and their rewards were quite handsome. Before the next version came, he was preparing to only accept such missions in order to earn some wealth, strengthen his position, and grow in a low profile.

After such a huge event, they had to rest for some time.

The players were immediately revitalized. They picked up their things very quickly. Fifty armored warriors stood before Han Xiao neatly.

Han Xiao glanced at them, turned around, and walked outside with big steps. The players followed right after.

"Let's go!"

...

Han Xiao had decided on the plan—accept requests from partners one after another. They were active in various star systems in the Shattered Star Ring.

After the heat from the Floating Dragon incident cooled down, the position and name of the mercenary group were slowly being built up in missions after missions. Their resume gradually became richer.

The Black Star Mercenary Group was busy accepting one mission after another, and nine months passed in no time.

[1] The words and grammar used in this part look strange because the original text was written in a strange tone to highlight Bun-Hit-Dog's shoddy narration. Back

Chapter 417: Nine Months later, Planet Dawn.

In the Ancient City Ruins of the South Territory on Planet Dawn, an alliance of various tribes had gathered.

Three thousand Blue Shield Knights of the Vain Kingdom, five thousand Savage Berserkers of the Howling Barbarians Tribe, one thousand Alchemist Bombardiers of the Earth Tribe, five hundred Beast Riders of the Child of Voices, and the mixed army of the Southland City and the Principality. There was a total of fifteen thousand people camping in the green field outside the Ancient City Ruins, their flags swaying with the wind.

There was not a single cloud in the sky. The sky there was the color of dusk, turning everything into a darker shade. The sun hanging high up in the sky looked tiny as it was very far from the planet.

The Imperator was having a meeting in the tent with the commanders of the various armies, and they were having a heated discussion. Only one tall blue-skinned man did not speak at all. He was the Blue Shield Knights Captain, Rex, the war hero of the Vain Kingdom. He had turned from a civilian into the commander of the ace army of the biggest kingdom on Planet Dawn. His deeds were praised by all the people on Planet Dawn.

When the others were almost done talking, only then did Rex open his mouth. The commanders of the other tribes all respected him very much, so they stopped their argument and listened to his words.

"Rezar and his believers are currently hiding under the ruins, preparing the ceremony of polluting the Origin Water. We have about two and a half hours' time. There's about eight hundred high-level Mojo Puppet Colossuses, which he spent twenty years building, sleeping in the ruins. He's installed complex magic arrays, so the path toward the ceremony altar will only open if all the Mojo Puppets are destroyed.

"This means that we have to break through the lockdown of the Mojo Puppets in a short time, find their position, and stop the ceremony. If not, the Origin Water of more than half of the Southland territory will lose its vitality, and hundreds of thousands of people will die!"

Another commander sighed. "The scouting troops have sent back a message—every Mojo Puppet is more than seven meters high. They are extremely hard and are even blessed by prayers. Even our Reasteel swords broke from slashing it and could only leave a white mark...

"This intel cost us six elite troops. Also, Rezar's sect has one hundred [Polluters] who can corrode our weapons and bodies. No elite warriors can withstand the corrosive spell. This situation is too tough.

"It's very difficult for the fifteen thousand of us to breakthrough in a short time. Sigh, Rezar prepared in darkness for twenty years. If we had discovered his conspiracy ten days... no, even just three days earlier, we would not be in such a situation. This is everyone that we could gather in such a short time."

"This affects the purity of the Origin Water and the lives of hundreds of thousands of people; we cannot fail," Rex said with a deep voice. "The Kingdom Tribune Mages have contacted the ascenders from the higher worlds. The ascenders have hired warriors from the higher worlds who will help us in combat..."

Rex then looked at the corner of the tent. A human in a red battle suit was sitting there, looking completely different from the others who were wearing chain armor. He stood up and said, "I'm the Red Horn Mercenary Group's Captain, Lin Ge. The people of your race have paid the gratuity, so we will help you to our best ability."

"Captain Lin Ge, are you confident?" Rex asked.

Lin Ge shook his head and said with a bitter smile, "Frankly, the situation here is much worse than the information that we received when we accepted the mission suggested. Our strength is limited, and we aren't able to deal with missions of this level. The details have already been reported to the employer, and the second batch of external reinforcements is on the way. If we're lucky, they should be able to reach us within two hours."

Frowning, Rex's face turned grave, and he said, "Time is too scarce. Are the reinforcements dependable?"

"Don't worry, the mercenary group in the second batch of reinforcements is much stronger than us. As long as they arrive in time, solving the incident here will be a piece of cake. Their stronghold happened to be in this Star System. If not for that, they would not even have bothered to take on small incidents like this."

"I hope so..."

Rex was worried, but Lin Ge was confident.

Planet Dawn was located in the Garton Star System, Godora's territory. This planet was very far from the Fixed Star, so it was at dawn even in the day, hence its name. There was no moon at night too, only darkness. There was no difference in seasons; every day was cold. Theoretically, this should have been a frozen planet that was unable to birth lifeforms. Its vitality came from the river running through the surface and underground. The natural water on Planet Dawn contained magic energy. It had warmth in it that diminished the coldness of the entire planet and gave birth to plants and lives. It was called 'Origin Water' by the inhabitants of Planet Dawn. The Origin Water was the most important resource on the entire planet.

Civilizations on Planet Dawn was built on Origin Water. The changes and wars between nations throughout history were mostly because of Origin Water. The long-term consumption of Origin Water gave people strong physiques. The light blue-skinned Vainerians were the main race. The ancient Vain Kingdom was the strongest kingdom on this planet. The existence of Origin Water determined Planet Dawn to be a magic civilization—its technological development was slow, and it focused on individual capabilities. Its social construct had very obvious characteristics of magic civilizations, such as the ones who could control magic all had higher positions in society.

Although this was a surface civilization, as it was focused on magic just like Godora, it had a connection with the galaxy. Once someone reached a certain level of strength, they could request Godora's help and enter the 'higher world', which was the galaxy. These people were called the ascenders. There had been hundreds of ascenders throughout history. Some completely disappeared, but some returned from time to time and left communicators. This was also the Kingdom Tribune Mages' Holy Relic, used to contact the ascenders.

Not long ago, the Vain Kingdom had discovered the conspiracy of the notorious 'Pollution Mage' Rezar. He wanted to use some kind of large magic ceremony to divert the Origin Water from more than half of the Southland territory, giving himself an incomparable amount of magic power. Originally, the magic in the Origin Water would perish. Even if they were used, it would also be recovered through natural cycles.

But this ceremony would strip all the magic from the Origin Water in a certain area, and that Origin Water would need hundreds of years to recover. The density of the entire planet's Origin Water magic would decrease because of this, which would lead to the planet's temperature decreasing.

Even if Origin Water would still cycle, it required time to do so. That area would lose its protection and be covered in ice within a month, turning into a place of death, causing hundreds of thousands of people to lose their homes or even die.

In the 'Ancient Age' one thousand years earlier, someone had carried out the same ceremony, and that was the cause of the North Wasteland in Planet Dawn, which had yet to recover. Back then, all the tribes had formed an alliance and killed the culprit after a tragic war. The knowledge of this ceremony had been destroyed at that time, yet one thousand years later, this ceremony appeared again.

Hence, the Vain Kingdom emergency gathered troops, contacted other nations, and formed an alliance, heading directly to the place where Rezar was hosting the ceremony, preventing Planet Dawn from repeating the past. Furthermore, the southern soil was very fertile. If this place was frozen, the production of food would largely decrease. Thousands of people would starve to death afterward.

Lin Ge's Red Horn Mercenary Group had accepted the mission from the ascenders of Planet Dawn and arrived here a few days ago to solve the problem. However, the number of Mojo Puppets exceeded their expectations, so they had no choice but to request external reinforcement. To their surprise, an unexpectedly strong mercenary group was willing to help.

This mercenary group was very well known in the industry and had a very strong background. People like the Red Horn Mercenary Group would not even have the opportunity to form any connections to them under normal circumstances. Lin Ge was very relieved—this mission was not a problem with them coming to help.

Time was scarce. Rex could not wait any more and issued the order—the alliance started to march.

Boom!

Footsteps and beast hooves formed a tsunami of sound. The army charged forward and quickly approached the Ancient City Ruins. Even from afar, they could see the dark green magic colossuses inside the ruins. They had four arms, held a huge axe, and were flickering in magic light. Their texture was like stone but also like metal. The army could see that they were hard with just one look.

"Blue Shield Knights, charge!"

Rex pulled down his visor and clipped his legs. The mounts of the knights were called Ravening Beasts; they had a snake head and a horse body. With a growl, the Ravening Beast charged forward. Three thousand Blue Shield Knights followed right behind. Facing the magic colossuses, which were more than three times their height, every single one of the knights had absolutely no fear in their eyes.

The Magic Colossuses were controlled by someone. They formed a formation quickly and collided with the charging knights!

Bang bang bang!

People fell down, and beasts flipped over. The scene turned very chaotic very quickly. The other tribes joined the battle as well. Blades and claws slashed against the Magic Colossuses and clanked, their growling louder than the explosions!

The Berserkers and the knights were at the front, but regardless, the Magic Colossuses smashed the bones of the warriors with their huge strength one after another. The place was filled with screams of agony. The enemy [Polluters] hid behind the colossuses and cast corrosive spells at the warriors.

The spell array could only be opened when all the Magic Colossuses were destroyed. Often, they had to pay the price of thirteen to eighteen elite warriors just to destroy one Magic Colossus. Even though the Red Horn Mercenary Group helped with their firearms and abilities, they were not killing the Magic Colossuses fast enough.

There were more Magic Colossuses than the estimated eight hundred. It was like a wall of desperation.

Blood slowly spread out on the green field, and the dawn in the sky witnessed this bloodbath.

"Continue charging forward, don't stop!"

The Knights led by Rex had already lost a quarter of their members. At the same time, they had killed the most Magic Colossuses too. His face will resolute, and he went out of the battlefield and charged back in again.

His spear stabbed into a Magic Colossus's leg. An explosion occurred on the spear tip enchanted with an explosive spell, shattering a small part of the Magic Colossus's body. One Magic Colossus could wipe out hundreds of normal troops. The Blue Shield Knights were the elite troops of the Vain Kingdom, so every one of them was a warrior who had magic powers. They were far stronger than ordinary people. Such heavy battle damage was already very tragic.

At the same time, at a strangely shaped huge altar inside a man-made space under the Ancient City Ruins, countless believers in black were praying softly, sending magic into the magic array on the altar.

In the heart of the altar was an old Vainerian in a gorgeous bright red robe—Rezar. A golden framed mirror was floating beside him. It possessed the [Clairvoyance] spell, and the image in the mirror was a reflection of the war above him from an aerial view.

"These fools, they fell for your scheme as expected. These Magic Colossuses are used to fight with them specifically. Our magic array is hidden under the field. Blood from above is directed into this place. The ceremony can only be activated with enough blood as its fuel. Hehehe, your idea of tying the magic array with the Magic Colossuses is really brilliant, leaving them with no choice but to fight head-on with the Magic Colossuses," a superior believer under the altar said in a flattering tone.

Rezar nodded and asked coldly, "How much more blood is needed."

"The fuel to activate the altar will be enough in one hour if they continue fighting. You will become the lord of magic, the strongest Mage in history!" the superior believer said with a fanatical face.

"Strongest..." Rezar looked at him pitifully. He shook his head and mumbled, "Twenty years of preparation, I'm finally close to success. I've been stuck at this stage for so many years, and this is the limit of my talent. As long as I cross this step, I will be able to go to the higher world..."

The battle on the surface lasted almost an hour. In order to save time, the army almost completely gave up its defenses and attacked crazily. Half of the Magic Colossuses were destroyed, and all the Polluters were dead. However, the warriors had suffered heavy losses as well. Blood turned into a river. The rest of the people were exhausted. The casualties were increasing at a very high speed.

"Hold on. According to this speed, we can stop the ceremony in time!" Rex yelled loudly to boost morale.

At this time, he felt a chill above his head. A Magic Colossus was near him and slashed down its huge axe.

Boom!

Rex pounced forward hurriedly. The Ravening Beast was split in half, and the axe slashed right into the ground. The blood and intestines of the Ravening Beast spilled all over the floor. If he did not dodge it, this would have been him.

He did not even have the time to be glad. This colossus was already walking toward him with the axe in its hands. A shadow loomed over Rex's head as the axe was raised up high in the air.

Rex's felt a sudden pain in his legs, having been hit just now. He was covered in sweat and wanted to stand up with all his might.

In the blink of an eye, he suddenly realized that the shadow under his feet seemed to have expanded, followed by the sonic boom that became louder and louder.

Bang!

An alloy airdrop cabin fell down to the ground right beside this Magic Colossus, and the impact blew both the Magic Colossus and Rex away.

Dong! Dong!

Then there were more sounds of these cabins falling onto the ground. Many airdrop cabins fell onto the ground nearby.

Whoosh!

The hatch opened, and a group of warriors in heavy metal armor gushed out. The leader was a human man in a black windbreaker wearing many spherical jewelries. He was looking left and right with curiosity.

"Are they the new reinforcements from the higher world?" Despite having a very rational personality, Rex could not help but be surprised.

At this time, that Magic Colossus charged toward this human man, and its axe slashed down. Rex subconsciously wanted to yell and remind him, but what happened next made him swallow his words.

This man raised his hand and easily grabbed the axe that was more than enough to slash a Ravening Beast open. The impact from the axe only made his wrist sink a negligible amount of distance. He raised his eyebrows and said, "Tsk, the way this planet welcomes its guest is really passionate... We came right on time. Stop standing there, time to do the job."

Lin Ge, who was in the middle of a fight, looked over and heaved a sigh of relief.

"They're finally here, the Black Star Mercenary Group."

Chapter 418: The Unobtainable Is Always Tempting (1)

Tu tu tu tu!

The pro players who landed with the airdrop cabins raised their high caliber armor-piercing cannons and fired at the dark green Magic Colossuses around them. Fire sparkles exploded on the Magic Colossuses' body, and thick clouds expanded from the explosions. Under this nonstop storm of iron, these Magic Colossuses that could face the charge of the knights head-on were now shivering and backing up continuously, unable to move forward a single step, as fractured shards fell from their bodies.

In nine months, they had experienced dozens of battle missions. They had very rich experiences in facing such magic combat puppets. Although their numbers were much fewer than the army, they took control of the battlefield very quickly.

Herlous drew his Battleship Slicing Blade, smashing a Magic Colossus with every slice very efficiently. Aroshia and the Volga brothers stood beside Han Xiao and did not move.

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and observed the battlefield while standing still. He was not preparing to attack; Herlous and these players were more than enough to deal with the enemies. The capabilities of these people under him were up to standard, so he was having a good time doing nothing as much as he could.

To put it simply, this incident was about a villain who wanted trouble appearing on this planet, so they had invited him to deal with it. There were hundreds of similar incidents happening every day in the Shattered Star Ring. The motive of the villains was also very varied. They experienced it many times, so they were used to it and were familiar with the process—land in airdrop cabins then clear the scene. Han Xiao did not even need to command anymore.

He was proud of his team's progress!

Nine months had passed, and he had deliberately controlled the size of Black Star, keeping it the same size as before. But as their resume grew, they had built a good name for themselves. When he carried out cooperative missions with Sky Ring, Blades, Purple Gold, and other large mercenary groups, not only were they able to force their way through most easy missions, they also always had a very dependable performance when facing difficult problems. They built the image of a dependable partner in no time at all. Originally, most large mercenary groups wanted to build a relationship with him because of his Floating Dragon background. But they slowly acknowledged and respected Black Star's abilities. When they needed external reinforcements in the Colton Star Cluster, Han Xiao was almost always among their first choice.

When a Mercenary Group's Credibility Rating reach a certain level, they would receive additional benefits. They would be listed among groups that had good Credibility Ratings in the area and automatically send some emergency hires in the area exclusively to Black Star. That was how they had become the reinforcements for Planet Dawn.

Actually, he had just completed a guarding request two days ago. As per their habit, they were supposed to rest for some time in Juberly Hub. However, he saw it was an emergency event from Planet Dawn, so he decided to cancel the holiday and come to their aid. This planet was one of the infection targets in the [Mutation Disaster] mission that was yet to be activated. Hence, he came to take a look.

Planet Dawn's development level is low magic level, yet to achieve the stage of magic being industrialized. They focus on individual powers. Although they sent some supposedly grade B 'ascenders' to Godora, their society's knowledge of the galaxy is very limited, not even as good as Planet Aquamarine...

Every civilization had their own name for the universe. Planet Dawn called it the 'higher world' and 'ascending', showing that their civilization was more focused on individuals. Furthermore, most of the people did not know of the situation in the galaxy. They only knew that it was a higher level world. The king not spreading the knowledge was also part of the reason.

DarkStar deployed the mutation source here as well. Now that nine months had passed and the Version 1.0 update was near, it was time to visit the other planets where the Mutation Disaster would occur in Version 2.0 so that he would be mentally prepared.

"Black Star, I've heard so much about you."

Lin Ge walked over and greeted Han Xiao with a pleasing and respectful tone. With the people of Black Star taking part in the battle, he was not worried about the situation at all. Hence, he took the opportunity to create a connection with Han Xiao.

"Hello." Han Xiao extended his hand out and gave him a handshake.

Lin Ge was a little flattered. He thought the top-level people of the industry would be very arrogant and did not expect Han Xiao to be so friendly.

The two of them were chatting over there as Rex crawled up from the ground on another front. He picked up his shield and spear, caught his breath, and joined the battle again. He did not even have time to communicate with the reinforcements. His army had a chance to catch their breath, so they gathered again and cooperated with the players.

Magic Colossuses broke apart one after another. With the strong help from the players, the battle ended very quickly. The rest of the soldiers hurriedly bandaged their wounds and recovered their physical strength as fast as they could.

Rex came before Han Xiao and Lin Ge. His face was solemn, and he did not say any useless words. "The door to the altar will open now that these Magic Colossus have been destroyed. Rezar's sect is gathered there; there are more enemies waiting for us. We have no time to waste, please follow us and move forward immediately."

Rex saw Lin Ge's respectful expression toward Han Xiao between the breaks of his battles, and from that, he knew that this new reinforcement was someone important. Therefore, his tone had respect and alarm in it. The guests from the higher world were always mysterious in his eyes.

He could not help but look at the airdrop cabins, guessing how the people from the higher world landed in these things. He wondered what the principle behind these things was.

"Ok, let's end the chitchat here and start moving forward." Han Xiao nodded and agreed since it was a request from the employer.

After the alliance army had a brief moment to rest and regroup, they hastily looked for the entrance in the ruins. They were able to find the entrance to the underground altar very quickly.

This was an abandoned underground city, built into a secret stronghold by Rezar and used for many years. They surged in and followed the corridor down. The underground city was not large, so the tunnel was narrow. Rex's troops had a high number, so they had no choice but to leave some of their people on the surface.

Han Xiao and the others followed behind and moved outside the army. This was a very serious situation in Rex's eyes, but to him, it was very simple. Find the target BOSS, kill it, the end.

...

At the underground altar in the deepest area of the underground city, the scene of the army entering appeared on the magical mirror. The hundreds of believers' face changed instantly.

"Sh*t, why is another group of warriors from the higher world here? Our plan is ruined. The Magic Colossuses did not kill enough people; the blood is not enough to activate the altar! We're done for!" The superior believer was panicking.

Rezar was not calm anymore. His face became very grave. He stared at Han Xiao and the others in the mirror, and a sense of envy, yearn, and jealousy appeared in his eyes.

These people all came from the higher world...

Soon, very soon.

I will become someone of the higher world, too.

Rezar had always felt that the people who were trapped on planets were pitiful. The believers thought that Rezar carried out this plan to become the strongest Mage. He ridiculed this idea. These foolish believers did not know the vastness of the universe, and their sights were so narrow.

Pitiful!

Maybe in the eyes of galaxy residents, the universe was nothing much, but for people who could only look up at the sky and draw out the universe with their imagination, being able to enter the galaxy was exceptionally attractive. Furthermore, he knew that there were other civilizations and races in the universe. His curiosity and desire for knowledge was like a flame in his heart that could not suppress.

This was the exploration instinct of intelligent species, wanting to advance, wanting to step onto the peak of mountains and take in the beautiful view. When something was yet to be obtained, it would always be very tempting.

Rezar's target was only going to the higher world. He could sacrifice everything and not care about the consequences at all for it. However, the higher world mercenaries that suddenly arrived had changed the plan that he had spent so much effort to prepare.

If not for those people, his plan definitely would have succeeded.

A heavy shade of mania appeared in his eyes.

"Mentor, what do we do‽" the superior believer asked anxiously.

Rezar looked down at the panicking believers. This was a sect that he had spent dozens of years building. A hint of cruelty appeared on his face. "Lend your flesh to me..."

A bright red light suddenly burst out from his magic staff. The pillars on the altar were glowing in blood red. A complex glowing magic array appeared on the floor. This time, all noise disappeared. The believers' eyes suddenly swelled, and their faces turned blue-black as if they were suffocating. They scratched their throats, but their bodies were out of their control. They fell to the ground one after another, struggling frantically as their body twisted into countless strange positions.

That superior believer's face was filled with agony; his eyes were filled with disbelief. He crawled up the altar while struggling. His shivering hand wanted to grab Rezar's robe, but before he could do so, his eyes burst. Blood gushed out onto the floor, turning into a long, thin line of blood like a red earthworm, 'crawling' down to the bottom of the altar.

Hundreds of believers died together. The blood in their bodies was sucked dry by the magic array. They turned into dry corpses with opened mouths and sunken faces. The altar that absorbed the blood, on the other hand, became smooth like gray jade.

Although rowdy moments earlier, the scene was now dead silent.

There was finally enough blood.

Boom!

The ceremony activated.

The enormous amount of magic power constructed a special magic array smelled like blood.

Behind the altar was an Origin Water vein. The underground Origin Water that was slowly flowing suddenly started to boil, and tiny spots of light appeared on the water surface like fireflies. It was all visible magic power. The light spots suddenly combined into a few light dragons, absorbed by Rezar frantically through his face organs.

Rex finally arrived with the troops five minutes later. They saw the altar and the dried corpses on the floor from far away. When they clearly saw Rezar absorbing the magic from the Origin Water, Rex's face turned grave.

"No, the ceremony has started! We have to stop him immediately!"

Just as Rex was about to order his troops to charge forward, the sound of magic buzzed from around the altar. Defensive arrays appeared on the walls one after another. Colorful lights covered the altar. There were almost a thousand layers of defense spells, and they were all extremely tough. The floor trembled, and twenty new Magic Colossus climbed out of the ground and stood beside the altar.

Rex's expression changed immediately.

They would not be able to break through so many defensive spells and Magic Colossuses. He had thought that he could stop the ceremony once he found Rezar, but they were now blocked outside.

Rezar had planned too far ahead; he could not allow accidents to happen, so he naturally had a large number of defensive measures. As long as he could stop the enemy for just a short time, he would be able to complete the magic absorption ceremony.

The magic that a thousand miles of Origin Water contained was enormous. This ceremony had been passed down from the Ancient Age, and it constructed a magic fountain inside the body. Only then was it able to contain so much magic, so he could break through his strength limit.

"It's the end of the Southland territory if he completes the ceremony. We have to destroy these defensive spells as quickly as possible. Follow me and charge..."

He had yet to finish when someone suddenly pressed on his shoulder and stopped his sentence.

Rex turned back and saw that Han Xiao walked past him and stood before the troops.

"You're too slow, let me."

Han Xiao's tone was unwavering and had the confidence of a professional. Different from the Planet Dawn troops, his face was always calm and relaxed, not bothered by these defensive measures at all.

Clank!

Next moment, compressed orbs shot out one after another and expanded quickly. About a hundred different models of artilleries surrounded Han Xiao. The cannon tore the layers of spells apart instantly. To him, these defensive spells were as weak as paper!

In nine months' time, although Han Xiao did not change his combat style, he did make enhancements. He had increased his machinery and enhanced their power. In less than ten seconds, the twenty Magic Colossuses were torn into pieces.

The firelight lit up the underground city like it was in daylight. The explosive power that he showcased made these soldiers dumbfounded. Rex was shocked, and he mumbled, "Such strong power, even stronger than the ascenders in the legends. Even the Kingdom Tribune Mages are not this strong. Is this the power of the higher world warriors?"

He heard the secrets from the Kingdom Tribune Mages before that the warriors from the higher world were completely different from them, who only used magic. They had all kinds of strange abilities. Now, he had finally witnessed it.

The cannon shattered the defensive spells and the altar easily, and the ceremony was instantly stopped.

Rezar fell to the ground, shocked and furious, overwhelmed with disbelief. He had never thought that the defensive measures that he had spent so many years on would be completely obliterated in a matter of seconds. The strength of this higher world mercenary was far beyond his expectations.

However, Rezar's face changed the next moment. He felt a strong magic power inside his body, crushing that limit in his body. A new power was born.

His eyes widened, and tears rolled down his face.

"Success... I succeeded..."

Although the ceremony had stopped not long after it stopped, the magic that he had absorbed had already helped him break through that limit. He had finally reached the standard that Godora had set; he could head toward the higher world as he had been yearning for.

The increase in power made Rezar have a false sense of confidence like he could defeat everyone with just a wave of his hands, but he did not want to stay and fight. He was about to turn around and activate the explosion runes. While the underground city collapsed, he would then leave through the hidden tunnel. His heart was filled with excitement; his lifelong wish was going to come true.

However, plans very rarely worked out.

Noticing the rapidly increasing energy reaction, Han Xiao raised his eyebrows.

"Yo, broke through to grade B, but..."

The next second, the Void Dragon mechanical suit covered his body. Han Xiao moved beside Rezar as if teleporting. He gripped his head and smashed it heavily into the ground.

Bang!

Before Rezar could react, his head had already struck the ground. His staff slipped out of his hand and rolled far away. The power that he had just gained did not have any effect at all. The feeling of being strong only lasted a few seconds before it was shattered instantly!

"Does it make a difference?"

Chapter 419: The Unobtainable Is Always Tempting (2)

His aged face was pressed tightly against the ground, his gorgeous rope was dirtied with dust, and Rezar was completely unable to move as if he was being held down by a mountain. He was furious and shocked; he had finally seen hope for the lifelong dream, and he could not let it disappear no matter what.

Even if the opponent was someone strong from the higher world, he could still fight!

Rex activated his magic power. A blood-red and blue magic current gushed out from his body, stirring up a strong wind. The faces of Rex and the soldiers who were more than a hundred meters away changed.

[Nitrom Repulsion Ring] pushed away enemies within ten meters radius and was used to deal with enemies who were at a melee range; it was a must-learn spell for Planet Dawn Mages. Its power depended on the Mage's strength. The ring cast by Rezar was the strongest that Rex had ever seen. It was said that only ascenders could have such strong magic power, which meant that Rezar had reached that level.

Rex's face tightened.

The situation had suddenly become much more difficult.

"Get ready to throw spears as backup!" Rex ordered loudly. All the Blue Shield Knights beside him raised their cone-shaped spears and prepared to throw them.

From what he saw, Rezar now had the strength of an ascender and should be on par with the higher world warrior. Hence, he decided to interfere and help just in case. However, when he turned around, he noticed that the other higher world mercenaries had their arms crossed with a calm expression and seemingly no intention to interfere at all.

Lin Ge smiled and said, "You don't have to worry. Black Star's Captain's strength is well known among the mercenary industry in the Garton Star System."

Rex was stunned for a second. He then took a closer look past the gushing spell and realized, no matter how enormous Rezar's magic power was, Han Xiao continued standing still like a reef. His hand was still pressing Rezar firmly on the ground, not budging in the slightest.

At this time, Rezar suddenly noticed that a horrifying power was brewing in the mechanical suit hand pressed on his head, like some kind of strong attack was about to be released on his head. His weak body would definitely not be able to withstand it. In a panic, he could not be concerned with pushing Han Xiao away and was hastily casting all kinds of defense enhancement spells on himself.

The next moment, a gray energy fog appeared around the Void Dragon mechanical suit, flowed down the arm, and shot out from the palm. Rezar's head was being grabbed by Han Xiao's palm, and he faced this energy directly.

Boom!

With a violent explosion, the gray fog surged out!

Like thousands of sharp blades, the gray shockwave spread out. The floor was filled with cracks in an instant like it had been plowed. At the middle of the explosion, a pit with a diameter of almost two meters appeared.

Before the explosion aftershock had yet to disappear, gray light glowed from Han Xiao's body once again. The second energy exploded immediately after.

Void Jet Spray!

Even though the enemy was rather weak, Han Xiao was not taking any chances and gave all he had. Although Rezar was grade B, the same grade as him, Rezar had only just passed through its door and had yet to familiarize himself with his powers.

It was a piece of cake for the Great Mechanic Han to fight this kind of novice grade B.

He used three full capacity Void Jet Sprays continuously without stopping, using 1,170 points of the mechanical suit's energy. Three high damage numbers appeared above Rezar's head, adding up to a total of 4,700 health points. It only took a few seconds. This ability's damage efficiency was extremely high. This was the strongest explosive ability without using [Flaming Will]. [Flaming Will] had a five-minute cooldown, and [Void Jet Spray] had no cooldown. It had become Han Xiao's go-to ace.

The smoke and fog dispersed. Rezar was lying down in the pit, his body covered in wounds from the energy shocks. Void Jet Spray was a pure energy attack, and it contained the Space attribute. Just as the ice attribute could slow and the fire attribute could burn, the direct effect of the space attribute was ignoring a part of the target's resistance.

Having taken damage of more than half his health points in an extremely short time, Rezar was heavily injured and had fainted. A small BOSS character with grade B attributes had been demolished by Han Xiao within ten seconds.

After many combat experiences throughout the nine months, Han Xiao was already very familiar with the Void Dragon mechanical suit's attributes and functions. This Single Unit Battle Suit was definitely one of the top on the list of the strongest mechanical suits in the current level, and Void Jet Spray was a very good ability against Supers of the same level.

"How's the strength difference so big‽" Rex's lips were dry. He was completely astonished. Rezar was already the strongest on Planet Dawn after he gained these powers; even ten of him would not have been able to beat the Rezar. Yet, in front of this mercenary, Rezar was as powerless as an infant.

Are all the people in the higher world this strong‽

The soldiers of Planet Dawn were dazed. Something that was so difficult and important in their eyes had been solved so easily—everyone felt it was almost unreal, like they were in a dream.

Han Xiao pulled Rezar by his collar and threw him before Rex. His mechanical suit folded itself, and he was back in his clothes.

The hundred or so artilleries around them turned back to compressed orbs, rolled on the floor following the attraction of magnetic force, then rolled up to Han Xiao's belt and clothes in a neat queue.

"Done, pack up."

Han Xiao clapped his hands. With his strength now, even crushing the whole of Planet Dawn was a piece of cake.

As if he had just awakened from a dream, Rex ordered his subordinates to tie Rezar up with multiple chains. He explained, "The king wanted me to capture Rezar alive and bring him back for interrogation. We need to know where he learned the ancient ceremony to prevent the possibility of someone else knowing the spell to absorb the Origin Water magic powers..."

"Do whatever you want. My job here is done." Han Xiao raised his eyebrows.

At this time, Rezar woke up slowly, still dizzy. He realized that he was tied up by magic suppressing chains, and the magic in his body was forcibly restrained and could not be used. Subconsciously, he wanted to struggle and resist, then he saw Han Xiao, who stood at the side, and he immediately stopped his actions. As long as Han Xiao was there, resisting would just give him more shame and torture.

However, he could not hold back his rage. He stared at Han Xiao and clenched his teeth tightly.

If not for this external help from the higher world, he would have already succeeded. Before this, he never would have expected the Vain Kingdom's king to be able to call such a strong reinforcement. These people were the culprits that had ruined his plan, Rezar hated their guts.

"Why did you stop me? This obviously has nothing to do with you..."

Han Xiao shrugged and said, "There's no why; it's all a job. I have dealt with dozens of outlaws like you. Thieves have no rights to complain about the police. If you want to blame something, blame it on your luck being bad and meeting us in your act. What's your motive?"

"I just don't want to be trapped in a behind planet forever. Can you understand the feeling of surprise and my dreams shattering when I knew that we were just one of the countless races in the universe?

"We're not special, but that means that we have many friends too. I don't want to be ignorant forever, and I don't want to stay in this planet and wait for my death like the rest of the people here. I want to see the real world!"

Rezar pulled the chains, making clanking sounds.

"Since my ceremony has failed, you have no need to deal with me anymore. Aren't you mercenaries? They can hire you against me, so I can hire you too. Please take me away from Planet Dawn. I can offer all of my wealth as the reward. If you don't need that, I can work for you too..."

Rezar was still making his last struggle. The soldiers at the side heard this and could not help but get nervous. They were afraid that the higher world mercenaries would change sides.

Han Xiao, however, did not hesitate at all to reject the new mission that popped up on his interface, [Rezar's Request]. He said coldly, "Sorry, but Black Star Mercenary Group keeps its words. Furthermore, even if you have quite a good reason, it cannot be an excuse for you to harm the planet."

Rezar was furious and frustrated. He kept silent and let the soldiers pull him by his chains.

After returning to the surface, the army gathered and rested, getting ready to make their return. Rex found Han Xiao and said solemnly, "Captain Black Star, Captain Lin Ge, on behalf of the Vain Kingdom, I invite you heroes to be guests at the palace. The king wants to thank you personally. Do you have the time..."

"Sure, we will go with you then. I can take a look at Planet Dawn on the way." Han Xiao nodded. Of course, this was an excuse; his main goal was to get the intel regarding signs of the Mutation Disaster, and getting intel from the higher-ups of the kingdom was the most convenient way. Since the king had given him such a good opportunity, he was definitely not going to miss it.

"I will stay too, let's go together then." Lin Ge did not want to stay initially, but he saw that Han Xiao accepted the offer, so he changed his mind. He wanted to stay with the Black Star Mercenary Group longer and leave an impression.

The alliance cleared the battlefield quickly. The tribes left in various directions. The Blue Shield Knights escorted Rezar and started heading toward the Vain Kingdom City.

...

Late at night, the Blue Shield Knights stationed themselves on a plain. The night on Planet Dawn was very dark, almost pitch black. The wildlife consisted mostly nocturnal creatures; light could be used to repel them. Illumination spells were deployed around the temporary station as the light source, but it was barely visible.

Rezar was locked in the prison car in the middle of the camp, surrounded by guards in continuous shifts.

In the dark, silent night, inside a single-person tent, Han Xiao opened the galactic communicator and looked at the mercenary hiring panel.

Chapter 420: Surprise Deal

Black Star Mercenary Group

Credibility Rating: 875 (High)

Scale: 173 members

Grade D: 39

Grade C: 132

Grade B: 2

Requests Completed: 76

Main Activity Area: Colton Star Cluster

Resume:

[Sunil Defense Battle]

[Silver Rescue Operation]

[Rosai - Planet 9512 Exploration]

[Juberly Hub 'Letton' Large Stargate Maintenance Guards (Remarks: Eradicating Space Parasites)]

[Capture of Purple Germ Civilization's Head of Rebels 'Pilipelapa Wasasa']

[71 more missions... (Expand/Collapse)]

Creator: Black Star – Han Xiao

Creation date: Galaxy Calendar Year 688, 02 October

Summary: Small to medium-sized mercenary group with a very good name, very high credibility, and strong ability. Completed hiring missions with high ratings multiple times, and most mercenaries under their command are undead. Partner with many large armies. Stationed in the Juberly Hub, often responsible for matters happening around them. Operates under the Dragon Emperor Ames. They are a dependable mercenary group that is active in the Colton Star Cluster. Mainly accepts combat and guarding missions, very trustworthy.

In nine months, Black Star Mercenary Group's resume had become a lot richer.

With players as the combat power, not only did they not suffer any manpower reduction, but their income was increased too; it was very convenient. In the nine months, he had only taken on hiring missions from partners. They had grown while keeping a low profile and made quite a fortune.

His savings were now 784,000 Enas. Other than buying some materials, metals, and parts to build new machinery, he had saved the rest and planned to use it to complete the class advancement mission. With so much money, buying one high-end knowledge would not be a problem, but it would be difficult to buy two.

According to the standard of galactical mercenaries, Planet Dawn's mission was very easy; therefore, the reward was not high. However, he had not accepted the mission for the reward alone.

Han Xiao planned to gain some information about the Mutation Disaster on Planet Dawn, so he told the spaceships waiting outside Planet Dawn to leave first. He had hitched a ride with the spaceship to this place. It was really great to have so many partners; he did not have to spend money on traveling at all. It was even better than Uber.

The dim light from the communicator's screen reflected on his face.

The International League is in a few days. After the things here are done, I shall bring the team back to Juberly Hub. Three months ago... which is two weeks ago for the players, the Competition Alliance announced the system for the first international finals. The online store will be selling Gathering Crystals to the qualified players, which has a similar effect to Dungeon Crystals and will gather them from all planets to a simulated stadium. The entire competition will be recorded and broadcasted live on all channels.

The system of the first season was the same as the previous life. The international competition would only be held in real environments after the players were able to carry out interstellar travel. By then, the stage would be planets and star systems.

The players from the Chinese clubs had been following him for a year; they had earned a lot, and their equipment was very strong. Thus, their performance in the international competition would definitely be better than in his previous life.

In his previous life, the performance of the Chinese clubs in the first season had been quite enraging. To avoid spoiling their reputation or taking the blame, their battle style had been very cowardly and time-consuming or way too steady. Sometimes, they were able to outlast the enemy, but sometimes, after stalling and wasting a lot of time, they still lost. It was difficult and upsetting to watch.

Hence, it had led to very few people watching the competition every time the Chinese teams were competing. The players preferred to watch other countries' contestants passionately fight each other and would all directly skip the fights with Chinese teams. Although China's result in the first season was acceptable, they did not make any impression or notable performance at all. Their first impression on players around the world was that they were very good at dealing with pressure.

If they don't fight tougher this time, they will've followed me for nothing.

When the International League ends, the version update should come soon too. The players will disappear temporarily, and by then, the rewards from accepting requests will not be as high anymore. When the time comes, I shall not do mercenary work for some time. Since moving in a team is more mobile and swifter, it's more suitable to do some preparation for Version 2.0 Mutation Disaster. It's going to require some planning. While doing that, I can also recruit some main character type people and increase the number of officers...

As he was thinking, Han Xiao's senses felt a tiny abnormality. Han Xiao's eyes swayed, and he stood up and walked out of the tent. It was silent. He looked around and was stunned for a second.

The prison car in the middle of the camp was gone. Rezar was nowhere to be found, and the guards were missing too.

"Escaped?"

He did not want any accidents to happen on the mission, so he equipped his mechanical suit and scanned with its radar. Then he discovered that Rezar's signal was in a small forest just outside the camp. Beside him were signals from about a dozen soldiers, and there was another individual signal hidden not far away from them. That signal's strength was much higher than the soldiers'. Han Xiao checked through the database and realized that it was unexpectedly from the commander of the Knights, Rex.

The other soldiers are all asleep. What are they taking Rezar to the bush at night for? Holy, can it be...

Han Xiao took a deep breath in.

That is an old man!

They have a really unique taste!

Han Xiao walked into the forest on tiptoes, terrified, ready to turn away and run anytime he saw something dirty. He activated his night vision and looked inside the forest extremely carefully.

Rezar was tied tightly by the magic suppressing chains, and a few knights surrounded him with steel swords in their hands.

Their lips moved, and they seemed to be saying something. Han Xiao increased the output of the sound collection function in the battle suit and heard their conversation.

"I will ask you one last time, where did you get the ceremony from?"

"I found a stone tablet under the Ancient Ruins, on it was the incomplete method of carrying out the ceremony. I changed the spell into using blood as the energy source. How many more times do you want me to say it?"

"Who else knows about this spell?"

"No one. After I memorized the spell, I destroyed the tablet. Do you think I would tell others such a dangerous spell? It's only safe in my hands."

Rezar's face was full of impatience as he replied to the knight.

This knight rubbed his hands, and he said with a tone of suppressed excitement, "How about this, let's make a deal. You tell us the method of carrying out the ceremony, and I will let you live. Frankly, I am... quite interested in the higher world as well."

Rezar's eyes brightened like he had caught the last straw to save his life.

Hahaha, there is always a way out!

Rezar pondered, and a sense of derision appeared on his face. He felt that after he told them of the method, these people would definitely kill him. He secretly raised his alert and asked, "How do I know you don't just want to trick me out of my spell?"

"We are the guards on duty during this time," the knight before him said. "If you die, it will easily be traced back to us."

"Are you not afraid of me killing you after I escape?" Rezar said with narrowed eyes.

"Humph, do you dare? As soon as there is magic movement, these higher world mercenaries will come to deal with you."

"If I run, won't you people be traced as well?"

"Hehe, this is not a question that you need to worry about."

"What if, after you let me go, you immediately alert the rest?"

"Then you can go ahead and sell us out."

With the conversation, Rezar gradually started to believe that these knights really did want to make a deal with him. His tightened nerves became more relaxed. His attention was completely on talking with the knight in front of him, and he did not notice that a few knights behind him secretly raised their steel swords and aimed at his vital parts.

Even if Rezar was at grade B, if he was penetrated by steel swords when his powers were suppressed, his life would still be in danger.

Han Xiao secretly observed the situation, his eyes swayed as he saw this. He had thought that these knights wanted Rezar's spell. The deal was almost coming to an end, yet they suddenly wanted to kill him?

Seeing that these knights were about to attack, Han Xiao thought about it and walked out.

Hearing the footsteps, the people immediately turned around. When they saw who it was, they were all shocked.

Rezar's face changed immediately. You again!

If their conversation had been overheard, his tinder of hope would be extinguished once again.

Han Xiao looked around and noticed that although these knights were surprised, they did not panic like their private deal had been found out.

"What's going on?" Han Xiao decided to speak first.

"Yo—you heard?" a knight asked carefully.

"Guess." Han Xiao's eyes landed on his steel sword.

"Kill him!" that knight yelled as he turned around and stabbed his sword at Rezar's chest, blood splashing all over.

Han Xiao's expression was strange. He had thought that these knights were going to fight him, but what was happening now?

Rezar's eyes widened. Before he could react, the other knights lunged at him with their swords. Han Xiao's outline swayed, and these knights could only see a flash before their bodies fell back in the air. They were all sent flying by Han Xiao's kicks in an instant.

"Although I don't know what's going on, I shall stop you first."

Han Xiao looked at Rezar. This guy was kneeling on the ground. His face was pale, and he was gasping for air. Although he was a Mage, he had at least more than one hundred Endurance, so he would not die. The steel sword did not cut too deep, but it probably penetrated his lungs, so he was having a hard time breathing.

"Can anyone explain this?" Han Xiao glanced at the knights. They closed their mouths and did not say anything.

Han Xiao turned to look at the deeper side of the forest and said to the darkness, "The one hiding, they're not speaking, so you will explain it to me."

The sound of footsteps approaching appeared in the forest. Having hidden for a long time at the side, Rex walked out with a serious face. He knew that he could not hide anymore as soon as Han Xiao appeared.

Rex took a deep breath and said slowly, "These knights are my supporters. I arranged for them to be on duty at the same time. Bringing Rezar here was to kill him."

Han Xiao raised his eyebrows and said, "Isn't he already captured? Why bother killing him secretly? Just kill him in broad daylight."

Rex shook his head and said, "The king wanted me to capture him alive, interrogate him openly, and lock him in a cell. Captain Black Star, you're not someone from our kingdom, so I shall tell you bluntly. For criminals at the level of ascenders like Rezar, the higher-ups of the kingdom will very likely give them to the Godoran emissary in exchange for something. This way, Rezar will still be alive, and his dream of going to the higher world will become true as well. When it comes to this kind of person that almost killed a million of others for his own sake, I don't even want to give him the slightest chance of staying alive!

"Also, Rezar knows the ceremony to absorb the Origin Water. Maybe someone in the kingdom is interested and might force him to share the ceremony spell in exchange for not killing him. Then this horrifying spell might be leaked out. If that happens, something like this will happen again. Therefore, even if this means disobeying orders from the king, I can't let him reach the Kingdom City alive!

"As long as we kill him this way, we can use the excuse of Rezar trying to escape to cover up his death. Captain Black Star, I appreciate your timely assistance very much, but this is our kingdom's matter. Please do not interfere."

Rex spoke in a very justified tone. Although he clearly knew that he was no match for Han Xiao, he did not intend to back off.

Han Xiao now understood.

So, that's what happened. As it turns out, the deal was a trick to divert Rezar's attention. Quite a smart plan.

He sized Rex up. Being so full of justice, could he be another main character type of person?

Or... did you make up an excuse long ago and are lying?

Han Xiao pointed at Rezar and said, "Since you don't want him to go back alive, how about giving him to me? It's easier for you this way."

"What do you want him for?" Rex frowned.

"That's not for you to know. Anyway, I will take him into the galaxy... er, the higher world, far away from you, and never let him come back here."

Rezar heard this and was immediately surprised; going to the higher world was something that he had dreamed every day. He was already in a hopeless situation, but now he felt like he had found hope again!

However, when he looked up, he saw Han Xiao smiling at him with unknown meanings in his eyes. That look was almost wicked and giving out a cold aura.

Rezar felt a chill, and the excitement immediately dissipated.

His intuition suddenly told him that this was probably not good news...

Chapter 421: Super-Gene Extractor and Temporary Character Summon Card

Boom!

The explosion awakened the night.

The Blue Shield Knights in the camp walked out of their tents and looked at the forest not far away with suspicion. Thick smoke was rising inside the forest. They turned around and were shocked to realize that Rezar was missing.

"The prisoner has escaped!" someone shouted.

The knights hastily picked up their shields and steel swords and hurried to the scene of the explosion.

As they entered the forest, they saw Han Xiao standing before a huge pit. Inside was a corpse that was as burnt as charcoal, unidentifiable.

Rex 'hastily' arrived at the scene and demanded with a serious face, "What happened here?"

"Your prisoner almost escaped, and I caught him." Han Xiao shrugged and said, "As you can see, I accidentally played too much."

"Rezar is dead‽" The knights were shocked.

Rex's expression changed. He shook his head and said, "The king wants him alive. He should not have died, but sadly, he decided to die..."

As the commander, he concluded this matter with just a few words. He strictly punished a few guards on duty then ordered the knights under his command to go back to sleep. The people saw this and did not bother too much about it. Since Rezar had died, there was no need to escort him anymore, and they would not have to be nervous on their way back anymore.

Many people heaved a sigh of relief and felt content. Most people had the same thought as Rex and wanted Rezar dead. The hometown of some knights was the Southland territory, and Rezar had almost killed their family. If not for the higher world warriors, the outcome would have been unimaginable. Despite Rezar's failure, they could not take it as if nothing had happened.

A few old soldiers who had followed Rex a long time realized something and gave Rex a meaningful look. They knew their commander well; this 'escape' was most likely planned and acted out for the sake of the king and those royalties who wanted to capture Rezar alive. Killing Rezar was to prevent others with vicious intentions from benefitting from him and causing more harm. Rex had a very good reputation among the army and was loved. Furthermore, the soldiers did not have very good impressions of the royals. Without any discussion, they all took it as they knew nothing.

After everyone dispersed, Rex nodded at Han Xiao and left.

Han Xiao did not return to the camp but walked further away instead. In the dark night, he came to the back of a small hill. Rezar had been thrown there, and Herlous was guarding him with his arms crossed.

In the end, Rex had given Rezar up. Although he really wanted to kill Rezar, he did not have much of a choice with Han Xiao, so he could only believe Han Xiao's words.

"How is he?" Han Xiao asked.

"The wound on his chest is bandaged, so he won't die," Herlous replied.

"Good. I'm going to King City with the knights. You'll need to stay in the wild with Rezar. When I'm done, we will call a spaceship and leave together."

Herlous nodded. He sized up Rezar and questioned, "Black Star, are you actually recruiting this Mage? He's not the good kind at all."

"Do I look like I'm that short of people?" Han Xiao padded his back and said, "Don't forget, I promised to bring hundreds of thousands of Supers to solve Sunil's problems. I'm not interested in him."

"Alright then, I will listen to you and stay to guard him. If he wants to run, I'll slash him."

Herlous trusted Han Xiao a lot. He knew that his fate was bonded with Han Xiao. In the beginning, he had joined Black Star full of doubt, but after going through so much together, he strongly believed that Han Xiao had the ability to live up to his promises when he recruited him. Han Xiao had the ability to change the future of his race.

"Since you're not recruiting him, what do you want him for?" Herlous asked.

Rezar looked up at Han Xiao. His aged face was filled with horror, no idea what awaited him next.

"You'll see."

Han Xiao took out a small suction cup-shaped device, in the middle of which were many tiny needles. He pressed it on Rezar's arm where his veins were closer to the surface. The needles penetrate into his veins, slowly sucked his blood, and gradually released a dim magic light.

Rezar suddenly felt he was losing the magic power in his body. Terrified, he looked at the device on his arm.

This thing was sucking his magic!

"No! No!" He struggled with all his might, but his strength was disappearing very quickly.

Magic was disappearing continuously. Very soon, more wrinkles appeared on Rezar's face like he had become ten years older. A sense of weakness filled his body, and he felt like he was back in his childhood when he was just an ordinary person.

"Where's my power‽ Give me back my power!"

He had gained the power of an ascender for less than half a day, and before he could feel that power fully, he had already lost it. Rezar almost fainted.

Even when the twenty-year plan failed, he had not been this desperate. Power was the foundation of his confidence, and Han Xiao took that away from him.

With his power lost, Rezar's mind seemed to have become an ordinary person too... no, not even as strong as an ordinary person. He was crying and begging.

Han Xiao shook his head. Some people used their power to do whatever they wanted and be evil, and when they lost it, they became cowards.

The device in his hand was indeed the [Super-Gene Extractor—Test Version] that he had gotten from DarkStar. Herlous saw this, and a chill ran down his spine. "Quickly, put it away. I'm afraid."

A few months ago, Han Xiao had tested the effect of the extractor. The first test subject was Frenzied Sword. The effect of it on players was absorbing twenty to fifty points of a random attribute and a certain amount of energy from them, which could be given to another person. The duration of it was ten minutes to two hours. In his previous life, the Super-Gene Extractor was controlled by DarkStar. The players could only get [Broken Super-Gene Extractor] after completing highly difficult related missions. Its effect was similar to the one that he had but weaker. The practicality of the extractor was very low in combat, as it had to be in direct contact with the body of the target to take effect. Most people had physical or magical armor, so it was very hard for it to work. Furthermore, the target had to be under control and not fidget around. The prerequisite to use it was very tough.

The hidden function of the extractor would only take effect when the target was completely unguarded, such as sleeping, enslaved, paralyzed, or willing, which meant that the target had to be under complete control. If the players were affected by it unluckily, they would enter a twelve-hour weakness period where their attributes would decrease by thirty to ninety percent, depending on the extractor output. If it was used on an NPC, not only would that NPC also become weak, it would also generate an ability potion. Drinking that potion would grant a certain ability from the target, which would be shown as a Temporary Character Summon Card on the players' interface.

The second test subject that contributed to this result to Han Xiao was indeed Herlous. Herlous vividly remembered the sense of terror and weakness when his power was taken away, and he was horrified of it. When Han Xiao used it on him, he had only used a low small output, but even so, Herlous had needed many days to recover from it. Things like this that could take away Super-Genes were the natural enemy of Supers!

How many Supers did the organization that invented this device destroy in the process?

Han Xiao took out three empty tubes and poured the blood extracted by the device inside.

You have received [Ability Potion] x 3.

He drank one tube straight away. The sweet and metallic taste filled his mouth. The warm blood flowed down his throat, and it was very spicy on the nose. Then, a warmth that belonged to magic power rippled in his body.

You have received [Character Summon Card—Rezar (Temporary)]!

Character Summon Card—Rezar (Temporary): [Origin Water Magic Power]

Temporarily grants power beyond one's self. +20% All Attributes.

Duration: 5 – 15 mins

Usage: 0/1 (This Character Summon Card will exist for: 15 days)

A buff, not a bad ability at all. Han Xiao was quite satisfied.

Rezar had only lost his magic power temporarily, but this crying old guy did not know that. This meant that Han Xiao could keep shearing him and make many Ability Potions. Although the temporary Character Summon Card's ability would be different, he believed that the players would be willing to pay for this new product.

In his previous life, DarkStar had used the Super-Gene Extractor to carry out this plan. The difference was, Han Xiao would not capture people as batteries out of nowhere. The temporary Character Summon Card was just an add-on for him—he had no need for it. Only when he met someone that he could use it on without conflicting with his morals would he do it.

"I recall that you begged me to bring you to the higher world. Hehe, now, I promise you I will."

Han Xiao's smile was like a demon's in Rezar's eyes. This old guy shivered in terror.

Going to the higher world like this was the exact opposite of how he had thought it would be. A strong sense of regret filled his heart and climbed into his eyes.

"Yo—you're a demon..." Rezar wanted to roar but could only speak these words softly.

Han Xiao was amused. You're calling me a demon?

...

Two days later, the Blue Shield Knights returned to King City. This city was sitting on a plain, and the Origin Water river split the city in half from the middle, separating it into the East and West Shore, at the same time dividing the classes. The East Shore had royal mansions and palaces, beautiful and luxurious. The West Shore was the crowded civilian area, filled with buildings and all kinds of pollution pipes, forming the complex streets. Only the people who had lived there for more than ten years could remember the roads. The usual people would lose their way after a few turns.

It was now noon, and a bean-sized sun hung high in the sky. The lights were dim and gave the city a dark yellow shade. The buildings and streets shrouded each other. It was like dusk under the sunset, but this was the brightest time of the day in Planet Dawn.

Rex brought everyone to the East Shore and settled near the palace. The steward came to welcome them, and his attitude was more polite and respectful than when he faced the king. He bowed so low that it was as if he wanted to plant his head in the ground.

"On behalf of the Vain Kingdom, I welcome you to Planet Dawn. His highness has invited the higher world warriors to join the palace for dinner. We hope that you can give us the pleasure. By then, our ascenders will communicate with you through the Kingdom Tribune Mages and make payment for the reward of this hire."

The people had no objection.

Han Xiao's main goal of this trip was to ask around about the signs of the Mutation Disaster, and it was the perfect opportunity to ask the king. If the palace dinner was the type of party that allowed him to move around freely, he would then ask the King for intel.

Chapter 422: Sign of Mutation and Beginning of the Finals

When night came, it was bright in the palace. Han Xiao and the others accepted the invitation, changed into formal clothes given by the steward, and attended the dinner banquet. The waiter of the palace led them to the garden courtyard that was already set up as an outdoor banquet area. The warm, bright light expelled the darkness of the night. On the long tables were exquisite dishes; green, yellow, and purple fruits and vegetables; the fragrant roasted meat from unknown beats, the sweet pies with overflowing cream, and the light blue liquors made from Origin Water. Waiters roamed the place with a plate on their hand, and a musician sat in the middle and played a joyful rhythm with a strange-looking instrument. Meanwhile, the light blue-skinned Vainerian royalties chitchatted in the courtyard. The banquet had just started. At a corner of the courtyard was a pavilion, inside which were the Vain King and the supreme royalties. They looked at the courtyard entrance. Seeing that the higher world warriors had arrived, the King cleared his throat and led the others to stand up.

"Everyone, welcome to the palace dinner banquet. I'm Galo Mio, thank you for your kind assistance," the King said. 'Mio' in the Vainerian language meant king or leader, and it was how the king addressed himself.

King Galo was a rather built middle-aged man. As he was saying his appreciation speech, he walked down from the pavilion and welcomed Han Xiao and the rest personally. The other royals stopped their conversations and greeted them together. In front of the guests from the higher worlds, they knew that their royal status meant nothing. This was a level difference, similar to a native tribe chief facing guests from a developed civilization, but the difference was larger. The higher world warriors were dragons that were strong enough to ignore the local overlords.

Lin Ge clearly expressed that Han Xiao was the leader, so Han Xiao had no choice but to take on the conversation. They exchanged pleasantries, playing down their roles. Then King Galo told a joke that was not funny at all, yet the royalties laughed out loud like it was some kind of extremely funny tease.

A group of Kingdom Tribune Mages walked out while holding up the Galactic Communicator. They handled it so carefully like it was some kind of holy relic. After some clicks and pressed, the hologram of an 'ascender' appeared in the middle of the courtyard, sparking shocked awe among the Vainerians. Han Xiao heard an old royalty beside him saying to his offspring, "Treasure this moment. We can only see an act of God like this when there are important guests."

The oldest Volga curled his lips and said, "These people are so ignorant."

The second brother glanced at him and said, "Weren't we like this when we were young, too?"

The oldest brother had nothing to say. He turned around and saw that their youngest brother was already ramming down a beast drumstick with oil around his mouth.

King Galo spoke a few words with this ascender. The ascender thanked them for their help and sent the money to their accounts, then ended the communication. King Galo smiled and said, "Please enjoy the food and drinks. This is a joyous occasion."

The people fitted into the atmosphere of the banquet. Royals came to talk with them from time to time with a stiff and curious attitude. There were also shows at the banquet. Not long after, a group of female dancers appeared. They jumped and turned in the crowds with seduction in their eyes.

Han Xiao had no feeling toward these blue-skinned Vainerians at all. He drank some Origin Water liquor, turned around, and saw Aroshia staring at the dining table, seemingly hesitant as to whether she should eat any food or not.

Han Xiao walked over, placed a hand around her shoulder out of habit, and said, "There won't be any combat for the foreseeable future. You don't have to use your powers. Eat something."

Aroshia did not seem to care much about Han Xiao's actions. She picked up a purple food and bit her lip. She did not need food to live as she automatically absorbed stray energy from the environment around her to sustain her energy use, which was supposedly a characteristic of energy lives. However, back then, Han Xiao was curious about what would happen if she ate something and convinced her to consume some food. Although Aroshia had no sense of hunger, she felt that consuming food was interesting after tasting how delicious food was. Eating then became an entertainment activity for her. Compared to her blur and extremely calm personality nine months ago, Aroshia was now more human-like.

Aroshia's digestive system was very strong, and all her food would be decomposed into energy without any waste, so she did not need to excrete. However, a very weird accident happened. Her Energize Esper power could only be used on herself and not on anything external. Before her food was completely digested and turned into energy, the leftovers in her stomach that had yet to be digested would drop out in a splashing way. At that time, they were just about to start a battle with some enemies, and this scene shocked both sides. The food pulp had splashed out below the ball of energy that Aroshia turned into, and the areas had fallen into a deep, awkward silence.

Ever since then, Aroshia would always count the dates before consuming any food, calculating whether she would need to use her powers before her food was digested. Her Esper power strength was rocketing, and it was not much slower than the players. She was already at grade C+, only half a grade away from grade B in the mission requirements.

After lifting and putting the fruit down multiple times, Aroshia took a bite in the end. Joy appeared on her face, and she passed the fruit that she had taken a bite from to Han Xiao and said, "It's delicious, try it."

Han Xiao bit on the fruit. His face was then immediately covered in wrinkles. He pushed Aroshia's hand away and said, "It's so sour! Your taste is too different from mine, keep it for yourself."

Han Xiao guided her to train her energy. After spending more time with each other, Aroshia was closer to Han Xiao. Their interactions were very intimate, but there were no inappropriate thoughts. Han Xiao did not look at Aroshia as a normal female being at all. In his eyes, she was a sexless and pure energy form. Aroshia did not see herself as a female either, so these intimate actions were very natural to her.

After walking to the side, Han Xiao thought that it was time to have a talk with King Galo. King Galo invited Han Xiao into the pavilion and asked with a smile, "Captain Black Star, what did you want to talk to me about?"

Han Xiao lowered his voice and said, "I have a special kind of intuition ability. When I arrived on this planet, I felt that there was some kind of virus from space that's here on Planet Dawn."

King Galo was shocked. He sat up straight and said, "Are you saying that our planet is infected by some kind of illness‽"

"No no, this is just a feeling. The details still require some research on if there were any similar symptoms appearing on a large scale, only then can the virus be confirmed to exist."

King Galo took it very seriously and ordered the steward to arrange the intel of all the territories. The Vain Kingdom had existed for many years and had a very large intel network. The lords of the territories would submit reports of their territories once every certain period, so it was very easy to collect."

Not long after, the steward returned to the courtyard and sorted out a few pages of a report. King Galo took a look, shook his head, and said, "It's all usual infectious diseases; there don't seem to be any new symptoms in a large scale..."

Han Xiao raised his eyebrow and said, "It might not be falling sick. It can also be some kind of unusual behavior, such as... sleeping more than usual?"

King Galo froze for a moment. Who would check on the sleeping quality of others out of nowhere? Everyone slept with their doors closed, and no one would talk about how their sleep was the previous night with every person that they met. There was no record of the sleeping quality of the people.

"Hmm?" King Galo suddenly thought of something. "This year's mineral production from the territories is sixteen percent less than last year, but the mines did not dry out, and the number of miners is more than last year. The factor that could have affected the production rate... can only be the duration of work. Maybe it has something to do with this?"

"Maybe." Han Xiao gave King Galo another look. This king seemed quite capable as he was able to notice a hidden connection between matters that did not seem to have any relation.

The incubation period of the mutation virus was very long, and the means of its spreading were many. The early-stage symptoms of the infected were sleeping more than usual and drowsiness. The symptoms would gradually become worse, and the infected could sleep for even two to three days. That would be when the mutation virus was close to erupting. When the virus became more mature, the incubation period would become shorter, and the symptoms would become worse. The drowsiness period might even be entirely skipped, and the symptoms would enter the next stage. According to the version time, the mutation virus at this moment was still in its infancy, so it was very hidden.

I wonder how Planet Aquamarine is now.

King Galo was rather worried. He asked if there were any solutions for it. Han Xiao shook his head and told him that he did not know what virus it was either, but they had better be cautious about it, then he left. Han Xiao had already gotten the information that he wanted and reminded King Galo, so Planet Dawn would at least not be totally unprepared. After all, this planet was one of the mission targets as well.

During the incubation period of the mutation virus, Han Xiao had no solution for it. Unless he was willing to give up on the yet to start [Mutation Disaster] mission and face a huge risk by giving the seventh generation Mutation Source to Godora before the disaster began so that they could make a cure for it, which would also lead to him being questioned and suspected as well. This was not worth it at all. He could only maximize the value of the things he had when the disaster struck and caused Godora and DarkStar to fight directly.

The only preparation I can make for the Mutation Disaster is to become stronger—everything else has to wait for the right time.

The next day, Han Xiao kindly rejected King Galo's invitation and left King City. He called the spaceship of a nearby partner out in the wild, picked up Herlous and Rezar, and headed back to Juberly Hub.

Lin Ge got Han Xiao's communication number and left joyfully with his people as well.

Black Star Mercenary Group was now considered quite well known in Juberly Hub, and they could finally enjoy the same privileges that they had seen given to the Sky Ring allies when they first arrived at Juberly Hub. They did not have to queue and had priority in many services. When they walked on the street, many mercenaries and passersby greeted them with respect and kindness.

After going back to the stronghold, Han Xiao knocked Rezar unconscious, placed him in an empty room as a cell, and left him there for the time being. There was something more important that needed attention at the time.

The International League would begin in three days!

The International Leagues were divided into two stages. The first stage was the point-based regular competition, where the top eight teams and top sixteen Singles contestants would enter the international finals.

The second stage was the finals where two teams battled each other through best of fives until the final champion was decided.

In China, the qualified teams were King Admiral's Dynasty, Hao Tian's Long Sky, and Li Ge's Temple of God. The Singles contestants were King Admiral, SnowFlower, and Frenzied Sword.

The other unqualified pro players helped them to train and lent equipment to them generously. In important times like this, everyone had put down their past grudges and become united. The clubs in all the countries did the same, giving the best equipment and abilities to the contestants.

This was the first international competition, so other than King Admiral, who was the calmest, all the other contestants were somewhat nervous. Not only them, but all the pro players in the various countries had the same feeling, nervous and anticipation.

A festival was around the corner, and the passion of the players had been ignited once again. The forums were filled with information on clubs from all the countries, and all kinds of analysis and prediction posts appeared. Compared to regional competitions, international competitions were much more vigorous. Players from different countries came together to discuss. It was very boisterous on the forums.

Bun-Hit-Dog enjoyed the benefits of being in a favorable position. He temporarily stopped the Black Star Series that already had sixteen episodes and started to make a special episode featuring the pre-competition interviews of the Chinese contestants in the mercenary group.

Chapter 423: Debut

"The international competition is about to commence. We've invited a few captains and contestants to be with us today for a simple pre-competition interview."

The location of the video was Han Xiao's stronghold in Juberly Hub. Four pro players sat on the sofa and accepted the interview from Bun-Hit-Dog. The four of them were King Admiral, Hao Tian, Li Ge, and Frenzied Sword, all either captains of the qualified teams or contestants in the Singles. SnowFlower, who had gotten second place in the Singles, did not enter Han Xiao's galactic team and was still on Planet Aquamarine, so he was not included in the interview.

The four of them greeted the audience, and the regular interview started. Bun-Hit-Dog was different from his usual style like he had become the host of Galaxy Times. He sat up very straight, and his face was very serious. However, no matter how formal his actions were, it could not cover his cheeky personality.

The questions in the interview were all regular questions, asking about their confidence, preparations, and goals. They were all typical questions.

When asked if they were confident, who would dare say no in front of such a large audience? Do you want your club to close down?

How did they prepare? Who would expose such confidential information directly? If the opponents saw it, there would be no end to the scolding that they received!

Target in the competition? Which club would say they did not want to be the champion? Even if their target was just top four or even top eight, how could they say it openly? Pro players all wanted to be champions!

The four pro players answered these questions with ease, giving typical responses. After these questions were finished, Bun-Hit-Dog started to chitchat with the four of them. In an informal interview like this, the topic could be more casual. Bun-Hit-Dog stated some good foreign players for them to comment on, and the atmosphere was rather peaceful.

"Who do you think are the strong opponents that you need to pay attention to in this competition?" Bun-Hit-Dog asked.

Li Ge pondered and said, "Tulips Club from France; Team Devil, Team Thunder Snake, and Team Key from America; Rose Knight from the United Kingdom, Team Hydra from Japan, Kimchi Club from Korea, and so on. I'm looking forward to battling with these teams and players. Although the opponents are very strong, I am confident."

The teams were all top teams in their respective countries. Their positions in their country were the same as the positions of the four biggest clubs in China.

Bun-Hit-Dog nodded, looked at the other three, and said, "What about you guys? Which are the opponents that you need to take more seriously?"

"None," King Admiral said.

"My opponent is only myself," Hao Tian said.

Frenzied Sword looked left and right at the confident and proud godly players beside him, swallowed his saliva, and said cautiously, "I—I think Li Ge put it well..."

Hao Tian and King Admiral glanced at him with 'too young, too naïve' and 'we expected you to be better than this' in their eyes. Frenzied Sword shrunk his neck from the stare.

Li Ge gave a very stiff smile. He was so tempted to take his shoes off and slam them on these two captains. Do you think I don't know what you're saying between the lines‽

The interview was going on joyfully, and the comment section was very active.

Key of Solomon quickly watched the Chinese interview and switched to the interviews of the other countries.

In France, Tulips' captain [Lost Angel] accepted the interview.

"Which opponents are the ones I pay more attention to? Hmm... the three teams from China, I guess. They're very strong opponents, and I think most teams agree on that too, haha. Plus, King Admiral and I are old rivals."

Lost Angel was a senior player, so he replied to the questions with a smile on his face, and his voice was soft and warm.

Key of Solomon then watched the interviews from other countries as well. Whenever the host asked about which opponents were threatening, China's name was definitely in the list. Every team was taking the Chinese teams very seriously.

The Esports standard of China was not too bad and could be considered as tier one, but this was the first time that they had received so much attention from all the teams. This came from the opportunities that they had. China was the only country where the contesting players had been given the opportunity to enter the interstellar stage in advance. These foreign clubs had always been paying attention to the China players' experience in the Black Star Mercenary Group. They were deemed as very strong opponents.

After exiting the forums, Key of Solomon looked at his teammates in the room and said calmly, "Apparently, the other teams have the same thoughts as us. The Chinese teams are a problem."

Outside the house, the ground was covered in snow that extended beyond the horizon. Demon nest military camps scattered across the land, and demon army roamed around from time to time. This house was an army camp as well. The players there, including Key of Solomon, all had the looks of the Demon Race—the race shown on their interfaces was Young Demon. They were more than two meters tall, and they had short sheep's horns extending from their forehead, a tail behind their back, thick and strong legs, and black Demon scales on their body. They were equipped with armor and weapons. Although their faces were ferocious, they still had some sort of human features, differentiating them from each other.

This was the base camp that America had chosen, one of the planets of the Extinguish Army—Planet Winterfrost. These were all renowned pro players of the Club Key.

Electrolux, who was far away on Planet Aquamarine, was a retired player of Club Key. Key was very passionate in planting scouts and spies. In fact, they had a mature team for it, providing all sorts of intel and help to their team.

The captain, Key of Solomon was an official account registered by the club, and every captain used the same name. The previous captain retired, and this generation's 'Key of Solomon' had been given the position last year. He defeated all the players in the team through the selection process. Club Key saw extraordinary potential in him, so they had made an exception and made him the captain, deciding to focus on training him for a long time. They had very high hopes for him. Key's higher-ups planned to use one to two seasons to build an ace team surrounding him and a few old members, gambling on their future, hoping to achieve three consecutive championships. This was also the dream of every team out there.

This generation's Key of Solomon was not as steady as the old players. He was known for being quick and fierce in both his combat style and commanding style. The higher-ups had very high hopes of him, but he felt it was what he deserved because of how capable he was. He was arrogant, but he had the right to be. His teammates, fans, and the superiors all admired his sharpness.

Humility is a virtue in China but not in America. Being direct and proud were the characteristics of American players.

In the first league season, most of the clubs only planned to observe the situation, train their team, and familiarize themselves with the competition, and they did not have too much desire for the results. However, Key of Solomon was not like others; he had only one goal—the championship!

"There are many opponents, but there are only a few strong ones that can obstruct us. China's Dynasty is one of them. Other than these obstructions, the other teams are no threat; they're all just prey for us to gain more points..."

Key of Solomon placed his legs on the table and glanced over his teammates. He had a confident and contemptuous smile on his face.

"Guys, let me lead you to become the champion!"

...

Three days quickly passed.

Han Xiao settled the matters of the mercenary group. He temporarily did not accept any requests and announced that they wanted to rest for a period of time. The international competition would last three to four months, and Han Xiao planned to give the players some holiday at the start for about a month. He was going to rest for some time as well, getting his hands on his class advancement requirements and subclasses.

Today was the day of the International League commencement. Han Xiao stayed in his room and opened the forums. At the top of it was a live-stream of the International League, which had yet to begin.

In the stronghold hall, all the Black Star players had gathered. The contesting players were surrounded in the middle, waiting for the store to start selling Gathering Crystals.

Frenzied Sword rubbed his hands together. The thought of battling with pro players from various countries made him nervous. He had never been to such a big stage before.

"I've made a name for myself in the area competition, but if I don't perform well in the international competition, more than half of the hard work before this would go to waste. Only if I perform well in the international competition can I maintain my fame or even increase it!" Frenzied Sword was spirited in his heart. He prayed for himself to not underperform.

On the other side, Hao Tian, King Admiral, and Li Ge were talking to each other.

"If one of us is unfortunately in the same group as the other, it's best for us to cooperate. If one team ends up having absolutely no chance of qualifying, that team can help the other team in the same group. If we meet each other, let's not go all out," Li Ge said.

Hao Tian intercepted him and said calmly, "I will go all out no matter who the opponent is. My professionalism doesn't allow me to hold back."

King Admiral yawned and said lazily, "You can't beat me even if I hold back."

Li Ge was furious. Why can't the two of them see the big picture!

We are now representing China, if we don't get good places, we're wrong no matter what. It will cause a huge negative impact on the name of the teams. The result is the only thing that's important in competitions. For the sake of getting better results, what's wrong with some suitable adjustments?

We have to be flexible!

At this time, a notification popped up on the interface of the contestants. They hurriedly opened the store; the Gathering Crystal was already available for purchase.

They crushed it as soon as they bought it. Fog popped out from the crystal and wrapped around them. When the fog was gone, the contestants disappeared. Just like the effects of Dungeon Crystals, they entered a duplicated scene.

With a flash in Frenzied Sword's eyes, the surrounding environment changed completely. He was in a huge arena, and beside him were the other China contestants. Looking away, players of different races appeared out of nowhere one after another.

The players from the various countries appeared. They stood in groups and sized each other up. The account names above their heads were all famous.

"French Tulips, UK Rose Knights, American Devils, Thunder Snakes, Swedish Tomahawks..." Frenzied Sword scanned across one by one. They were all world-renowned teams. At this moment, he finally felt how real this international festival was. He could not help but tremble slightly from the excitement and anticipation.

Beside him, King Admiral was looking casual and lazy as usual, waving at foreign players from far away. Many of them knew each other.

This scene appeared on the live video in the forums. The boisterous atmosphere was like a festival of millions of people.

The host appeared in the middle of the arena, attracting the eyes of the contestants. He first congratulated the contestants for qualifying for the International League, then started the official opening speech regarding who sponsored the competition and similar formalities. After five minutes, he finally finished the opening speech and started to talk about the competition system.

"There's a total of thirteen divisions. A total of thirty-nine teams and Singles players from all around the world are qualified for the International League. The competition mode is a continuation of the area competition. The team competition includes team battle and Challenge, the Singles include Duel..."

Han Xiao nodded while he listened to the host. The first league season had very few varieties. In his previous life, the later seasons had more types of competitions, such as Dungeon, Survival, Hunt, Race, and all sorts of strange ways to compete. In order to be more entertaining, the competitions became more and more diverse.

The host continued and said, "Thirty-nine teams and players will be divided into three groups—A, B, and C. They will compete within the groups, and the winners will be rewarded with points; the number of points awarded depends on the damage the winning team received in the competition. The top eight teams and sixteen Singles players will enter the finals..."

He looked around. The pro players had various expressions. Some were excited, some were serious, and some were confident.

"Let's begin drawing lots!"

Chapter 424: First Showcase, Overwhelming Opening

While drawing lots, every team sized each other up. The Chinese teams were looked at most frequently.

Most of the people did not want to be in the same group as the Chinese teams—they were the tough bones.

The grouping was completely random, and the results came out very quickly. Dynasty was in group A, Temple of God and Long Sky were in group C, and all the other teams were randomized as well.

Group A was the most normal group—the mix of strong and teams was very balanced. Dynasty and Devil were the two strongest teams and had a good chance of going into the finals. Group B had mostly smaller and weaker teams; it was the safest, but there might be a dark horse in that group as well. Group C, however, was the worst. It was full of strong teams such as Kimchi, Tulips, Rose Knight, Thunder Snakes—often abbreviated to TS—Tomahawk, and so on. Almost seventy percent of all the strong teams were in group C.

Other than the host, there were also commentators who were all professional streamers or retired players. They discussed and analyzed for the audience.

"The eligibility of qualifying depends on the total score. The grouping has a very large impact on the results. If a group is filled with strong teams, it will be very hard to gain points, and even teams who are capable of qualifying might fail to do so. On the other hand, if the group has many weak teams, even if the teams are not as strong, they might be able to qualify! In a situation like this, as teams want to qualify, the battle will be very heated. No one will dare to hold back. Even when facing a battle that they are unable to win, they will try to damage the opponent as much as possible so that they don't score so many points. Hence, the battles in group C will definitely be very exciting!"

"Group C is the group of death! There're so many strong teams that would definitely qualify if placed in the other two groups, but now no one can guess the result. Any team could be eliminated... Competitions like this are very interesting, and I look forward to their exciting performances."

The result was determined. Teams in group C were all very serious and passionate. Li Ge and Hao Tian looked at each other with a hidden meaning in their eyes.

"Looks like you guessed right—we are in the same group," Hao Tian said with a poker face.

Li Ge frowned and did not reply. The grouping was very disadvantageous to him, but it was a reality that could not be changed. With so many strong teams, qualifying would be very difficult.

Today was the opening ceremony. After the draw finished, all the participating teams immediately started to dig into the information of the opponent teams in their group.

Four hours later, the schedule was officially announced on the forums. International competitions had a slower pace; in one in-game day, every group would have two team battles and two Singles battles. This meant that the international group stages would last around thirty-nine days. Every team would battle once with the twelve other teams in their group.

The competition officially started the next day, and it was played live on all channels. Countless people saw the capability of the qualified teams.

Every team had their own special tactics and style, and it was eye-opening. A rough outlook had formed in all the groups. Devil was defeating other teams in a demolishing fashion; their performances were impeccable in all the competitions, but they had yet to face Dynasty, who were in the same group. Although group B only had weak teams that were not as well known, they were still teams that went through the merciless elimination process and had qualified for the International League. The difference in strength between them was comparatively small, so their battles were mostly on par. Kangaroo Boxing team from Australia had the best performance. Group C was the most popular; it was filled with heated battles between strong teams and was the most exciting.

China's first match was on the third day; China's Dynasty VS Poland's Wings. China's players looked forward to their country's first appearance on the international stage.

The other teams watched, too; this was a very good opportunity to observe the strength of the Chinese teams. Although they were in different groups, most of the teams felt like they had a very high chance of meeting the Chinese teams in the finals, so they could not possibly take it lightly.

The third day arrived under the anticipation of countless people. The match between Dynasty and Wings started.

The night was dark, and there was no moon in the sky.

This was a desolate ancient ruin. The collapsed houses and shattered pillars were signs of how boisterous the city that had once existed here had been. Cold, blue spheres of light roamed the place without a destination, bringing light and dispelling the darkness.

This was an actual scene of one of the novice planets, duplicated to become the match map. Team matches were all carried out in duplicated scenes; the terrain was the duplicate of a random area in the various novice planets.

The spectators could see every action of both teams.

Dynasty landed in a corner of the ruins. Everyone was wearing Sunil NCO Class armor, carrying different mechanical weapons, and clad in technologically advanced equipment. They looked around and observed their surroundings.

"Ruin terrain, many obstructions, so ranged attacks are limited. Plus, it's night, so melee and assassination are very suitable. The class combination of team Wings is defensive Esper, range Mage, and combat Mage. Their damage output is plenty, but their backlines are comparatively weak. If we get into combat, we have to quickly deal with the backlines. The opponents should have... no, definitely have mobility abilities. Hence, our dexterous player shall not follow the rest of us and act alone, staying stealthy near the battlefield and striking when there is an opportunity. There are two methods that they might use to do damage—one is to surround the player with damage output in the middle of layers of protection, and the other is to act alone and look for opportunities to deal damage. As they have many damage dealing players, they might use both methods.

"The only source of light here are those light spheres running around. Entering the ring of light would mean exposing ourselves, so the areas with light are dangerous; it's only safe to hide in the dark. Therefore, the battle will only happen in the dark, and it will depend on which of us discover the other first. They have Mages, so they can be enchanted with [Cat Eyes] and [Life Senses]. Our advantage is the night vision, heat vision, and radar function from the mechanical suit. In terms of detection, we are slightly better..."

King Admiral explained the situation calmly. He was very experienced, quickly analyzing the situation and what they should do. Team matches were not just fighting each other head-on—there was also the battle of cooperation, detection, tactics, and so on.

The information of the opponent came from the area competition. Now that a long time had passed, although their class would not change, they definitely made changes to their tactics. The reason that China was feared was that they had left the planet and received too many opportunities in space. There was no way to interpret their tactics and equipment. The unknown was the biggest enemy!

Dynasty's class combination only had Pugilists and Espers, but they were all wearing high-quality mechanical equipment. This meant that their every member had part of the ability of a Mechanic, and it was quite powerful even without the boost from Machinery Affinity. Their strength was absolutely superior. Hence, Dynasty actively searched for the enemies.

In the live feed, team Wings cast all sorts of stealth spells instead, clearly showing that they did not want to fight Dynasty head-on.

In his previous life, the side avoiding the battle had always been the Chinese teams who were steady and cowardly. Now that their positions had switched, the Chinese teams had become the ones to strike actively. In the audiences' perspective, Dynasty was like a hunter that chased after the prey and had the upper hand while the opponent ran around. Such a strong stand made the Chinese viewers feel very proud; they could feel Dynasty's strong confidence even through the feed!

Dynasty's confidence came from Han Xiao. After following Han Xiao through the universe, their equipment and abilities were top among all the teams. Their raw strength was extremely strong, and this was the advantage given by Black Phantom.

It did not matter how much the pro players from other novice planets envied this—there was no one like the Great Mechanic Han on their planet.

Chinese teams were the ones being chased back then; now, it's the other way around. Not bad, they're all youngsters with a lot of potential. Han Xiao smiled, quite content.

Wings was very cautious and cast [Chameleon] and other spells to get rid of their tracks, but the map was only so big, and they would not get far away no matter how much they ran. Sooner or later, they would have to fight. King Admiral commanded his teammates to fire toward the sky to break the stalemate, letting the enemies hear where the sound of gunfire came from. This way, the uncertainties would be eliminated—the enemy would either approach, run the other way, or flank them. With greater strength, Dynasty was completely unafraid of letting the enemies know their location.

The head-on battle broke out from an accident. As King Admiral expected, a combat Mage from the opponent was acting alone near their team and was discovered by Second Prince, who was also acting alone.

Although Second Prince was very cheeky usually, he was very decisive in competitions and struck immediately.

Second Prince was a Pugilist that focused on Dexterity and assassinations. He was using the scouting style NCO Class mechanical suit, which had a streamlined body and a pair of blades extending from the wrist like fangs. He attacked like a cheetah; not only was his assassin combo completely on point, but it was also smooth and quick. There was close to no gap between his abilities and position changes. This was considered to be a great performance even on the professional level.

That combat Mage could not react in time to the attack. He was heavily wounded by Second Prince's storming and thunderous attacks, then ended up turning into a flash of white light and dying before the reinforcement from his teammates arrived.

Solo kill!

Second Prince backed up into the darkness again and disappeared, only leaving blood all over the floor.

The Assassin's way.

Strike once and back off miles.

"Damn, that was beautiful!"

"Although Second Prince's brain has some problems, he is really quite strong."

The audience was excited.

This solo kill opened up the situation suddenly. Wings lost a teammate and were more disadvantaged than they had initially been. They were eventually caught by Dynasty and completely demolished in one team fight.

Dynasty achieved an overwhelming victory with zero losses, shining brightly and making the audience thrilled!

The Challenge after this was an even more steady victory. King Admiral alone ferociously defeated two opponents and handicapped another.

The first match could be considered a perfect opening. Compared to Devil, who were in the same group, this performance was not any worse at all.

The huge victory inspired the audience and also made the other teams fear them even more.

Dynasty's mechanical suit made its first appearance in a competition. Equipment like this gave comprehensive enhancements to the players. No team dared to claim that their chance of winning Dynasty in a head-on battle was more than fifty percent.

"Looks like more targeted methods need to be used against the Chinese teams." The same thought appeared in many captain's minds.

Second Prince made a huge contribution. During the post-match interview, he could not hide the excitement on his face at all, and he did not want to. As usual, he boasted about how important he was, how much of a contribution he made, how key players like him should be the captain instead, how the captain now was too noob, and so on. King Admiral was used to it and ignored it completely.

The competition was going on intensely. The first round ended in four days, meaning all teams had taken part in a battle and made their debut.

Hao Tian's team, Long Sky, was the same as Dynasty. They used a completely different style as compared to Han Xiao's previous life, changed by the man indirectly. They let themselves go and were very tough. Sadly, they met a strong team in group C, and although they won in the end, it was a difficult win and did not score them as many points as Dynasty had scored.

On the contrary, Li Ge's team Temple of God was exactly the same as the previous life. Even when their strength was completely superior, they fought steadily and only hoped to not make a mistake. Their first appearance was very dragged out, making people complain non-stop.

"You're strong yet you are so cowardly—can't you make things more exciting‽"

Anyway, Han Xiao did not have high hopes for Temple of God. That team had always been this way, not hoping for merits and just hoping to not make mistakes. For them to be more diligent? Not unless pigs could fly.

Luckily, there were Dynasty and Long Sky, so Temple of God did not receive too many negative comments. After all, it was very different between one team dragging the match out and all three teams doing the same.

Chapter 425: Black Star's Ability Potion

After the first round, the leaderboard was the focus of much discussion. Devil was first, followed by Dynasty, and third place to sixth place were all teams from group B, and the Group C teams were in the lower positions. The battles between strong teams in group C were very intense—most of them won by a small difference—so they did not score many points. However, there were strong ones even among the weaker teams, which was team Tulips that were placed at seventh place. Although their place seemed a little low, their opponent was Tomahawk. Sweden's Esports had always been strong, and Tomahawk was a very strong team that had the chance to become the champion, yet Tulips could take so many points from them. It was rather terrifying.

Han Xiao recalled the first season league in his previous life, then it occurred to him. Right, the first season champion was French Tulips, these people's strength is overwhelming. Their class combination, equipment selection, and ability collaboration are almost perfect, and their tactics are seamless. For China, only Dynasty was in top eight; the other two teams did not even qualify for the finals.

Looking down, the scores of eighth place to seventeenth place were the same.

This was just the first round so the ranking did not matter too much. Every team still had eleven more matches, so the final result was far from being decided.

The popularity of the Singles was high too, as one versus one has always been. Frenzied Sword barely won the first match, King Admiral won as well, but SnowFlower lost. SnowFlower was a feminine man, and his fans called him 'Sister Snow'. Among all the contestants from China, he was the only one that lost, which was regretful.

After completing the matches, the Chinese players found Han Xiao to repair their mechanical suits. During the competition, these pro players did not hold back in spending all their Enas on enhancing their mechanical equipment. Han Xiao accepted the request with a smile—it was because of the player's continuous hard work that he had accumulated close to 800,000 Enas. It was enough to even buy a spaceship.

Of course, he was definitely not going to buy a spaceship. Why would he buy one when he could take rides on others' spaceships?

The competition carried on. The Chinese teams doing very well. Although they did meet strong teams and faced tough fights, they still won in the end. Han Xiao filtered the equipment that he sold to them. Although NCO Class armor was strong, it was not invincible. Players were all at max level 60 and had gathered the best equipment in their area, so their equipment was not bad either. They might even have something hidden up their sleeves that could turn the tables completely in important times.

Although China's raw strength was at the top, the competitions were very unpredictable, and there were countless examples of the weaker ones winning through tactics.

Han Xiao was definitely not going to sell the core equipment ahead of schedule—he would not destroy his sales plan for the sake of helping China get better results. He had yet to even figure out what was happening to him in this world, so he did not have the time to control the players' competition. Furthermore, the league was a business opportunity in his eyes. His main goal was to let the players showcase how good the equipment that he sold was so that he could expand his potential market. As long as the result was not too bad, it was enough for him.

After several battles, all the teams had a clearer understanding of the other teams and had designed specific tactics; China was no exception.

The strongest point of the Chinese teams came from those mechanical suits and weapons from Black Star. As long as they could deal with that, their threat would decrease tremendously!

Therefore, the next few opponents that China met with all changed their class combination, adding a Psychic.

In the earlier stages, the Psychic class was not one of but the biggest nemesis of the Mechanic class. Not only could they control objects, but their psychic attacks completely ignored physical armor. For the Mage class, their Psychological Resistance was high, so they could at least block it to a certain extent, the Pugilist class could reduce the duration of negative effects, and the Esper class was made up of extremely lucky people, so it could not be considered as an example. Hence, the Mechanic class was the only one left that was targeted by it.

Mechanics depended on machinery to battle, so they were usually weak. Psychics just happened to be able to deal direct damage to the user through physical armor. Plus, there were many methods of mind-controlling, such as illusion, confusion, fear, and many other debuffs. Furthermore, their attack range was very long, and the attacks ignored terrain. The minimal level of skills needed to play this class was just a little bit more than Pugilists.

When faced with such specific tactics, the specialness of the Chinese teams was shown. Although they were wearing armor, they were Pugilists and Espers. Despite the Psychics reducing the effects of the armor and dragging them down from the top place, the strength of the Chinese teams was still top tier. The opponent still had to face a group of top tier pro players.

Other than the Psychic class, the Mage class' elemental, corrosive, and curse spells also reduced the effects of mechanical suits. Of course, while they could reduce the effects of mechanical suits, they were paper-like themselves.

The very existence of the armor forced these teams to spend more effort to deal with it; its strength was clearly shown. This thing could be used by all classes and provided comprehensive enhancements. It was like they wore a turtle shell with spikes that had an extra bar of health and were given the ability of ranged damage output. If the margin for error for normal teams was three, China's was ten!

The enhancement was too tremendous!

Even with a certain level of damage adjustments and balancing, it was impossible to cancel out China's equipment advantage.

Actually, in Version 2.0 or 3.0, basically, everyone had a mechanical suit. Since everyone had one, the difference was in the performance of the mechanical suits, and that difference would not be as huge as it was now. Sadly, characters that sold armor in the first version were extremely rare, and even if they did, they were selling rough, semi-finished ones. Han Xiao was the one and only place that provided high-quality armor and related services.

However, these specific tactics did have an effect. The Chinese teams' damage taken increased clearly. Everyone was a strong team from their area, so they could not defeat all of them in an overwhelming fashion. The matches after were all back and forth; it was exciting and intense.

The rankings on the leaderboard fluctuated every day. Dynasty and Devil faced each other once, and Dynasty won with a slight advantage, placing them at the top of the leaderboard and attracting a lot of attention.

Such results made Chinese spectators feel very proud. Every time a Chinese team or player was having a match, they would definitely be waiting on the forums for it to start. Not only the Chinese fans, but quite a number of foreign viewers became fans of Dynasty because of their performance. The popularity of the matches involving China was at the top three.

Comparing to the tragedy in the previous life, this was a complete change.

On the other hand, Long Sky and Temple of God, who were in group C, were not doing very well. They were drifting between the eighth and twelfth place, at the edge of being unable to qualify. The competition was very intense.

...

In an unused alloy room in Black Star's stronghold that was modified into a prison cell, Rezar was still imprisoned. His hands were fixed tightly on the metal bed, and a few needles were inserted into his body and kept that way, injecting nutrients and sedatives. His eyes were filled with emptiness, and his face was completely stiff.

He was being used as material for the extractor. He had no freedom and was tortured till he was nearly not a person anymore. His magic would be extracted as soon as he recovered any, not giving him even the slightest hope.

The door opened. Han Xiao walked in, glanced and him, and refilled the nutrients without stopping, even humming while he worked. He completely ignored Rezar's tragic state, like a doctor that was used to life and death. He then took out the extractor and extracted Rezar's blood as usual.

Red and slightly illuminated blood flew through the pipe and into the tube, turning into a new Ability Potion. Han Xiao had already made eight potions.

Rezar turned his head, looked at Han Xiao, and opened his mouth to speak. His voice was so hoarse that it was almost silent. "Are you planning to imprison me forever?"

"Of course, not forever." Han Xiao raised his eyebrows and said, "Do you think you can live that long?"

"Can we make a deal? You let me free, and I can give you everything that I have and work for you. I just wanted to come to the higher world and satisfy my desire for knowledge. I don't oppose working for anyone," Rezar said in a pleading tone.

Han Xiao picked up the new Ability Potion and shook it. He turned around to look at Rezar, smiled, and said, "I already have your everything."

"You! Are! So! Evil!" Rezar clenched his teeth tightly, his eyes filled with bottomless hatred and despair.

"I won't do this to the innocent. If you were a normal person, maybe I would pity you, but you're an evil person that almost killed millions of lives. Hehe, do you think I should pity you? That would be an insult to the millions of lives you almost took.

Han Xiao's heart was never shaken. He had been through the dark times of being imprisoned by the Germinal Organization and being a test subject, so he knew very well how it felt. He was very happy to let people like Rezar experience it too.

He knew that he was not a forgiving and kind person.

"Look forward to the day of you dying. That is your last hope of feeling relieved," Han Xiao said coldly and closed the door, leaving Rezar screaming in agony and despair.

After returning to his room, Han Xiao sterilized the extractor and laid out all the Ability Potions. They all had tags on them. With the popularity of the league, he was planning to sell these potions to the players.

Looking at these potions, the Great Mechanic Han suddenly had an idea.

The extractor can only generate potions when used on an NPC. If I extract my own genes... will it work?

Han Xiao was interested. He washed the extractor again and pressed it down on his arm. He changed the output of it to the lowest level.

You are using [Super-Gene Extractor - Test Version] on yourself.

A sense of weakness appeared and penetrated his body instantly. Han Xiao raised his eyebrow and did not stop until the entire tube was filled.

You have received [Ability Potion] x 1.

It worked! Han Xiao's eyes sparkled. He then looked at his character interface. He had received a [Weakened] debuff for twelve hours, reducing all his attributes by thirty percent. He was feeling a little bit powerless and sluggish.

He did not mind it. He was resting in Juberly Hub, so there would not be any fighting for this period. Thus, being weak for a short period was not a problem.

What effect will my Ability Potion have?

Han Xiao was extremely curious.

It's too much of a waste if I drink it myself. I have ready-made customers.

Chapter 426: BOSS Type Player! (1)

A faint light flashed past. Frenzied Sword, who had just finished his match for the day, appeared in the stronghold hall. He was quite upset.

"Sigh, another loss. Lost Angel is too steady—I really can't beat him. My ranking dropped by one again. The next opponent is Club Key's Key of Solomon, a very strong guy. If I lose again, it will be completely impossible for me to qualify."

Frenzied Sword shook his head worriedly.

More than half of the matches were finished, and the situation started to get clearer. In the team matches, Dynasty had secured one qualifying position; Long Sky and Temple of God were both still moving around the edge of eighth place. If they lost a certain match or did not score enough points, they would be left behind instantly. With the harsh environment in group C, catching up afterward was extremely difficult.

However, the team matches had nothing to do with Frenzied Sword. His performance in the Singles was not too great but not too bad. He was ranked in the middle around 17th to 18th place. His win percentage was about fifty percent, but every victory was a tough one. He started to feel what a Mechanical Pugilist lacked.

Although the Mechanical Pugilist class could both fight and take hits, was capable of both melee and ranged attacks, and was quite well rounded, it did not have a unique strength. Despite his skills being very high, there was still quite a distance between his skill level and the top tier skill level. These maniacs in the Singles all had their own special tactic or even tactics. They were good at dragging their opponents into their own tempo. Frenzied Sword realized that if a Mechanical Pugilist like him wanted to chase up, the only method was to depend on stronger or more unique mechanical weapons.

However, the flaws of the Mechanical Pugilist class were not because of personal skill level. The Mechanic class did not suit the first version very well. After all, every version had its own legends. In order to make up for the shortcomings of a Mechanical Pugilist, one had to depend on stronger machinery and higher-level enhancements in the later versions. In all versions, the Mechanical Pugilist class was considered a class that was fun, well-rounded, and not a bad class. It could be played as the main tank or the damage source, and its development curve was smooth, unlike the Mechanic class.

It was already very rare for Frenzied Sword to have achieved so much. Other than his skills, the main reason was his high-quality mechanical equipment from Han Xiao. If he had not met Black Phantom back then, he probably would have been in the area competition and never would have made it to the international stage.

Of all the players that followed Han Xiao, Frenzied Sword was the firmest supporter. Not only because he had received the most help but also because he really liked the character of Han Xiao after spending so much time together. Sometimes, he even felt as if Han Xiao was a real person.

Although all the NPCs in Galaxy felt like real people, Han Xiao gave him a unique feeling. Maybe it was because Han Xiao was the first important character that he had met.

After regaining his focus, Frenzied Sword decided to find Han Xiao to repair his equipment and add some new weapons for the next match, hoping to increase his chance of winning.

Just as he was about to head toward Han Xiao, Han Xiao came to the hall. Frenzied Sword approached immediately and expressed his wish of repairing. The store interface appeared before his eyes.

He quickly browsed through it. Suddenly, he noticed a few new items at the bottom.

"Hmm? Ability Potion? Never seen this before. Is this new?" Frenzied Sword was surprised.

Han Xiao placed the Ability Potions into the store. There was a limited quantity, so he made their price very high. The effect introduction was that they granted one ability of another character for a short period. The source of the Ability Potion was written, and the potion that Han Xiao made from his own genes was in it as well, which was discovered very quickly by Frenzied Sword.

"Only one Ability Potion from Black Star. What's its effect?"

The potion prices were all 2,000 Enas, not cheap at all, or it was quite expensive. One would only know its effects after using it. The effect of the temporary Character Summoning Card would definitely be one ability of the person that it came from. The ability given was random.

Frenzied Sword had yet to make a purchase decision. At this time, Dynasty, Temple of God, and other contesting teams approached as well. They noticed the new product, Ability Potion, as well.

"Temporarily grants an ability of someone else. This looks like a buff potion. Why is it so expensive? Are the effects very strong?"

In order to increase their strength, these teams did not hold back on spending. Hao Tian immediately bought an Ability Potion from Rezar. After drinking it, a notification of temporary Character Summoning Card popped up. Its effect was increasing the damage of magic attacks by seventy-seven percent; he was quite shocked by it.

"Sadly, I'm not a Mage, or this enhancement would be quite strong. It can be used in key moments in the team fight or to kill the weaker opponents in a short time. It can turn the tables if used properly!"

This was not the first time that the players had come into contact with Character Summon Cards. The Character Summon Cards could enhance one's strength and were very practical. Usually, only special missions awarded such things, so they did not appear often. They did not expect Han Xiao to sell Character Summon Cards. Despite these being temporary ones, this was the first time that they had seen them. They were shocked and joyed.

Frenzied Sword's eyes sparkled, and he hastily bought the only Black Star Ability Potion. He was a Mechanic, and so was Black Star. Thus, the ability was definitely going to be suitable for him.

Not bothering about the other teams snatching the rest of the Ability Potions, Frenzied Sword walked to the side and drank Han Xiao's potion carefully.

A notification appeared on the interface.

You have received [Character Summon Card - Han Xiao (Temporary)]

[Character Summon Card - Han Xiao (Temporary)]: Black Star's Advent

Increase your Machinery Affinity by 247%.

Duration: 3 mins

Usages: 0/1

Frenzied Sword instantly opened his eyes widely. The shock was stuck on his face. He could not help but to rub his eyes, afraid that he had read the wrong numbers.

"Tw—two point five times enhancement!!"

Frenzied Sword could hardly believe it.

"My Machinery Affinity is barely half of this number even after using all my enhancing abilities. Black Star's attributes are way too strong. How strong is he?"

'Overpowered' was not even enough to describe this!

The enhancement was almost like a bug!

Using this Character Summon Card at this level, even a pig could defeat the opponent!

Han Xiao had many abilities, and this Character Summon Card granted the user his Machinery Affinity. This was not considered an ability but Han Xiao's basic attributes, so its effect became a buff.

Without using any abilities, Han Xiao had 247% Machinery Affinity from his talents and passive abilities. When abilities were used, this number would be increased by another 100% to 200%. This was the simplest effect but also the strongest one.

That was because Machinery Affinity was the core attribute of the Mechanic class—it directly influenced one's strength!

As the level of the Mechanic class continued to increase, the Machinery Affinity would continuously increase as well. However, the effect of the temporary Character Summon Card was an extra enhancement. Hence, this was like giving the user the attributes that he would have dozens of levels later!

And dozens of levels higher... happened to be the level that the Mechanic class started to be strong!

Luckily, the temporary Character Summon Card could only be used once and was very rare. If it was a fixed ability, it would make the player invincible!

Seeing that Frenzied Sword was breathing heavily in excitement, Han Xiao touched his chin, very curious.

Which of my abilities did this kid get for him to be this excited?

"Frenzied Sword, third place in Planet Aquamarine Singles, Mechanical Pugilist class, known as the strongest Mechanical Pugilist in China..."

In the Club Key stronghold in Planet Winterfrost, Key of Solomon casually browsed the information of his next opponent in Singles. He sneered and said with pride and confidence, "Looks like there's nothing to worry about."

"Are you planning to use Howling Gate?" an old member, Cursed Staff, asked.

"You're overthinking, there's no need to use my trump card to beat the next opponent. I bet that people like Lost Angel, Golden Champagne from Rose Knight, and Scarlet Marshall from Devil definitely have trump cards up their sleeves. Although I'm ranked seventh now, I can definitely reach the top if I used my trump card. However, just qualifying is enough for now; it's best to leave the trump card to use in the finals."

Key of Solomon was very confident in his trump card. [Howling Gate] was a special spell item that he had gotten from an extremely difficult hidden mission. Although he did not know what the trump cards of the others were, he was confident that he was close to invincible in this level in a one on one. Even if he did not use his trump card, his skills were among the highest. Being able to reach seventh place had already proved that.

"After winning this, my ranking will go up another place. The opponents in the last few matches are all quite difficult to deal with. I can deliberately lose these matches to hide my real strength. This way, my ranking should drop to about fifteenth place, just enough to qualify. And that's enough..."

Based on the assumption that he would win the next match, Key of Solomon started planning for the rest of the matches. In his eyes, the next match was free points before facing strong opponents. He was certain of his victory and did not even consider his chances of losing.

Frenzied Sword was one of the few Mechanic class players in the international Singles and the only Mechanic class from China. With the title of 'Strongest Mechanical Pugilist in China', he received a lot of attention from many fans and viewers.

From the start of the competition, Frenzied Sword's performance had been nothing extraordinary, and his ranking was only average. Even for the matches that he did win, the viewers could see that he had a hard time winning. His ranking could not go up; it seemed like he had reached his limit.

Between the three Singles contestants from China, King Admiral had a very high ranking and did not have to worry about qualifying; SnowFlower was at the bottom, and due to the fact that more than half of the matches had been completed, unless he won every match from now on, there was no chance for him to qualify; Frenzied Sword's ranking was fluctuating around sixteenth place, which meant that he had a chance of being the second contestant from China to qualify. He had the hopes of many fans on his shoulders.

The rest of Frenzied Sword's journey in the competition was rather extreme. His opponents were either very strong in the top ten or very weak at the bottom. The fans analyzed according to his performance and realized that even if he could beat all the weaker players, he would still need a few more points to qualify. He had to beat at least one strong player in order to qualify. However, Frenzied Sword had a very low win rate against strong players at this time.

The situation did not look good.

And the opponent of this match was ranked seventh, [Key of Solomon].

Many fans were secretly anxious and encouraged him. There were also people who were bitter and complained, saying that Frenzied Sword was falsely given the title of the strongest Mechanical Pugilist in China and embarrassed himself in front of the entire world. As always, the forums were filled with all kinds of comments.

No matter how they looked at it, time would not slow down even the slightest. The day of the match arrived as usual.

Frenzied Sword and Key of Solomon entered the match venue. The image that the viewers saw included the health, stamina, status bar, and all their attributes. The situation was clearly laid out for the audience to make watching the match simpler.

The venue was a huge city. Tall, thick walls made of concrete and steel surrounded the city. The two of them landed on the two sides beside this dozens of meters tall, four to five meters thick wall. They could see each other's tiny outline from far away.

Storm clouds flew above the sky of the desolate city.

The audience pulled the bird-eye view higher and realized that on the outside of the wall, there was a huge oil painting of a few words.

Black Phantom Sanctuary Three.

"Haha, this is the random venue."

"I know this place. Isn't this Sanctuary Three from our planet?"

The Chinese fans were pleasantly surprised.

Chapter 427: BOSS Type Player! (2)

The commentary from the two commentators appeared timely to introduce the battle.

"The two contestants in this match are Key of Solomon and Frenzied Sword. Demon Mage against Human Mechanical Pugilist. Key of Solomon's ranking at the moment is seventh place, and Frenzied Sword is at eighteenth place. The win rate estimation is 57% to 43% in favor of Key of Solomon. From their performance in the previous matches, Key of Solomon is slightly advantageous."

"As you might have noticed, the venue is Planet Aquamarine's Black Phantom Sanctuary Three. The Chinese contestants come from Planet Aquamarine, so Frenzied Sword should have the advantage of knowing the terrain well. One thing that I would like to mention is that Black Phantom is Black Star, the first NPC to lead the Chinese contestants into space. Since the Chinese players are following Black Star, I have to say it's quite fated."

"They have started moving. Okay, let's look forward to an exciting battle..."

As soon as the battle started, Frenzied Sword avoided fighting head-on. A steel cable shot out from his waist armor and hooked onto a house under the wall. With the sound of the steel cable retracting, he was pulled down and moved away from the wall. He took out a high caliber machine cannon and fired. A string of orange bullets flew toward Key of Solomon.

Hum!

Key of Solomon held a bone staff and activated the standby rune. A translucent blue and green magic sphere surrounded him and protected him; the bullets created a dense scattering of sparks on the shield. The audiences could see that Key of Solomon's status bar had a shield durability bar, which was decreasing slowly.

At this time, Frenzied Sword had already disappeared between the houses. Bullets were fired at him from time to time, small grenades too, blasting clouds of black and thick smoke on the wall. Key of Solomon squinted and said, "Because of his familiarity with the terrain, he plans to first deal some damage to me through ranged attacks. Hmm..."

As he was speaking, jumped down from the wall as well. He took out a few magic scrolls and tore them. Various colors of magic light then appeared. Many buffs appeared instantly on his status bar.

"Tracking, Stealth, Misdirection, Shadow Demon Cloak, Fake Death..."

"Damn, that is so costly. Magic scrolls are very expensive."

The Chinese spectators felt nervous for Frenzied Sword. Although they had not come into contact with magic much, they had learned about many magic effects through the forums.

The enemy's location suddenly disappeared from the radar of Frenzied Sword's armor. He frowned and thought, Magical stealth, a troublesome ability. I'm at a disadvantage in terms of detection, so I can't kite him easily...

As he was thinking, he changed the detection method of the radar into detecting air movements in order to relocate the opponent's location. The detection range was smaller than before.

The two of them moved stealthily and tracked each other, both attacking and receiving attacks. They were mainly testing each other, and as soon as they noticed the opponent's weakness or mistake, they would immediately launch a thunderous strike on the opponent. The audience could not move their eyes away from the match, and the tension grew as the distance between them became shorter. They were both making micro-movements on each other.

"Huu, huu..."

The sound of breathing echoed in the armor helmet. Frenzied Sword hid behind a house and looked at the tactic screen. The trace of the air movement appeared in his vision, showing a blue snake-like line. The end of the line was the opponent's position. Frenzied Sword was good at melee battles, but he decided to distance himself. This was because the information on Key of Solomon showed that he was not as paper-like as other Mages; many melee Pugilists had lost tragically because they got too close. Frenzied Sword's plan was to find an opportunity to land a stealth attack followed by a combo, controlling the opponent and maximizing the damage output.

Although he had an invincible trump card, he was not going to use it easily. If he could win by himself, the Character Summon Card could be saved to use the next time that he faced a strong opponent.

There is a time limit to his magic shield, and it costs him mana. I have quite a lot of ammo left, so I should be able to deplete around twenty-eight percent of his mana and fifteen percent of his health...

As he was thinking, he fired at the enemy's location, hitting on the magic shield. However, at this time, a new buff appeared on his status bar—[Marked].

Reverse Revenge Mark! Frenzied Sword knew that this was bad. This ability was very rare, and it was the first time that the opponent had used it. There was no information about it in the data that he had received. Its effect was very simple, locating and tracing the attacker if the user was attacked in a certain duration. This was a spell used to deal with stealth attacks.

The next moment, a blaze quickly approached.

Boom!

A Frostfire Ball blasted through the house that Frenzied Sword was hiding behind, turning the environment into a sea of blue flames. Key of Solomon slowly walked over from afar, his face expressionless. He was a Demon Mage trained in both ice and fire. He combined the two of them and formed the Frostfire style.

The spell combining function was similar to the blueprint invention function of the Mechanic class. The difference was that the chance of it succeeding was quite high, but at the same time, its experience cost was much higher as well. The combining method was to put two or more spells together and form a new effect. It also cost a certain material to do so. The Frostfire Ball spell, for example, required the spell [Frost] and [Huge Fireball] as well as the material [Fire Trapping Ice Crystal]. The spells used for the combination would be forgotten. There were two ways of relearning these forgotten spells—one was to separate the new spells that were formed through combining these spells, and the other was to learn it again by spending experience. It cost a lot of experience as well.

The specialty of Frostfire was the ability to quickly reduce the durability of metals, it was an extremely effective way of dealing with the Mechanic class.

At this time, a layer of magic light appeared on the surface of Frenzied Sword's NCO Class armor. The Frostfire was repelled, and the speed of the armor's durability reducing slowed down. The enchantment from the Volga brothers gave his armor a certain level of magic resistance.

Frenzied Sword's armored legs stomped heavily on the ground, and blue fire shot out from the thrusting device on his back. He charged forward like a rhinoceros. A huge foldable alloy shield ejected from his left arm's armor, big enough to block his entire body. His right hand pulled out a short metal rod from his waist. The metal rod automatically extended and turned into a long, thin gunlance spear.

He entered melee mode instantly!

The alloy shield smashed on the magic shield with a force so huge that it made Key of Solomon take two steps back. This time, Frenzied Sword saw an opening and jabbed with his spear, penetrating into the magic shield. A Concentrated Explosive Bullet slid into the chamber of the gunlance. The next instant, a violent explosion was released from the tip of the spear, exploding from within the magic shield!

Boom!

Black smoke spread out.

"A beautiful attack!" a commentator complimented. "Mechanical Pugilist's tactics are very flexible; Frenzied Sword changed his weapons again. Speaking of which, he has yet to use the same weapon in all the matches of the Singles..."

"Wait, the health loss is very little. It did not seem to hit completely!"

In the black smoke, Key of Solomon had disappeared, replaced by a stone that had already turned into ashes, while he appeared more than fifteen meters behind Frenzied Sword, not taking much damage.

"He used the Object Swap Spell on himself in an emergency. The cooldown of this ability is very long, five minutes. Apparently, Key of Solomon is very cautious about keeping his health up. That's right, after all, Frenzied Sword is wearing a mechanical suit, so his health is almost 1.7 times Key of Solomon's."

After the stealth phase of the match ended, the two of them entered a tug of war. Frenzied Sword continuously poked Key of Solomon in close range, and Key of Solomon cast Frostfire from far away. It was a back and forth and exciting battle. They looked to be on par, but the status bar showed that Frenzied Sword was at a disadvantage and was losing health faster than Key of Solomon. The battle between two pro players was definitely not just standing still and attacking each other; they were both using very delicate dodging abilities. Obviously, Key of Solomon's skill was higher.

However, it looked like Frenzied Sword had the upper hand. With his armor, his health was way too high, and he would be able to win even by exchanging hits.

But the commentator was not optimistic.

"Frenzied Sword has eighty percent health and sixty-six percent armor durability left; Key of Solomon has seventy-three percent health, thirty-one percent magic shield, and sixty-eight percent mana left. The situation is actually very disadvantageous to Frenzied Sword. Although he has a lot of health, if the durability of his armor is depleted, he will lose at least half of his strength! He only has one set of armor, but the opponent can create a new magic shield as long as he has mana."

Boom!

The Frostfire exploded, this time with a repelling effect. Frenzied Sword was forced to back off a few steps. Key of Solomon backed off as well, his eyes sparkling as he thought, Not a bad fight. I underestimated him a little, but that won't affect the result.

Key of Solomon took the opportunity and started to murmur in the strange Demon language, like a deep whisper. His eyes started burning like flames, countless blue flames gushed out between his scales, and his body suddenly became taller and bigger. He turned into a demon covered in blue flames, and a new buff appeared on his status bar.

Demon Talent—True Name Release Basic Stage!

All attributes increased by thirteen percent! Ten-minute duration! Health and mana recovered by thirty percent! All buffs removed, including positive buffs!

He took a deep breath. The flames around him turned into a blazing current and were swallowed by him. He received an extra twenty percent health, and his health was now at one hundred and twenty percent. This was the [Flame Excitement].

"It appeared," the commentator said with exhilaration, "Demon Race's talent ability with a three-day cooldown! In all the regular races on the novice planets, the talent of the Demon Race is the most suitable for real battles. They are born with a self-enhancing ability that's very powerful!"

Boom!

The situation turned one-sided instantly. Frostfire exploded violently, and Frenzied Sword was being overpowered by the storm of attacks. The power of the opponent's spells was hugely enhanced, and his health recovered above the maximum, which meant that the health and durability that he lost went to waste. Key of Solomon continued his spell combo calmly, not giving any chances.

As he had predicted before the match, this was a match that had no threat; there was absolutely no need to use his trump card.

The Chinese spectators were shocked. They became upset as they saw how beaten Frenzied Sword was in the live feed.

"How is this even winnable!"

"That's the end."

"The Americans really got lucky. They chose Planet Winterfrost as their base. All of the Demon Race have this overpowered ability. They're like bosses."

The heat penetrated through the armor. Inside the helmet, a bitter expression appeared on Frenzied Sword's face.

Damn it, I really can't beat him. No wonder he's the captain of such a big club...

With his own skill and combat power, the chance of him beating Key of Solomon was close to zero.

However... he was not alone.

I can't beat you, but if we're comparing whose more overpowered, who the hell are you?

Frenzied Sword clenched his teeth and used his trump card.

Character Summon Card — Black Star's Advent!

Hum!

A four-meter high translucent hologram appeared behind Frenzied Sword wearing black clothes. His looks were very familiar to the audience; it was none other than Han Xiao.

"Isn't that Black Phantom?" The audience was surprised.

The tall hologram slowly pressed his hand on Frenzied Sword's head with an expressionless face.

Buzz!

A blinding electrical light suddenly appeared, and rampaging Mechanical Force flowed into Frenzied Sword's body through the hand of the hologram. The next moment, Frenzied Sword was completely surrounded by violent bolts of lightning.

"What ability is th... What‽" Before the commentator could react, the next scene made his jaw drop.

Frenzied Sword lunged forward, and Key of Solomon's new magic shield was broken in just one hit!

It was as weak as a bubble.

Then, Frenzied Sword closed the distance and smashed down his shield on Key of Solomon's still confused face.

Bang!

The demon flew out spinning like a cannon, shattering a house. Key of Solomon's health decreased by twenty-one percent instantly!

Just a shield slap took more than one-sixth of his health! The overwhelming enhancement dealt tremendous damage!

The tables turned in an instant!

The image quieted down, and only the sound of flames and electric currents could be heard.

The audiences hastily looked at the status bar and were dumbfounded.

[Black Star's Advent]: +247% Machinery Affinity

Duration: 3 mins

Source: Character Summon Card—Han Xiao

"Th—This..."

The commentator opened his mouth but could not give a proper description of what had just happened. In the end, he could only say one word.

"Overpowered!"

What he had forgotten was that the compliment 'overpowered' had belonged to Key of Solomon not long ago.

Chapter 428: Trump Cards Out

Frenzied Sword was covered in lightning snakes, and the lighting effect was gorgeous.

"So, he got my Machinery Affinity." Han Xiao was watching Frenzied Sword's match. He smiled and said, "This kid really is lucky."

Through the status bar, the audience was surprised to see that the buff had Han Xiao's name on it.

To appear in the league in such a manner, Han Xiao found it quite interesting. He had only had a flash of inspiration when making the Ability Potion, and now it seemed to not only have brought him a profit but also fame.

The players were very familiar with the name Black Star, but they did not expect to see Han Xiao's Character Summon Card in a competition. When they thought about it, Frenzied Sword... no, all the Chinese players were following Han Xiao through space, so it was quite normal for him to have Han Xiao's Character Summon Card.

The problem was, this Character Summon Card's effect was way too strong. Who could face the close to 250% Machinery Affinity boost at this stage‽

Han Xiao's personal attributes were shown as all question marks when detected by the players, so they never knew his real level. Now there was finally a lead. With close to 2.5 times affinity, no wonder he was so strong. He was probably above level 100!

Han Xiao had always been a blessing in the eyes of the Mechanic class players. Now, he had showcased the tip of the iceberg of how strong he was, making the spectating Mechanic players extremely excited. They felt like they saw the bright future of their class.

Boom boom boom!

Frenzied Sword did not dare waste time. He charged forward with large strides, jabbing his spear again and again, causing chain explosions. Even though Key of Solomon tried his best to dodge the attacks, the impact of these attacks still caused his health to go down to around forty percent very quickly. The magic shield that he summoned could not even block even one hit.

Just more than ten seconds ago, Frenzied Sword had been the one being overwhelmed. Now, the situation had completely reversed, and Key of Solomon had become the one that could not fight back at all. He did not dare to divert his attention onto fighting back; he would die if he failed to dodge just one attack.

This buff has a stupidly strong enhancement to the Mechanic class. If this goes on, I won't have a chance of winning at all.

After calming himself from the shock, Key of Solomon quickly adjusted his mindset. He had thought that this was a definite victory, but he had never expected his opponent to have hidden such a strong trump card.

Key of Solomon had his trump card, too. He had originally planned to win this match, deliberately lose the matches afterward, and barely qualify, saving his trump card for the finals. However, he was forced by Frenzied Sword to change his plan. If he still did not use his trump card, he would definitely lose. If he lost this match, he would not be able to hold back in the later matches, and those opponents were all very strong. He would surely end up using his trump card to secure the victory. Since that was the case, he might as well use it now. As long as he could win this one, he would not have to worry about the matches afterward.

Frenzied Sword's sudden explosiveness did indeed shock him, but he found a way to deal with it very quickly. He admitted that Frenzied Sword was near-invincible in the duration of [Black Star's Advent], but the buff would only last for three minutes. As long as he survived past that, he would still stand a chance!

It just so happened that his trump card [Howling Gate] was able to do that!

Whoosh!

Key of Solomon used his last mobility ability [Flame Jump] and disappeared, then reappearing in a sea of fire more than twenty meters away. He quickly pulled down his necklace and pressed it on the floor. His mana decreased by forty percent instantly, and blue magic flowed into the necklace, releasing a blinding light. At the same time, Key of Solomon started to chant.

"Frost that spreads death, fire that extinguishes life. With the blood of the Demon Race, I build a bridge. Please answer my call, the most elite invaders. Let our enemies witness the winter that froze the world..."

Hum!

A divine sound appeared like it came from the void. An ice blue gate of light rose from the ground before Key of Solomon, covered in dancing blue flames. It was four meters tall, and inside it was a vortex of magic. Demon warriors that were three meters tall walked out from the light gate one after another. They wore black metal armor covered in spikes. Two of them held a two-handed axe, another two had a magic crossbow flickering with blue light, and at the front was a ranger who had a chain hammer and rode on a demon wolf. There was a total of five demons.

This was the phantom of an Extinguish Army scouting team.

"He's... a Summoner!" The commentator yelled so loudly he almost broke his voice.

The spectators' expressions shifted.

One word could conclude the image of Summoners in the hearts of the players—b*stard!

In Han Xiao's previous life, the Mage Summoning Style and Mechanic Army Style were known to be the two most disgusting styles.

Balance? Technicality? Sorry, never heard of that. I am just strong!

The Human Wave Tactic could drown enemies. If there were enough summoned creatures, even a player could fight many others at once. In the current stage, the Army Style had yet to appear, but the Summoning Style was already beginning.

Of course, strong styles had their limitations. There was a chance to fail summoning spells, and a spell medium was needed, some of which were specific summoning items. Some required the user to have certain abilities, and some required the user to make contracts with the summoned creatures. There were many ways the summoned creatures could exist, such as in its real and physical form, which would be gone once it died. Key of Solomon, however, summoned phantoms, similar to the duplicate monsters in dungeons, which meant that he could summon them again after they died as much as he wanted. His [Howling Gate] was a pink quality rare level 60 summoning item that could summon the phantom of a demon scout team.

Demon scouts were the specialty of the Extinguish Army. [Howling Gate] was a solo challenge mission. It was very difficult and meant to be completed by players above level 60, but Club Key had used their team's power to help Key of Solomon get this pink item!

The attributes of these five demon scouts appeared on the status bar—2,500 health, 134 – 197 attack, 40 defense. In this stage, the Summoning Style was far from being complete. Usual Summoners could only summon Forest Wolves, Venomous Snakes, and other small creatures, which did not even possess one-third of the attributes of the demon scouts. Yet, he could summon five demon scouts together!

What did that mean? A level 60 Pugilist player had about 3,000 to 4,000 health. These five demon scouts had the total health of about three Pugilists, and their damage was high as well. The theoretical damage that they could deal at most in one round of focus fire was close to 1,000!

This was Key of Solomon's confidence of being close to invincible in duels. Not only because he was a Frostfire Style Demon Mage, but also because he could change to Summoning Style any time.

The audience was still in awe of how strong [Black Star's Advent] was, and the situation had already made another turn, astonishing everyone.

"Holy, he summoned a group of elite monsters. That's almost the same as a boss!"

"Really‽"

Key of Solomon made the ranger and two axe demons surround Frenzied Sword, while the two archers stood beside him and attacked from range.

He did not have much health left, and he feared Frenzied Sword's damage, so he hid behind the archers.

Frenzied Sword's face turned grim. He raised his shield and held his sword, charging forward in large steps. The metal armor strongly clashed into the three demons, making a loud clank. The impact created a shockwave in the air, and the players could feel the image shaking.

Boom! Pa!

Then, the thick smoke and electrical sparks of the explosion were released from the tip of the spear. Frenzied Sword slashed horizontally, hitting those three demons at the same time. The audience could see that the health of the three demon scouts decreased by a quarter instantly.

With the enhancement from [Black Star's Advent], Frenzied Sword's damage was extremely terrifying. Not only that, the defense power of his armor enhanced too, so he was not afraid of being surrounded.

Just three minutes... Key of Solomon was frustrated. In his eyes, the first appearance of the [Howling Gate] had to result in an overwhelming victory. Yet, his first use of it was to stall the enemy and cover his retreat.

Shameful!

As they fought, the number of people watching increased continuously. This match was filled with many twists and turns and had many exciting parts, so it attracted more and more viewers.

The appearance of the summoning spell made the audience think that the situation would turn around once again, or at least they would be on par. However, the following scene was still Frenzied Sword's solo performance. He destroyed a group of demon scouts alone, and the Summoner who was supposed to demolish the opponent was still being beaten by Frenzied Sword.

"The Summoner class is a very strong class. Although Key of Solomon is currently at a complete disadvantage, it does not affect how strong Summoners are..." The caster was analyzing the reason for Summoners being so strong, but when he saw what was happening, he felt that he did not sound convincing at all. However, he could only continue speaking.

You're not making sense!

Many contestants were watching this game with a grave attitude. "Key of Solomon has very strong summoning items. Unlike Frenzied Sword's one-use Character Summon Card, his summoning spells can be used continuously. This guy is a very strong opponent, so specific plans have to be designed in advance."

Although contestant from the various countries feared Key of Solomon, they could not help but feel lucky. "Luckily, the [Black Star's Advent] buff is a one-time card, or there would be no point in taking part in the competition."

Key of Solomon felt like that was the longest three minutes that he had experienced. The demon scouts that he had high hopes on were all slashed into pieces by Frenzied Sword. He looked at the time. Less than two minutes had passed, and Frenzied Sword's status could last for at least thirty more seconds. Key of Solomon, on the other hand, had nothing up his sleeve.

The audiences were happy to see this.

"Three-minute real man, damn!"

"What Black Star's Advent? This is called Demons Demolishing Spell!"

"Summoners can be beaten? You should be ashamed!"

"Key of Solomon: What Can I do? I'm desperate too!"

"This is like a high-level account crushing a low-level one. Speaking of which, Frenzied Sword can indeed be considered a high-level account after gaining so much extra Machinery Affinity."

"Hahahaha, this is so funny. This Summoner looks like he was team wiped while fighting the dungeon boss. Just look at his confused eyes."

"Plop..."

The gunlance stabbed into Key of Solomon's chest without any obstruction. Key of Solomon held onto the spear with rage and regret on his face. He still lost even after he used his trump card. Now, others would be cautious of his trump card, but he did not get anything from it. This battle was not worth it at all!

Boom!

An explosion occurred inside his body and took away his last bit of health. Key of Solomon turned into a white light and died.

The commentator waved his fists in excitement.

"Such a wonderful and exciting fight. Congratulations to Frenzied Sword on finally emerging victorious!"

This match received a very high broadcast rating and popularity. Players from all around the world discussed the match passionately. They were especially happy to see the Summon Style getting overwhelmed.

As Frenzied Sword used the [Black Star's Advent] buff to crush the opponent, Han Xiao's fame increased indirectly.

A mysterious NPC that had been active since the start of the server launch finally revealed a little of his strength. The Great Mechanic Han was always a hot topic, and his past actions were made into memes by the players. As long as there was a related post, it was very easy for it to attract many people on the forums to meme it. This event sparked the players to guess his abilities and what Mechanic class style he used.

Frenzied Sword defeated a strong opponent, so his chance of qualifying increased. Key of Solomon's final trump card was forced out, but he still lost in the end. The Summoner that should have been like a boss became the party that fought against a boss. After the match, many reporters deliberately asked how it felt to be crushed as a Summoner. These questions were like rubbing salt in Key of Solomon's wounds. He left the scene furiously.

Actually, his [Howling Gate] was truly strong. In the matches afterward, he had no choice but to go all out in order to qualify. He used [Howling Gate] and defeated strong opponents one after another, showcasing how strong a Summoner was. However, the better he performed, the more it backed up how overpowered Frenzied Sword was, or more accurately, how overpowered the Han Xiao Character Summon Card was.

Frenzied Sword got rid of the post-match interview, hastily returned to the hub stronghold, and looked for Han Xiao. He tasted the sweetness of the Ability Potion; it could turn the tables completely. For things like this, the more the merrier.

He went to Han Xiao's room, and Dynasty, Temple of God, and Long Sky's people had been surrounding Han Xiao since long ago. They had all watched the match and could not wait to buy Black Star's Ability Potion.

However, there was no new stock in the store panel.

They looked up at Han Xiao. This scene made Han Xiao feel like these players were pigs waiting to be fed, and he became the mother pig.

"What you looking at? Do you want the Ability Potion? There's no more!" Han Xiao chased them out.

You people, the potion came from my blood; trying it once was enough. I would have to drain myself completely to satisfy you guys.

Chapter 429: The Finals

The group matches were coming to an end. The situation was becoming clearer. Long Sky was in eighth place, and Temple of God was in ninth place; their point difference was not a small one. Temple of God had to get a huge win in order to surpass Long Sky, but the next match was between the two of them. This meant that no matter who won and who lost, there would definitely be one side that qualified.

Many Chinese spectators felt their hearts being squeezed. They all hoped that all three Chinese teams could enter the top eight, but the situation was a very difficult one. This internal battle was expected since the grouping was decided, but when it really happened, they were still nervous about it. Group C was filled with strong teams, so it was very difficult to gain points. Many teams that had the chance to qualify did not even enter the top ten, so Long Sky and Temple of God's result was already quite good.

Some players calculated the points and came up with a conclusion that made the people feel very complicated. Long Sky had more points. If they deliberately held back and lost this match, giving Temple of God enough points, Temple of God would be able to jump to the seventh place while Long Sky would drop to the ninth place. In that case, Long Sky's point difference with the eighth-place team would be very small. The matches coming up for them was easier than those for the eighth-place team, so there would be a very high chance for Long Sky to get back to eighth place. This way, there was a chance for both teams to qualify.

The worst outcome of the internal fight would be Temple of God winning with a slight advantage and only getting a few points while Long Sky lost and did not get any points. This would mean that this round was a waste and did not produce many points. Not only would Temple of God's situation remain unchanged, but Long Sky's ranking would also become unstable.

Working together secretly was the only way to achieve the best results.

However, this was just the thoughts of the fans. Hao Tian had never been someone who would do such things. His professionalism made him go all out against any opponent, and it was absolutely impossible for him to fake the match. His personality was very simple and direct, so he did not want to bother about these things.

Long Sky did not plan to hold back at all. This internal battle was tragic and intense. Both sides had armor and were similar in strength. The outcome of this battle was Long Sky getting the upper hand and winning, defeating Temple of God and making their ranking more stable.

Temple of God's hope to qualify was destroyed by Long Sky.

A part of Temple of God's fans immediately became enraged. They scolded and blamed Long Sky and even made it into a matter of betrayal. However, most people, including a portion of Temple of God's fans, did not agree with such comments. They felt that Long Sky did nothing wrong. This was a competition, and competition meant going all out; playing fake matches was an unethical act, so there was not much to discuss when they lost after giving their all.

Of course, Temple of God stood on the side with moral high ground, telling the fans to not blame Long Sky, saying that they were the ones that did not perform well. Of course, it was impossible for them to be not upset; their journey in the International League had come to an end, but their competitor continued their journey by stepping on their corpses. However, Temple of God had always been very realistic. The situation had already been determined, so there was no need to be angry about it. The problem that they thought of was preventing more losses, which was what Li Ge was good at. He was proficient in building a good image and guiding the comments.

Under Li Ge's lead, not only did they deliberately not fight seriously in the last few matches, but they changed their tactics and fought more fiercely and aggressively. It felt like they knew that they had no chance to qualify, so they stopped being so cautious and played the game their way. More importantly, their goal was to give the impression that they wanted to make sure the opponents did not get too many points from them, which meant that they were indirectly helping Long Sky drag the enemies down, building an image of never giving up and showcasing the spirit of teamwork. Then they found someone to make this kind of 'deduction' in the forums and lead the others to agree. Temple of God's image became positive and selfless instantly; they were on the peak of the moral high ground. When people talked about Temple of God, they all praised them.

This way, not only did they receive fame and a better name, they also reduced the negative impact of not qualifying. Furthermore, they used this method to create a contrast between them and Long Sky, who defeated their fellow countrymen, emphasizing how 'virtuous' they were. The Temple of God superiors were somewhat satisfied with this result.

Of the four largest clubs in China, Temple of God was the most commercialized club. If losing the battle would give them more benefits, Han Xiao did not doubt that they would do that.

As the last match ended, the qualified teams were decided.

Devil

Dynasty

Hydra

Key

Tulips

Kangaroo Boxing

Rose Knight

Long Sky

Dynasty had the best performance in the group stages. Around the middle of the competition, they surpassed Devil and took first place, but in the last few matches, they held back purposely and dropped to second place. This was because the battle in the finals was determined according to the ranking of the group stages. If Dynasty was ranked in first place, their opponent would have been Long Sky, who were ranked in eighth place, which would not be good. Therefore, after discussing internally, Dynasty decided to drop one place. However, everyone knew that if Dynasty wanted to, they could absolutely have maintained their unbeaten streak and entered the finals without losing a single match.

This ranking was completely different from the one in Han Xiao's memory. Han Xiao's existence had a butterfly effect and changed the situation of the league. He vaguely remembered that one of the top eight in his previous life was Korea's Kimchi, but Kimchi was now below tenth place and had been replaced.

There were many strong teams in the top eight that had shone brightly in every season of the league in his previous life. Sadly, their novice planet was very distant, otherwise Han Xiao would have drawn those pro players into his faction. Their ability to complete missions was very dependable.

In the top eight, only China and America had two teams qualifying. Dynasty had been the only one in the top eight in his previous life, but Long Sky was now qualified as well.

In the Singles, Frenzied Sword qualified in fifteenth place, and King Admiral qualified in sixth place. There were two Chinese players qualifying as well. With strong teams and highly skilled players from so many areas competing on the same stage, getting this result was amazing.

The Galaxy Times did an episode focused on analyzing the performance of the teams that qualified, predicting the future situation in the finals. They came to the conclusion that three teams had the highest potential of becoming the champions—Devil, Dynasty, and Key. With the match system being Best of Five, every team would definitely use all their trump cards and target the opponent in any way possible.

The schedule of the finals was released. The first round was Key versus Tulips.

During the group stages, Han Xiao had stayed in Juberly Hub and temporarily rejected the partnership invitations from other mercenary groups, letting his team rest. He was not doing nothing; he had built more machinery, guided Aroshia, commanded the Sunil Division to do other missions, and helped Herlous in combat training.

Now that the group stages had ended and the ranking was up to his expectations, Han Xiao did not focus on the details of the competition anymore. No matter what results the teams got, it would not impact him much. He continued to expand the business scope of the mercenary group.

It just so happened that the Head Butler of the Floating Dragon Island, Jenny, had sent him a supply mission. The Logistics Manager Haier had requested a new batch of resources. The seller's team was on a Godoran colonized planet in the Gavin Star System, so they required Han Xiao to escort the goods.

Ames almost did not manage anything at all; Jenny had always been the one dealing with all matters. Compared to the other three beyond grade A individuals in the Shattered Star Ring, Ames was the most carefree in terms of making his forces stronger. The other three more or less had armies, while Ames only had a group of guards. The Black Star Mercenary Group was the only external combat force under her command, but they were actually just running errands. After all, compared to those large fleets, a medium mercenary group was as insignificant as a speck of dust.

Floating Dragon's protection did not come free; his Black Star Mercenary Group was Floating Dragon's field team on paper, so they often had to do some errand missions such as escorting supplies, chasing enemies, collecting intel, and so on. It was similar to the daily missions of a faction; it did not have a high experience reward and was mainly meant for increasing the faction favorability. Han Xiao's faction favorability with Floating Dragon was already at 2,100 points, and the relationship had become [Friendly].

Han Xiao brought the others and headed out. As the players used Gathering Crystals to enter the match, they were not limited to one location, so they acted together with Han Xiao.

Although the competition was important, following Han Xiao was crucial as well, or there would be no one to repair their armor.

Chapter 430: Poison Assassination

Tulips defeated Key 3:1 and entered the top four.

Most strong teams reserved their trump cards for the group stages, but Club Key's trump card had been showcased in advance due to the battle between Frenzied Sword and Key of Solomon. Although [Howling Gate] was very strong, the other teams had plenty of time to think of ways to deal with it. Tulips was steady and strong, and they had a trump card as well, which they finally used for the first time. As Key of Solomon expected, his team was unprepared and defeated. If not for Key of Solomon, who overperformed in the third match, it would have been an overwhelming 3:0 defeat.

Club Key stopped at the top eight. This result was far from Key of Solomon's target of becoming the champion, so he was furious.

On the other side, the Black Star Mercenary Group arrived at the planet where the resource team was and prepared for the escort.

...

A fan-shaped light-gold interstellar space station was floating outside the atmosphere of a Godoran colonized planet, following its course and orbiting indefinitely. Its alloy shell emitted a magic aura, and various models of spaceships were parked there. The seller was waiting for Han Xiao's arrival. His name was Tyrell, a slightly known businessman in the Gavin Star System. He operated a commercial department store group and had a long-term agreement with the logistics department of Floating Dragon. Han Xiao carried out numerous resource escorting missions, and Tyrell and he had known each other for quite some time.

Han Xiao and the others arrived at the pier, and a voice came from afar.

"Haha, Black Star of Floating Dragon, we meet again."

Tyrell was a Godoran. His body shape was round, and he had a passionate smile on his face. He approached with quick steps and gave Han Xiao a bear hug. "Have to trouble you guys again. All the resources that Floating Dragon needs are packaged and listed. Do you need to do a check?"

He guided Han Xiao and the others to the side, where metal boxes piled up like a small hill. They were all resources that Haier had ordered.

"We've worked together so many times; I don't doubt your reputation. However, this is Jenny's request, so I'll have to let my people do a check." Han Xiao passed the list to Maple Moon and gave her a counting goods mission.

"Understood, understood." Tyrell rubbed his hands and smiled brightly.

Escort resources were a daily mission, and the reward was 150 Floating Dragon Faction Favorability. Because of Han Xiao's position as a member of Floating Dragon, Tyrell gave him a certain discount, so Han Xiao often bought things from Tyrell. He trusted Tyrell's reputation, but now that he was working for Floating Dragon, it was better to be more careful.

When ordering resources in the virtual interstellar network, the logistics were a problem. Other than those advanced civilizations that normalized long-range transportation devices, the logistics in space were usually contracted by professional delivery organizations, or the seller would partner with a travel agency and have them airdrop the delivery on their way. There were many scavengers in Shattered Star Ring, and some low-level galactic pirates focused on robbing logistic spaceships. Hence, the commercial teams would usually hire mercenaries as guards.

Maple Moon counted very quickly; the number was correct. Han Xiao nodded and said, "There's no problem, let's head out now."

"I have already contacted a travel agency spaceship; it's parked at port 5468." Tyrell turned and said to one of his staff, "Dekker, get some men and take the resources into the goods cabin, then follow Black Star to Floating Dragon Island to carry out the handover."

The man who was called Dekker nodded, called some workers, and started transporting the boxes to the port. He was a regular manager of the Tyrell Group. He looked very ordinary, and he was someone that did not attract much attention.

Han Xiao and the others stepped onto the stairs into the travel agency spaceship. Tyrell stood on the dock and said loudly, "Send my regards to Jenny."

Han Xiao waved his hands and walked into the spaceship. After the hatch closed, he wrote a guard mission and gave it to some players, then told Herlous to take them to the goods cabin and begin shifts to protect the goods. He then went to the guest cabin with the others.

With some turbulence, the spaceship took off. This was a small traveling spaceship, so there were no other passengers. Tyrell had booked the entire spaceship specifically to transport supplies for Floating Dragon.

There were few people on the ship. Other than ten or so crew members and mercenary group members, there were only around ten of Tyrell Group's employees. Dekker was their boss. Han Xiao had met him before. They did not communicate much, but he did notice that Dekker brought a girl onto the ship this time.

"Are you Black Star?"

In the guest hall, as soon as they sat down, the girl beside Dekker spoke. She tilted her head and looked at Han Xiao curiously.

Han Xiao sized her up. This was a space human teenage girl, rather young, about fifteen to sixteen years old, and her head only reached Han Xiao's chest. She had dark brown short hair, pale skin, and a pretty face. The bridge of her nose was tall, and her bright eyes were filled with a youthful energy.

"Uncle Dekker always tells me stories. He's talked about you before." The teenage girl's eyes moved up and down on Han Xiao's body, sizing him up.

Dekker coughed and said, "This is one of my friend's daughters. Her family... ahem, let me take care of her temporarily. She wanted to follow me no matter what, so I brought her onto the ship. Lord Black Star, would that be a problem?"

"Not at all." Han Xiao shook his head. He looked at the teenage girl, smiled, and asked, "What's your name?"

"Sylvia."

"Quite a nice name, what's your home planet?"

Sylvia curled her lips. "Are you doing an identity check, Uncle?"

"Uncle..." Han Xiao was speechless. He was clearly young and handsome. What nonsense was she talking about?

Sylvia looked glanced at Han Xiao sideways, changed the topic, and said in disdain, "I heard you mercenaries have no morals and fight for whichever side pays higher. I really want to know, is the money earned from selling your souls not hot to hold?"

Han Xiao raised his eyebrows. Before he spoke, Dekker pulled Sylvia back in terror, scolded her, and hastily apologized to Han Xiao. "She doesn't understand many things. Please don't take it to heart."

"It's alright, understandable." Han Xiao waved his hands. Words had basically zero impact on him, so of course, he did not care. "This small girl has quite some guts. She knows we are a bunch of brutes, yet he still dares to question me right in my face. Quite brave."

"I'm not a small girl!" Sylvia was a little angry and pushed her chest up.

"Hmm... not small indeed but still needs development." Bun-Hit-Dog's eyes moved down, and a dirty smile appeared on his face. Suddenly, he realized that Han Xiao was looking at him without saying anything. He immediately kept his eyes to himself, wiped off his smile, and sat up straight.

They fastened their seatbelt, and the spaceship entered jumping mode very quickly—only then could they walk around freely. Sylvia was energetic and active. She curiously ran around the spaceship and glanced through the spaceship's structure in awe. Sometimes, she would place her head on the porthole and look outside the window at the streams of light outside.

Dekker smiled bitterly and said, "This is her first time on a spaceship. Sorry to trouble you."

"As long as the mission is not affected." Han Xiao looked at the energetic back view of the teenage girl and narrowed his eyes.

Sylvia... this name sounds kind of familiar.

He did not want to give up even the slightest doubt. He returned to his room and pondered for more than ten minutes. Finally, he found someone in his memories who had this name.

[Mechanical Lady Knight] Sylvia?

Han Xiao froze for a second. He did not expect the teenage girl that he had met coincidentally to be a known character. Furthermore, in the storyline of his previous life, Sylvia was very well known and was especially popular among the players.

Sylvia was still a young girl now. Han Xiao recalled her look in his previous life after 'growing up'—long hair, valiant and fearless, wearing light mechanical armor and a cape, just like a knight.

What was a very important factor in determining the attractiveness of a female character? Parodies!

Sylvia had a lot of parodies and being pretty was just one factor. After all, there were way too many pretty females in Galaxy. The more important reason was her background, identity, personality, and storyline.

Beauty was never Han Xiao's focus. He recalled Sylvia's character background. It was way too long ago, so he could only vaguely remember.

Sylvia's father was chased by a certain mercenary group and died. She was still young back then, so she took the path of revenge. She moved from forces to forces, learned Mechanic class knowledges, and became a galactic pirate chasing after that mercenary group.

In the timeline of that version, due to the Crimson Empire expanding once again, all the Star Fields could only care about themselves. The large mercenary groups in various Star Clusters of the Shattered Star Ring mimicked the mercenaries in the Silver Arm Star Field, creating the Shattered Star Ring Alliance. They turned themselves into an enormous mercenary group with millions of members and tens of thousands of battleships of all kinds of models, more than enough to take part in even large space wars.

Sylvia was the arch-enemy of the mercenary alliance.

Players back then took part in the mercenary alliance event. In their eyes, Sylvia was a renowned villain boss of the opposite party. Many players received missions to chase and kill Sylvia, but they all failed. Sylvia was too strong.

During the times of opposing the mercenary alliance, Sylvia often appeared in the eyes of the players. Then, through what looked like an accident, she discovered that her father was the bad guy and knew that her father deserved his death. She then disappeared for a period of time. When she reappeared, she was not a galactic pirate anymore; she became a freedom fighter of Shattered Star Ring, helping the people who were victims of harm, dealing with some criminals, and being responsible for quite a number of famous events. Furthermore, they rejected rewards or requests in any form; all their actions came from themselves. They were like Superheroes... Basically, she reformed.

Although Sylvia was not the main character of a certain event, she was a renowned character like Hila. She was involved in many events in the Shattered Star Ring. When the players wandered in space, they would sometimes bump into her fighting bad guys and could choose to help her. She was loved by many in Shattered Star Ring... These were all things that happened after Version 3.0

Han Xiao shook his head. Sylvia's reform process and her experience of turning from someone with so much hatred into someone as righteous as a knight were filled with opportunities for parodies, such as...

Bah! Why am I thinking of this?

Didn't expect to meet a future celebrity...

Han Xiao stroked his chin.

For some reason, he felt somewhat strange, like he had missed some important information.

...

Floating Dragon Island was in the Rain Star System of the Colton Star Cluster. There was a small star gate on their way that could teleport them, and the traveling time was about ten days.

Every day, Han Xiao built machinery and traded with the players.

He did not pay much attention to the league, only looking at the results. The top four teams were decided. Long Sky stopped at the top eight after facing Devil, who were ranked first, and were defeated 1:3. It was quite regretful. Dynasty defeated Rose Knight 3:2, advancing to top four. Japan's Hydra defeated Australia's Kangaroo Boxing 3:1. The top four teams were Tulips, Devil, Dynasty, and Hydra.

The upcoming grouping was extremely important. It seemed like the prayers of countless Chinese spectators had an effect; Dynasty's next opponent was team Hydra. Compared to the steady Tulips and extremely strong Devil, Hydra was no doubt a weaker opponent. Dynasty had the most confidence in defeating Hydra as compared to the other two teams. The Chinese panel in the forums was practically celebrating already.

In terms of Singles, King Admiral advanced to top eight, Frenzied Sword stopped at top sixteen. But Frenzied Sword was very satisfied; he was already overjoyed that he could enter the second round of the International League, a result that was much higher than his initial expectations. Compared to Frenzied Sword's ranking in Han Xiao's previous life, this was indeed a huge improvement. In his previous life, Frenzied Sword did not even make it into the International League, but now, he was one of the top sixteen players on the International League. Frenzied Sword benefitted the most, and his position among the Chinese players rocketed from nobody to a Supernova.

Ten days later, the spaceship exited the jumping state. Floating Dragon was only half a day away.

It was dining time. Han Xiao walked out of the machinery modification room and came to the dining hall. This was the usual dining area, so many people were eating there. The food was all portable space food, so it could not be considered delicious, but it was not tasteless either.

Herlous called for him from the bar.

"Have a drink?" Herlous had a bottle of liquor in front of him, the alcohol made his face slightly red.

"Almost forgot you're an alcoholic." Han Xiao sat down, and the bartender passed him a new cup. Herlous laughed, lifted the liquor bottle, and poured him a cup.

Han Xiao shook his head and lifted up the cup. Just as he was going to drink it, his movement suddenly stopped, and an unknown alert appeared in his heart.

Frowning slightly, he looked at the object introduction on his interface.

[Strong Liquor with an Added Ingredient]

Effects: Unknown

Bang!

The smashing sound shocked everyone. They put their food down and looked over in surprise.

Han Xiao held the bartender's collar, pressed the panicking bartender on the bar table, and said coldly without an expression, "You added poison‽"

Chapter 431: Revenge from the Past (1)

"What do you want‽"

The bartender was a member of the ship's crew. His face was filled with panic, and he could not even struggle.

Herlous was shocked. "Captain, this is?"

Han Xiao pointed at his cup and said, "Someone added something inside, probably poison."

"Impossible, I brought the liquor. Why am I fine after drinking it... or have I been poisoned too?"

Herlous was shocked. He hurriedly touched his tongue and throat, but there was no sign of the numbness from being poisoned.

"There is no problem with the liquor; it's the cup." The item information of the liquor bottle was normal—only his cup had something added into it. The only possibility was that someone had put something into the cup in advance, and the bartender who took out the cup was the most suspicious.

This started as a very simple daily escorting mission; Han Xiao did not expect to meet something like this. He was very curious—who wanted him dead?

This time, the players and the company employees came. Dekker and the others hurried there as well. They were very confused.

"What happened?"

Han Xiao explained simply, and everyone was surprised.

"Could it be a mistake?" Dekker asked.

Han Xiao shook his head. He wrote a new mission and threw it to the players.

You have triggered mission [Poison Testing]

Mission Introduction: Someone seems to have attempted to poison your captain. Are you willing to help him to test the effect of the poison?

Mission Requirements: Drink [Strong Liquor with an Added Ingredient]

Reward: Black Star—Han Xiao Favorability +8, 150,000 experience.

Remarks: Possible death

The mercenary group players received the notification on their interface. Their eyes sparkled for this was the first time that they had seen such an easy mission that could increase Han Xiao's Favorability and receive experience. Dying once was nothing.

Just as they were about to snatch the cup, a shadow flew past everyone. Bun-Hit-Dog snatched the cup extremely quickly and gulped it down without saying a word.

"How are you able to run this fast‽" Second Prince was shocked. I'm a Dexterity-focused Pugilist, yet I could not even catch up to you. How did you do it?

Bun-Hit-Dog glanced at everyone with pride. Before he could speak, his face suddenly changed, and the veins under his skin expanded and turned black, covering his entire face. He opened his mouth but could not say a word. The other players moved back as they saw this, leaving no one within a three-meter radius from Bun-Hit-Dog.

Bun-Hit-Dog froze in place for a few seconds, then blood sprayed out from his every orifice. He collapsed onto the ground and died on the spot.

"Tsk tsk, truly a man of the wind. He even died quickly," Frenzied Sword said.

"He—he's dead just like that‽"

The company employees and the crews were all dumbfounded. A mercenary died right on the spot, yet his friends had no reaction at all. What mercenary group is this? They're so cold-blooded! So horrifying!

Plus, these mercenaries are way too loyal to Black Star. Black Star had yet to even speak and they were already rushing to drink the poisoned alcohol, testing the poison with their body. This does not feel like a mercenary group at all but a fanatical cult!

However, the next moment, Bun-Hit-Dog's corpse turned into white light and disappeared, then the sound of trotting footsteps appeared outside the door almost immediately after. Bun-Hit-Dog had run over from the revive point.

"Yo—you..." Dekker stammered in shock.

Han Xiao looked at him. "After working together so many times, I'm surprised that you don't know that we have the nickname 'Immortal Mercenary Group'?"

"I see, I don't know much about the mercenary industry." Dekker smiled bitterly. No wonder the mercenaries were so calm, they were all immortals.

Black Star's name was widely known, but his details were only known within the industry; the other industries did not know much about it.

Han Xiao turned around and asked, "What was the effect of the poison?"

Bun-Hit-Dog looked at the notification from earlier.

You have consumed a certain poison. Judging END... Your END is lower than 280. No related immunity ability detected. You have entered [Poisoned] state.

High Concentration Corrosive Blood Poison: This is a poison made from some Esper ability and requires blood poison cure.

Current poison level: 135/135

You are losing 750 health per second.

Duration: 8 seconds

Warning! Your health is too low. Please consume antidote as soon as possible!

Your health is lower than 0!

You died!

Bun-Hit-Dog read accordingly, and Han Xiao nodded.

6,000 health in eight seconds, very lethal to players but can't kill me. This means that the person who added the poison has limited information of me, but the fact that the culprit could poison me on this trip means that they know my location or at least know that this ship is transporting supplies for Floating Dragon and that I would definitely appear here. This ship is only so big, and the culprit is definitely hidden among them. Plus, even the title of 'Immortal Mercenary Group' did not scare the culprit away, so there can only be two possibilities. Either they know that I'm not immortal or... an act of revenge?

Han Xiao's eyebrows were locked tightly. He had many guesses in his mind, and even the players were not excluded!

He had to guard against the possibility of something like this happening. He made himself stronger by helping the players, but he never completely trusted them. After all, he knew too well what the players were like. He only hoped that this was not the right guess and that there was no player who privately accepted a mission to assassinate him.

After proving Han Xiao's words true, many pairs of eyes full of hostility stared at the bartender who had collapsed on the side. The bartender saw that the poison did exist and was scared sh*tless; his entire body was shivering.

"It wasn't me. I don't know anything about this. I just took an empty cup from the drawer..."

Han Xiao opened the bar drawer. There were many empty cups inside. He took all of them out and poured water in each of them. These were all normal; his cup was the only one that had poison. He frowned and said, "There are so many glasses, and the only one with poison is the one you gave me. How can you explain that?"

"I—I don't know. That glass was at the most outside. I really just took it randomly!"

The bartender almost urinated out of horror.

Herlous suddenly was covered in cold sweat. "If the bartender took the wrong cup, wouldn't that have been the end of me‽"

"Your body is strong; the poison wouldn't have killed you," Han Xiao replied. He stared at the shivering bartender and said, "If it's not you, it's someone else that did something to the cup. Captain! Where's the captain?"

The spaceship's captain hurried to the scene, stepped out of the crowd, and said with sorrow on his face, "I'm the captain of Rainbow Conch. I am extremely sorry that something like this happened in my ship. I will provide my full cooperation to you with finding the culprit."

"I want to see the surveillance recording of this few days and see who has come close to this place."

"As you wish."

Other than the bedrooms, most areas of the spaceship had surveillance cameras, including the dining hall. The culprit could be found immediately through the recordings.

The bartender was surprised. "So, I'm free to go?"

"Are you dreaming?" Han Xiao said. "Tie him up and bring him along."

The captain led them to the main control room. Just as he was about to browse through the surveillance recordings, he was shocked to realize that the recordings had been wiped. Even the earliest recording was from less than one day ago.

"The surveillance recordings are all deleted!" The captain was stunned. "I'm the only one who can make such commands. Could it be that the spaceship system has been infiltrated? The culprit could bypass the alarms‽"

He hastily opened the background, passed through authorization with his fingerprint and pupils, and activated the system scan, but there was no sign of infiltration.

"Why can't the infiltration be detected? Is the spaceship completely controlled by the enemy‽"

The captain was sweating profusely. He looked at the operation diary of the spaceship, hoping to find the ID of the person that deleted the recordings. This small traveling spaceship belonged to a galactical traveling organization, so the captain was hired and only had second-tier authorization. The highest system authorization belonged to the organization, and the captain could not modify the dairy. Hence, even if the culprit controlled the spaceship, the dairy would not be changed. Unless the opponent's technology was strong enough to bypass the quantum network defense of the organization's headquarters and get the highest authorization.

However, there was no sign of any other accounts logging into the system, but they did find the records of the recordings being deleted.

[Operation Dairy #00784315]

22 hours ago—Clean all surveillance recordings.

Authorization granted.

Confirm/Back

Confirmed.

Deleting... Complete.

Operator: Captain's account

Chapter 432: Revenge from the Past (2)

The captains' eyes opened widely. "Why is it my account‽ I didn't do it! Twenty-two hours ago... I was sleeping at that time! It's the culprit, the culprit stole my account! But... the login password is my biometric data, how can they be stolen..."

The people looked at him doubtfully. Maybe it was you. Now that the surveillance footage is gone, you can say whatever you want.

"There are a few possibilities. Maybe the superiors of your travel agency worked with another organization that is against us, or maybe the opposite party used some method to get the captain's body password data, or maybe... there's a shapeshifter Esper hidden in the ship," Herlous contemplated.

Everyone's face changed. They looked at each other with suspicion—everyone looked like an enemy.

Han Xiao raised his eyebrows and looked around the crowd. Everyone on the ship was gathered here, even Sylvia. She hid at the edge of the crowd and showed half of her face, sizing him up...

His eyes suddenly narrowed.

Wait a minute, Sylvia?

With a flash of insight, Han Xiao finally realized where the strange feeling came from. He looked at Dekker and said, "Sylvia is your friend's daughter, is she?"

Dekker nodded and said with a confused face, "Yes, what's wrong with that?"

Han Xiao squinted his eyes. "Her family... only has her father, and if I remember correctly, that person is not a nobody. I almost fell for your lies; you acted quite well. Leniency for those who confess, severity for those who resist. Are you going to confess on your own, or do you need me to help you confess?"

Dekker's expression froze. His eyes clearly expressed his shock and disbelief. Why do you know who Sylvia is‽

Although Han Xiao did not know exactly who Sylvia's father was, he remembered that her father was a villain in the background introduction, and that was enough. Dekker was just a regular employee of a business organization, yet he had a villainous friend. It was certainly possible but still very questionable...

Han Xiao shook his head in his mind. He should have noticed this long ago, but everything was normal, so he did not think too much about it. It seemed like he had let his guard down a little recently.

After resting for a month due to the Pro League, along with not facing any huge threats in the nine months before that, his alertness had decreased subconsciously. Luckily, he noticed that in time and became more alert.

This time, Sylvia walked out. She was frowning. The feeling that she gave was completely different; the young and energetic feeling that she gave earlier was all a disguise. Although her body was still in puberty, the feeling that she gave was not like a teenage girl anymore—she felt more mature.

Sylvia stared at Han Xiao; her tone was complex and mixed with astonishment.

"You know me?"

She could not figure out how it was possible for Han Xiao to recognize who she was despite him meeting her for the first time. Logically, Black Star should not even know that she existed; she should have always been hidden in the dark.

Sylvia had thought of many possible ways in which she would be found out but never thought of her identity being exposed. Because of this, she would not be able to carry out her plan anymore.

In reality, if Han Xiao did not remember Sylvia's character background, he would not have known the identity of the culprit. It was indeed not a coincidence to suddenly meet a future renowned character!

Sylvia clenched his teeth and spat furiously, "Black Star, my father was sent to jail by you. You dishonorable mercenaries only fight for money, and for that, you help those tyrants suppress the people who are suffering. My father could've saved everyone, but he couldn't because of your mercenaries!"

Since she was already exposed, she did not act like a teenage girl anymore.

The players exchanged looks confusingly. When did we do something like that?

Maple Moon could not help but ask, "Little girl, what's your father's name?"

"Langley! How can you forget his name?" Sylvia was emotional.

Han Xiao opened the mercenary group panel and glanced through it. There really was this name in the mission resume. It was a partnership mission with the Purple Gold Army, to eradicate the stronghold of a certain rebel army. The leader of the rebels was called Langley, and as it turned out, that guy was Sylvia's father.

Han Xiao was speechless. He had become the 'certain mercenary group' that imprisoned Sylvia's father in her character background. What could he say? This was the result of the butterfly effect once again. It fell from the sky.

"Not only you but Purple Gold Army too. This will not be the last time; I will hunt you people to the depths of hell!" Sylvia yelled.

Bang!

As soon as she finished her sentence, the sound of a smoke grenade exploding came from behind them. Dark red poison gas rose from within.

_____________________

You are surrounded by certain poison gas. Judging END... Your END is lower than 280. No related immunity ability detected.

You have entered [Poisoned] state.

Low Concentration Corrosive Blood Poison Gas: This is a poison gas made from some Esper ability, require blood poison cure.

Current poison level: 30/30

You are losing 200 health per second.

Effects will wear off after not breathing in poison gas for 3 seconds.

_____________________

They turned around hastily and saw that the captain had already put on a gas mask. He was the one that threw out the gas grenades.

At the same time, the announcement from the spaceship system echoed in the entire spaceship.

"Auto-Navigation altered. Current destination: The closest Fixed Star. Heating up jumping engine. Estimated time till arrival: 13 minutes and 48 seconds."

"The entire ship has entered lockdown mode; all gates are locked! Repeat, all gates are locked!"

Boom!

The gate in the main control room closed with a loud band, together with all the doors along the corridor and paths in the spaceship. The captain had prepared long ago. He dashed out extremely quickly before the alloy door on the other side of the main control room closed. Herlous could not capture the captain in time, and he punched the metal door, leaving a shallow dent.

The central alloy door divided a small part of the crowd and blocked them outside, including Sylvia.

Now, Han Xiao and the others were all trapped inside the main control room.

The crew was all stunned. The captain was with an enemy‽

Whoosh.

This time, clouds of dark red poison gas sprayed out from the ventilation pipe. The ventilation system had been modified, and now the hidden system was activated by the 'captain'.

Han Xiao held his breath, and his eyes flickered.

This was not just an assassination; this ship itself was a complete trap for them! The reason that Sylvia knew their whereabouts was most likely because of how well known they were.

This time, a new mission appeared on the interface.

_____________________

You have triggered Urgent Mission [Sylvia's Revenge].

Mission Introduction: Because of a regular mercenary mission, you made Sylvia lose her father. Now, you have to face the blazing flames of her revenge.

Mission Requirements: Nullify Sylvia's revenge methods.

Reward: 1,200,000 Experience.

_____________________

"Tsk tsk, they actually plotted against us and plan to send us into a Fixed Star and burn us to a crisp. Not a bad idea."

Han Xiao smiled. He did not panic at all; he was extremely familiar with this kind of plan. He had fought the Germinal Organization this way back then.

"What do we do now?" Herlous looked at him. He could breathe and talk as usual because his END was more than 280, so the poison gas could not hurt him.

"Her plan is quite interesting, but she missed a very important factor..."

The mechanical suit expanded from his necklace to his entire body. His helmet filtered the poison gas, and his 'Poisoned' state was gone in no time. Han Xiao walked in front of the main control panel, pressed on the screen, and opened the spaceship system interface. He stretched his fingers, shook his head, and laughed.

"I'm a Mechanic."

Chapter 433: Revenge from the Past (3)

The players activated the filter in their armor as well, making them immune to the poison gas. They looked at Han Xiao and waited for his orders.

"That captain used his authority and locked the spaceship's navigation. I'll hack into the spaceship system and change its course. You guys blast the alloy gate open; some of you go to the central computer room and insert this chip, and the rest of you go to capture Sylvia and her allies."

Han Xiao opened his palm. With a flash of electricity, a black chip flew out from his pocket.

"Understood." Herlous nodded. He pocketed the chip, swung his Battleship Slicing Blade, and slashed alloy door. With a piercing sound of steel being torn apart, an opening appeared. Dozens of armored players raised their firearms and fired at the door. The door was quickly covered in holes before collapsing.

In the poison gas, they walked out of the main control room. In front of them was another locked alloy door, and the group of people who had been separated earlier were trapped in the pathway. Many of them were poisoned and barely clinging on to life. Dekker was surprisingly among them too, but Sylvia had disappeared.

The players took out gas masks and placed them on these people. Dekker was weak and powerless. The moment he caught his breath, he started tearing up.

"I—I was forced. That girl used my family to threaten me, forcing me to act and cooperate with her. I really had no choice. I'm sorry. I'm sorry..."

"Cut the cr*p. Where's Sylvia?" Herlous demanded.

"She's allied with that captain. She used the authority to open the alloy gate and escaped, leaving us here."

Bang!

Herlous slapped Dekker unconscious and said, "Tie him up. The captain might question him later."

Gunshots echoed in the spaceship. They broke through alloy doors one after another rather quickly. Sylvia had turned the spaceship into a trap, but the spaceship itself could not trap them. This was the difference in raw strength.

Han Xiao guessed that Sylvia would be going to the escape cabin as soon as possible and escape before the spaceship entered the jump state, at the same time releasing all the emergency escape ships and trap them in the spaceship. However, he was a Mechanic and could seize the spaceship's authorization. This was the flaw in Sylvia's plan.

Han Xiao opened the spaceship system—his fingers moved so quickly that they created afterimages. He entered countless codes and quickly hacked into the background of the system. Then he met resistance from the security system. He had bought some new advanced knowledges throughout the nine months, such as [Advanced Smart Technology], which made up for his weakness in terms of hacking. That black chip was an even stronger assistant Artificial Intelligence. After plugging it into the central computer room, the speed of breaking through the system would be doubled.

The alarm was triggered, and the system warning echoed in the spaceship.

"System infiltration detected! Please stop your actions immediately!"

As time was limited, Han Xiao did not go around the alarm and chose the roughest method.

"Hmm... 13th generation firewall from the TAK Series, 47th calculating method of the Silverlight sequence, random password wall. Quite advanced actually." Han Xiao's movements did not stop. He said while hacking, "Breaking through this system will take about five minutes, but the spaceship will enter the jumping state in two minutes. Sylvia will board the escape ship before this. Aroshia, capture her."

Upon hearing Han Xiao's words, Aroshia turned into energy form and left through the wall. Metal walls were meaningless to her; only energy barriers could stop her from going through the wall.

Everyone was moving, while Han Xiao stayed in the main control room and focused on hacking the system.

...

"Damn, how was I exposed? How can Black Star possibly know who I am?"

The sound of hurried footsteps echoed in the ship bridge. Sylvia was running hastily. She used the captain's authority to open one alloy door after another and closed them after she passed through.

The sound of gunfire became clearer, meaning that she did not have much time left. If they fought directly, she would not be able to resist at all.

Every second counted at this time. Sylvia did not dare to stop. Warm, moist air came out of her lungs time after time as she gasped for breath.

In order to complete the trap, she had used all her savings to hire a freelance killer and even knew about Han Xiao's whereabouts through the intel network of an organization. Sylvia clearly knew that she was too weak. In order to go against the Black Star Mercenary Group, she could only depend on a conspiracy and plot like that. She wanted this spaceship to become Black Star's grave... Sadly, she could now only hope to save herself.

Do you regret it?

A sound echoed in her heart. Sylvia bit her lips.

Many images appeared in her head. Her father's eyes that were full of love, the happy memories of her childhood, plating her memories with warmth.

However, the images shattered like a mirror. Flames devoured these memories. Mercenaries landed from the sky and destroyed everything with fire. If her father had not sent her away in advance, she would have died in that storm of bullets.

After being captured by the mercenaries, her father was sent to jail. She had wandered around and suffered a lot before she could finally return to the old place. Her father's stronghold was like a home to her, but now, the only things left were the burnt ruins.

She still remembered, when she was young, she liked to hide under the shade of an old tree and spend lazy afternoons time after time. But that tree was turned into charcoal now, giving out a pungent odor. The black branches were the only things left of the once dense leaves.

Every time she thought of these things, the uncontrollable flames of rage would burn her nerves and shatter her reason.

"In order to have my revenge on these mercenaries, it's worth it to be in danger!" Sylvia clenched her teeth.

Very soon, she arrived at the escape cabin. Inside were ten or so escape ships.

The captain happened to arrive at the same time, and he complained, "You did not tell me that the risks were this high. I want a greater reward."

The turbulence was becoming more violent. As soon as they entered the jump state, they would not be able to use the escape ships unless they wanted to be torn into pieces together with the escape ships. Sylvia hastily pulled down the bolt of the escape ship. With the sound of air streams, the other escape ships were released, leaving only two behind.

Just as the two of them was about to walk in, a tint of golden light appeared behind them. Aroshia passed through the wall and made it just in time.

"Quickly, go!"

Sylvia clenched her teeth. She was about to enter the escape ship, then suddenly, the captain pushed her from her back and threw her toward Aroshia.

In times of danger, he could not be bothered about the fact that Sylvia was his employee; he just wanted to stall time.

In midair, Sylvia turned around in disbelief. She did not expect the sudden betrayal of the captain.

Hum!

An energy impact ring expanded, sending Sylvia flying before she even hit Aroshia. She bumped into the wall and fell down on the side. Her expression was distorted from the pain.

Aroshia's straightened her arm. Her forearm turned into a bean of gold energy and swept at the two escape ships like a whip, melting through their shell and leaving a consistent red cut. It was clear that they could not be used anymore.

The captain's face changed completely.

Boom!

The alloy door collapsed. Herlous and the players rushed to the scene and surrounded the two of them.

At the same time, the spaceship suddenly trembled and entered the jump state.

"It's over..."

Sylvia closed her eyes in despair.

...

The poison gas dissipated slowly, and the locked alloy doors opened one after another. The spaceship exited the jump state and stopped in space.

Hacking the spaceship system was just a matter of time to Han Xiao. After getting Sylvia under control, he easily gained the captain's authorization.

The entire spaceship was under his control now. He canceled the navigation toward the Fixed Star, and the danger was diffused.

Sylvia felt that her plan was lethal, but in reality, it was not much of a threat to the current Black Star Mercenary Group. The mercenary group could get out of danger with their raw strength, so Han Xiao had no reason to panic at all. Sylvia was still too young and naive at this period of time.

The interface notified them that the mission was complete. The players were joyful upon receiving 1,200,000 experience.

The incident had come to an end. All the people on the ship were gathered in the guest hall—around them were mercenaries who aimed their firearms at them. In the middle were Sylvia, Dekker, and the captain, who were bound tightly.

Han Xiao sat on the sofa, placed his elbows on his knees, and leaned slightly forward, slowly scanning the three of them. His aura was like a crouching tiger, very pressurizing. The crew and the company employees did not even dare breathe loudly, despite them not being the ones who were being interrogated.

Dekker hastily explained the situation. A few days ago, the Tyrell Group had prepared the supplies for Floating Dragon Island and confirmed to let him take care of the handover. After that, Sylvia had found him and forced him to cooperate.

"You know about our whereabouts, so there's definitely an organization that provided you help. You're just a small girl and won't have such a vast intel network." Han Xiao was expressionless. "Plus, you bribed the captain to take the risk and fight a group of mercenaries, so you definitely depended on the power of that organization..."

Sylvia stared at Han Xiao with a determined face like she had decided not to say anything no matter what. She was not willing to lower her head in front of her enemy.

"Bang!"

The sound of gunshot suddenly appeared.

Smoke came out from the muzzle.

Droplets of blood splashed onto Sylvia's pretty face. Her whole body shivered, and she turned her head and looked over.

The captain's head had a penetrating hole of blood in it; the stunned expression was fixed on his face. He collapsed slowly, and the pool of blood expanded gradually.

The captain had thought that Han Xiao was going to interrogate him and was still troubled by what he should say in order to stay alive, but Han Xiao was completely uninterested in him and gave him a bullet straight away.

The widened eyes were filled with regret.

The corpse suddenly changed shape into another man. This was the shapeshifting Esper ability, especially suitable for infiltration. Herlous' eyes sparkled. "I guessed correctly. There is indeed a shapeshifting Esper."

Seeing this, Han Xiao could now guess roughly what had happened. "Looks like the original captain died long ago and was replaced by this shapeshifting Esper. He's a killer you hired, and he should be the one that poisoned the cup as well."

Sylvia bit her lower lip heavily. She turned her head to not look at the corpse. Despite her trying her best to stay strong, she could not stop herself from shivering or the tiny tears appearing in her eyes.

She only looked like a teenage girl in the face of her fear of death.

"Yo—you might as well kill me too!"

Sylvia closed her eyes and tried her best to make an unafraid expression.

"I don't oppose that."

The still-hot muzzle pressed on Sylvia's white and smooth face. Through the muzzle, Han Xiao could obviously feel Sylvia was shivering more and more heavily.

Chapter 434: Father (1)

Buzz!

At this time, a hologram appeared in the middle of the hall. It was an individual wearing luxurious clothes who looked similar to lizards. He scanned the entire place, looked at Han Xiao, and said in a confused tone, "The system of a spaceship under our organization was hacked. Black Star, did you do this?"

"Your response is too slow; I've been waiting for you." Han Xiao leaned back on the sofa and looked up at this lizardman, temporarily putting Sylvia's case aside.

This spaceship belonged to a galactic travel agency, so the organization had the highest level of authorization. As soon as the spaceship was taken away by an outsider, the organization would notice it right away and locate the spaceship, unless the connection was cut. However, doing so not only required hacking technology but also all sorts of disrupting and invading hardware, only then would the highest level of authorization be blocked. Han Xiao took the captain's authorization, so he had known long ago that the actual owner of the spaceship would find him.

Although the spaceship was under his control, there was no way to block the owner's range surveillance. With his technology level, it would take a few days to half a month to change the basic setting of the spaceship and erase the rights of the highest level of authorization. The deeper the authorization level was, the stronger its defense was; the difference in difficulty was like the difference between hacking into a small enterprise and hacking into the government.

The lizardman had thought that the spaceship had been stolen, but seeing the current situation, there seemed to be something else. He suppressed his rage and asked about what happened.

Han Xiao explained what had happened in a simple way. Knowing that the captain had been replaced and someone had tried to kill the passengers during the trip, the lizardman's face changed tremendously... but the humans present could not see it.

"I took your spaceship because I trusted your travel agency, but I faced such a huge danger. Your reputation is very disappointing! If potential customers hear about this, who would want to take your spaceship that's so unsafe?" Han Xiao pressed on his heart and spoke with an exaggerated tone, blackmailing under bright daylight. "Tsk... I have yet to recover from the terror. I am so upset. You have to compensate me for this, including mental damage, lost wages, post-trauma checkup, and others."

The lizardman swung his tail and said with frustration, "I'm sorry, this is a dereliction of duty from our organization. We will definitely deal with it and give you compensations accordingly..."

Assassinations were hard to guard against. His travel agency had been dragged into that mess as well, but there was nothing he could do. After all, it had happened on his spaceship.

There were many galactic travel agencies in the universe, so the competition was quite intense. If this was spread out in an exaggerated way, their brand image would definitely be affected. At least Black Star was a mercenary group that worked for money and kept their word—he was willing to compensate and avoid the damages.

This travel agency owned dozens of spaceships and made close to a thousand Enas every day, it would be a waste if Han Xiao did not make them pay. Han Xiao directly stated an outrageous amount, and after some negotiation, both of them barely agreed with compensation of 30,000 Enas.

After receiving the 30,000 Enas, Han Xiao now had around 840,000 Enas. He sighed in his heart and felt that blackmailing was a much quicker way to earn money compared to being a mercenary... but not as quick as earning from the players' wallets.

"Before you recall this spaceship, lend it to me for a few days. Anyways, you guys can track it and will know where the spaceship is," Han Xiao said.

"This... alright."

After agreeing, the upset lizardman turned off the communication.

Han Xiao did not intend to take the spaceship away. He was not a kid that could just snatch someone else's candy. Robbing a spaceship with an official owner will make him wanted, unless there were no witnesses. The cons outweighed the pros, and it was not as safe as blackmailing the owners. In his previous life, many players proved the consequences of robbing spaceships with actions. Regardless of whether they succeeded or failed, they would become wanted and be chased by mercenaries, bounty hunters, and the patrolling law enforcement of all civilizations. Their initial Favorability with the various lawful civilizations would drop by a huge amount as well. Also, if they were discovered in the cities or planets belonging to the lawful factions, they would be surrounded by the guards and imprisoned. It was not worth it at all.

Han Xiao had no interest in walking down the same path. He had no urgent need for spaceships, so he did not want to risk it. Furthermore, he knew how to get spaceships for free without the side effects, so of course, he was not interested in robbing the spaceship.

After this matter was settled, Han Xiao looked at Sylvia again.

This teenage girl was tied up tightly and was slumping at the side. Her low eyelashes trembled continuously, looking extremely pitiful and heartbreaking. However, this had absolutely no effect on the Great Mechanic Han. Only dead enemies were good enemies ...

"Wait a minute... who tied her up like this‽"

Han Xiao had only just realized the superb tying skills used on Sylvia.

Bun-Hit-Dog raised his hand immediately like a good student answering a question. He said with a bright smile on his face, "I did. Doesn't it look amazing?"

"You're really letting yourself go." Frenzied Sword's mouth twitched.

On the side, Herlous shook his head and asked, "Black Star, what are you planning to do with her?"

Han Xiao played with a firearm, glanced at him, and said, "Judging from your tone, you seem to have some suggestions. You should speak if you have any. I'm not a dictator—I believe in democracy."

Herlous paused and chose his words carefully. "She said, 'You dishonorable mercenaries helped those tyrants suppress the people who are suffering.' I think she has definitely misunderstood some details. We all know full well what kind of person Langley is, but she doesn't seem to. I think... isn't it better to ask about it first?"

Then, Herlous sighed and said, "After all, I understand the impulse of revenge. Not mentioning the fact that she's just a child, if there was a chance for me to assassinate the leader of DarkStar, I would not even hesitate."

"I see, good for you." Han Xiao's mouth twitched. He turned around, looked at the players behind him and asked, "What about you guys? Any suggestions?"

The players froze, not expecting to be asked.

"Us? Anything."

"Whatever is fine."

"Anything is fine... but which one gives a better reward?"

"This girl is quite pretty—it's a shame to kill her."

The players replied carelessly. Most of them were male—they preferred to be decisive and get it done with. The female players like Rainy Kim and Maple Moon were more gentle and suggested searching for the truth.

Sylvia clenched her teeth tightly and tried her best to show a fierce face, but her body was still shivering. She had no power to resist and could only wait for her fate to be decided by someone else.

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and stared at her as he contemplated.

He had many ways to deal with this; killing was the simplest one. As long as he pulled the trigger on Sylvia, who was acting tough but shivering in fear, the players in the future would lose thousands of parodies, making her journey end on his hand before it even started. He had a reason to do so. He was just killing an enemy, so no one could say that there was anything wrong with that.

With the blood of countless people on his hands, Han Xiao did not care for one more future known character.

However, he was not a bloodthirsty person. To him, killing was just a method; benefits were his real goal.

The question that was on his mind was if he could get more benefits from Sylvia and whether killing her or not killing her was more beneficial.

It did not matter whether Sylvia would be good or evil in the future; the Great Mechanic Han only needed someone with value, just like that crazy woman Hila. No wait, he saved Aurora, so Hila was not crazy. But in the storyline in his previous life, Hila wiped out entire planets of lives, so it would not be an overstatement to call her extremely wicked. Her power was what Han Xiao paid attention to, not her personality, beauty, or things like that.

There were many types of enemies. Archenemies that could not be negotiated with such as the Germinal Organization and DarkStar, competitors that could be friend or foe, enemies from misunderstandings, and so on. The way he saw it, Sylvia was an enemy born from a misunderstanding, and Han Xiao knew what misunderstanding it was.

Langley was a criminal rebel, but as a father, he had definitely hidden something from his daughter or even lied to her, finding excuses for his actions. Therefore, Sylvia thought that her father's actions were fighting against a tyrant and that he was saving his people.

According to the experience from his previous life, Sylvia was quite righteous—she was just blinded by hatred and lies. If she knew what kind of person her father was, she might give up on her revenge as she did in Han Xiao's previous life. Han Xiao had known the truth since long ago, and he knew how to quickly change Sylvia's perspective. To him, those were just small deeds... but this was not the key.

The key was, what benefit could he get from doing that?

Hmm... maybe a certain mission can be triggered. Since there are some rewards, she still has some value. That shall be it then, keep her alive temporarily and complete the mission first, then deal with it depending on the situation. If she still is hostile... then I shall bury her.

Release her? That was completely impossible.

From the perspective of a businessman, Sylvia was not just a person but a resource that had value. His assets were not so large to the extent that he could throw away money on the streets and waste resources.

Upon having these thoughts, Han Xiao stood up and said, "Pack up and prepare to leave. Knock her out and lock her up."

Sylvia's tiny face was filled with shock. She looked up and said, "Where are you taking me?"

"To see your father," Han Xiao said coldly.

Sylvia's eyes widened instantly; she could not believe it.

Chapter 435: Father (2)

Agolo Prison City was an enormous fortress made of steel located in the Agolo Alliance Garrison Planet, one of the seven planets under the New Phylen Alliance. It was used to imprison political criminals, war criminals, treason criminals, and other criminals from the members of the alliance. Sylvia's father, Langley, was imprisoned here.

The New Phylen Alliance was a small civilization alliance in the Rain Star System of the Colton Star Cluster in the Shattered Star Ring. In the sea of planets, there were countless political alliances like this. Usually, a civilization alliance only existed within a certain area. Most of them were formed when one civilization in the area decided to develop peacefully, hence forming an alliance.

The New Phylen Alliance had eight members, all small galactic civilizations in between planet level and star system level. These civilizations had once been nations on the same planet called Phylen. After Planet Phylen's technology reached a level that allowed them to enter space, these nations could not come to an agreement. Since there were disputes, they decided to split up peacefully. There were so many resources in the universe waiting to be discovered, so there was no need to be inflexible. Therefore, the strongest nation stayed on their mother planet, and the other nations took migration spaceships and migrated to other planets. In the end, they all developed into different civilizations.

In terms of fundamentals, these civilizations all had the same roots. Their technology and culture were very similar. Hence, after many years of separation, they came together once again, forming the New Phylen Alliance. This was the strongest force in the Rain Star System.

In Han Xiao's previous life, there were discussions about implementing a similar system on Earth. Since Earth could not be united, maybe this was a good idea. Of course, this was very idealistic, and problems regarding limited resources were always complicated. Furthermore, it was still unknown whether Earth could even develop to a point where they could enter outer space. Fortunately, the Great Mechanic Han did not have to care about this problem anymore.

Langley had originally been a high ranked army officer of a nation, almost a warlock that had a land of his own. His life was good, and he was paid handsomely too. However, one day, he suddenly used his influence to provoke the army, recruiting quite a number of people in secret and gathering a group of rebels, looking like they wanted to form a nation on their own. He called it an uprising, but in reality, they were doing immoral things. They built a very firm stronghold and fought with their old superiors for many years. In the end, they were demolished by a group of galactic mercenaries who fell from the sky and penetrated straight into their headquarters. The Black Star Mercenary Group was one of these mercenaries that accepted the hiring invitation from Purple Gold Army. There was a total of seven mercenary groups that worked together to complete this mission.

This time, Han Xiao was piloting Rainbow Conch spaceship and arrived at New Phylen Alliance's territory. He had sent a request earlier, and the alliance always welcomed mercenaries who had worked with them before. Thus, they agreed to his request of questioning the prisoner.

The spaceship landed on the pier of Agolo Alliance Garrison Planet, took the land transport, and headed toward Prison City. Han Xiao only brought a few people along for this trip—Aroshia, the tied-up Sylvia, and a few players including Bun-Hit-Dog. The rest were waiting on the spaceship. This trip was just to let Sylvia see her father, so there was no need to bring a lot of people.

"Wh—why are you doing this?"

In the stably moving Hovering Battle Vehicle, Sylvia was feeling complicated. A few days ago, when she failed the assassination, she had thought that she was going to die for sure. But to her disbelief, not only did Han Xiao not kill her, he even brought her to see her father. In the rare times that she was awake along the journey, she had been questioning if this was a dream. Without approval from the alliance, she would never be able to enter the heavily guarded Agolo Prison City. She had thought that she would never see her father again. Sylvia could not understand why Han Xiao was helping her.

"To let you know that your hatred is meaningless and how unworthy it is for you to give your life for him. Also, to let your father know about your death. I really want to see his expression when he realizes that his lies killed his own daughter. Killing people and destroying their spirit is my favorite."

Han Xiao shrugged. He could not be bothered with Sylvia's furious expression and opened up the interface.

After he let Sylvia live, a new mission [Lies] was triggered. Its requirement was to let Sylvia know the so-called 'truth'. The reward was not too bad, 540,000 experience. There was no need to search for the truth—he just had to ask her father.

In Sylvia's character background in Han Xiao's previous life, her father was blasted into pieces by the mercenaries, but now, he had been captured alive by Han Xiao. That hiring mission had given a greater reward for capturing him alive, so he had let Langley live, which made things much easier now.

Agolo Prison City was enormous and magnificent. There was a lot of guards, and many snipers were positioned at high locations. The searchlight illuminated the night and made it look like the day. They entered the prison successfully, and a warden came to welcome them.

"Black Star, I've heard a lot about you." This warden had a beard and was very straight forward. He shook Han Xiao's hand firmly and laughed passionately. "My friend Barny serves in the 37th Field Army. He took part in the Langley Stronghold Eradication Operation and fought alongside the mercenaries. He witnessed how powerful you are and always mentions you to me. I'm stuck in this silent Prison City every day, and finally, I'm meeting someone as renowned as you."

"You're too kind." Han Xiao maintained a slight smile and chatted casually as they followed the warden forward.

Very soon, they stopped before the metal gate of a single-person cell.

The distance was only one door away; Sylvia was very excited and almost wanted to immediately rush in to see her father. However, Han Xiao grabbed her shoulder, making her unable to move. "Mr. Warden, I want to see Langley alone first."

"No problem." The warden nodded.

"What do you want to do with my father‽"

Sylvia was like an angry kitten with flames in her eyes. She bit down with all her might on Han Xiao's hand, but not only was she unable to hurt Han Xiao, she was giddy from the shock deflected by Han Xiao's arm. A '-13' deflected damage appeared above her head, while the word 'Immune' appeared above Han Xiao.

"What do I want to do to him? That's a good question. I don't want him to look so good when he sees you, best to have lost an eyeball or an ear."

Han Xiao curled his lips and walked into the cell alone. The metal gate closed after him and blocked Sylvia's furious screams.

The light in the room was very dim. The cell was divided into two areas by a cage heated by electricity, and inside the cage was the actual cell. Langley leaned on the black wall covered in moss and dirt. There was stubble all over his face, and his eyes had no focus. He was much older and more decrepit than before.

When Langley heard a sound, he thought it was the guard, so he turned and looked over subconsciously, but what he saw was his nightmare that he could never forget. His expression became terrified, and he jumped up instantly. "It's you! Why are you here‽"

"You're very afraid of me?" Han Xiao walked to the cage with an expressionless face. "Shouldn't you thank me? If it was the other mercenaries that got to you, they wouldn't even have wasted their energy to pick up your corpse. Do you think you would be standing here with your full body like you are right now?"

Although there was a cage between them, Langley did not feel safe at all. He moved back hastily, and his back bumped into the wall. He swallowed his saliva anxiously, and the pain in his knees was becoming stronger. He could still vividly remember what happened—a group of armored mercenaries fell from the sky, killed his army like cutting through vegetables, and advanced into the heart of his stronghold. The mercenary that stood before him now waved his hands and summoned around a hundred cannons in an instant. At least a thousand people were killed by this person alone. He slaughtered his way through, marched up to him, and fired two bullets through his knees—that pain was almost suffocating.

Langley still had to depend on the nerves implanted into his knees to stand up.

"Cut the nonsense, I'm here for you," Han Xiao said coldly. "Your daughter Sylvia. I don't know what lies you told her, but she believed whatever bullsh*t you said and feels that you're a great man and a liberator of the people. She wanted to avenge you and tried to assassinate me..."

"What!"

Langley face changed instantly. He pounced at the railings and grabbed onto the heated cage, not caring about the high temperature burning through his hands and the burnt smell that came out of it. His face could almost touch Han Xiao's face, filled with anxiety and rage.

"Wha—what did you do to her‽"

"What else?" Han Xiao let out a sigh and said, "Of course I killed her. I shot her from below her jaw through his head, opening a hole at the back of her head. Her brain juice and blood splashed all over the wall. One of my subordinates thought she's quite pretty, so he's planning to skin her face and make it into a specimen for display."

Langley almost fainted. His daughter was his only motivation for staying alive. His expression became twisted, as rage, regret, heartache, desperation, and hatred flashed past one after another. He growled like a beast approaching its death, and even his fear of Han Xiao was completely forgotten.

"I will kill you! I will definitely kill you!!!"

Han Xiao looked at the furious Langley calmly, and when his throat became hoarse from the screaming and could only stare at him while breathing heavily, Han Xiao said slowly, "Okay, enough jokes. Your daughter is outside the gate. I captured her. I brought her here just to see you."

Langley froze and could not react to it. He felt extremely weak from the emotional rollercoaster. He collapsed onto the floor, pointed his trembling finger at Han Xiao, but could not speak a word.

Han Xiao squatted, looked Langley in the eye, and said, "You're a smart person. Whether I kill your daughter or not depends on you."

Langley's expression changed many times. He lowered his head and kept silent.

"Speak, I don't have the patience to wait for you to consider." Han Xiao knocked the metal cage impatiently.

"I'm not a good person... but you're eviler than me." Langley's eyes were filled with complicated emotions. He said with a hoarse voice, "I will do it. I will tell her everything about me. I was a high-level spy for another force from the start. I was controlled by someone else, and everything I did was to overturn the rules built by the New Phylen Alliance. I will tell her that I have been lying to her. I'm not who she thinks I am. I'm just a despicable traitor, an evil man who destroyed thousands of families for his own benefit. I will destroy the image she has for me and make her feel... completely disappointed... in me, her father..."

"You know what to do." Han Xiao stood up.

Langley looked at Han Xiao and said, "This way, will you let my daughter go?"

Han Xiao did not bother to reply, he turned to walk toward the door and left him with one last reminder. "Anyway, if I do not like the result after the conversation, I will make what I said earlier a reality... This is the one and only chance I'm giving you."

He opened the door and left the cell. He immediately saw Sylvia's anxious face. She was staring at him with rage but could not control herself from glancing at the gap of the door.

"Go in, you have ten minutes."

Han Xiao waved his hand and told Aroshia to let Sylvia go. Sylvia rushed into the cell and could not wait to see her father.

After closing the door, the warden turned on the surveillance footage and monitored Sylvia's conversation with Langley. Sylvia's change in her expression could be clearly seen.

She turned from anxious to stunned, then shocked, then there was an intense argument. They could even faintly hear Sylvia's out of control howling through the thick metal door. In the end, tears gushed out from her eyes.

[Lies] completed.

You have received 540,000 Experience.

"It's ten minutes."

The warden opened the gate and brought Sylvia out.

She looked like she had lost her soul. Her eyes were out of focus, and there were still tear marks on her face. She lost all motivations and was like a walking corpse. Her energy from ten minutes ago was nowhere to be found. The strong belief that she had been holding onto had collapsed.

Only then did she know that the great image of her father in her heart was completely built from lies. She had been lied to for more than ten years. He was not a great man; everything he did was despicable, and he deserved every bit of suffering that he had now. Even without the mercenaries interfering, he would have been defeated by the army sooner or later. If not for Black Star, her father would not even have been alive.

Her world had collapsed. The warm and bright childhood images in her memories all felt different.

Everything was a lie!

She felt like her heart was being penetrated by a thousand bullets.

She could not even digest this information in a short time. Her vision started spinning, and all the sound became distant and faint like she was isolated from the world.

Plop.

Sylvia collapsed onto the ground and fainted.

Through the slowly closing gap of the door, Han Xiao looked at Langley for the last time.

This rebel leader looked like he was decades older, but his face was very calm. It even had a tint of... relief.

Han Xiao shook his head, grabbed Sylvia by her back collar, and placed this kid over his shoulder like a sack.

"Congratulations on growing up."

Chapter 436: The Start of Ten Years

Han Xiao and the others arrived at the resting lounge. The warden left after saying a few words, leaving Han Xiao and the others in the room.

The mission is completed. Next, I need to deal with her.

Han Xiao tossed Sylvia onto a chair. He looked at the fainted teenage girl and contemplated.

I made Sylvia hear about what her father has done. With reference to what happened in my previous life, she should change... but it's not certain. Firstly, in my previous life, she only knew the truth after battling for many years; she was older and more mature, so she could adjust better. For now, she's just a kid. Maybe she'll still hate me or avoid it temporarily. Secondly, Langley died a long time ago in my previous life, but now he's still alive, and this will impact her in an unknown way. It's probably beneficial.

After some pondering, Han Xiao decided to make a decision after seeing Sylvia's reaction.

From his perspective, it was definitely better to make Sylvia stay. An NPC resource delivered to his doorstep, there was no reason for him to let it go. He even thought of going through the history of the mercenary group to see if there were more chances like this.

Han Xiao was just about to slap Sylvia awake, but suddenly, he remembered that Bun-Hit-Dog was beside him, so he did not do it. Han Xiao took two steps back, turned his head, and told Aroshia, "Wake her up."

Aroshia walked forward and slapped Sylvia on her face. Sylvia woke slowly.

"Hmm... My face is so numb."

Sylvia opened her eyes. She could feel numbness on her face, and it hurt a little.

She looked around, and the moment that she saw Han Xiao, she was about the turn angry subconsciously when she suddenly recalled what had happened before she fainted, and her rage disappeared. Instead, her mood plummeted. She looked down at her toes, her face filled with gloom.

She had thought that her father was great, but the reality was, Langley was a traitor. Even without Black Star, her father would have been defeated by the other mercenaries sooner or later. Furthermore, her father only lived because Han Xiao held back, so her hostility toward Han Xiao vanished.

If the person that she was going to avenge was a traitor, even if that person was her father, she still felt that what she did would be wrong. Langley caused his own suffering, so there was nothing that she could avenge.

The glorious image of her father in her heart collapsed. Sylvia's feelings toward Langley became complicated and conflicted. She believed that her father's love toward her was true, but everything that he did was beyond her acceptable range. Her father had been lying to her all along. Of course, she despised him for it.

The doubt of Han Xiao forcing her father to say those things only existed for a split second because Han Xiao did it way too obviously and confidently without any disguise. She knew that it was impossible with just a little thought. After all, she was just a small girl that failed to assassinate him—why would the captain of a renowned mercenary group go through so much effort to lie to her? Han Xiao had captured Langley with his own hands. If he did not know her father's real identity, why would he suddenly take her to question her father herself? Furthermore, her father had given a lot of details on the crimes that he had committed, and they were all real.

Maybe when she investigated back then, she had still held some hope in her heart and felt that those suspicions were all lies. Now that the source of these things had described those crimes in detail, all her fantasies were shattered.

Sylvia looked at Han Xiao with very complicated feelings. Although this mercenary group captain had been scaring her all along, his actions had truly helped her. After her father was captured, she had experienced both coldness and warmth between people. She did not know how to react to this kindness from a stranger, and she felt guilty.

When the flames of rage that burnt her senses away had extinguished, she finally spoke from her heart.

"Thank you. You're a good person... And... I'm sorry, really sorry..."

Han Xiao raised his eyebrows.

Looks like the heart modifying operation was a success.

"Our captain is known as the Women Loving Mechanic Han, what did you think?" Bun-Hit-Dog laughed with his hands on his waist.

Han Xiao acted as if he did not hear it and sized Sylvia up.

This girl was not grumpy anymore; she looked quiet and pretty. Although she was a mess after being captured for so many days, the dust on her face could not cover how pretty she was. As one of the most popular targets in the parody industry in his previous life, he could already foresee Sylvia growing up to be beautiful.

"I don't want to bother about anything else for now. Tell me, which organization helped you to know my whereabouts?" Han Xiao asked with a deep voice.

Sylvia did not hide anymore and spoke the truth.

"It's an intel selling organization called 'Mytar'. I used a part of my savings and told them to be mindful of your whereabouts, then bought this intel from them. The shapeshifting Esper that I hired is a freelance killer. He and I designed the assassination plan together. The poison gas and poison all belonged to him, but you have already killed him..."

Sylvia paused. She suddenly realized that Han Xiao had killed another person but not her.

Was it because he knew her?

Then she asked the question that she had been wanting to ask all along. "How did you recognize me? Did my father tell you?"

"Coincidence."

Han Xiao gave a perfunctory response and pondered about that intel organization called Mytar.

Intel organizations were usually neutral. If the customer requested intel about someone or some organization that they could not mess with, they would refuse to sell. Not messing with people who were too strong was an unspoken rule for intel organizations.

Clearly, he was not on that list in the eyes of these intel organizations, unlike his boss Ames, who really could not be messed with.

Honestly, Han Xiao did not like the feeling of exposing his whereabouts, but he did not have a solution for it temporarily. This was an unavoidable situation. In order to solve it, he could only become stronger. Whether it was strength, influence, or fame, as long as he could make the intel organization feel that he could not be messed with, they would not sell his intel.

Looks like I need to keep working hard. Han Xiao placed this matter in his heart, narrowed his eyes, and asked, "What is your plan?"

Sylvia shook her head and looked lost.

She did not know where to go after suddenly losing her goal. The Galaxy was so wide, yet she had nowhere to go.

"Father, he... although he's not a good person, he told me the truth. Maybe it's because he doesn't want to drag me down and does not want me to neglect myself because of him. He wants me to have my own life..."

After calming down, Sylvia sort of understood that her father did what he did to save her, or why would he destroy the image that he had been building in her daughter's heart for so many years? Although she was still bothered by it, she had no other choice but to accept reality. She said softly, "The universe is so vast. I will probably go look at different places... hoping to find something else I can be determined on..."

"You want to leave?" Han Xiao said with an expressionless face. "Did I allow you to leave?"

Sylvia froze.

"The first rule of mercenaries, all jobs have to be paid. Our help was not free. Furthermore, do you think I'm going to let go of the fact that you tried to assassinate me? I'm in a good mood, so I don't want to kill you, but that doesn't mean you don't have to pay a price. You have to compensate for all my damages." Han Xiao crossed his arms and snorted.

"I—I have no money now," Sylvia said embarrassedly and fidgeted uncomfortably. She had spent all her savings on this assassination, and those were the funds that Langley had left her. She truly had no money at all.

"No money?" Han Xiao was expressionless. "Then you shall repay me with your body."

Sylvia's eyes widened instantly. She blushed and stuttered, "Yo—You... I—I'm just a kid. I—I ca—can't..."

The players were all shocked and looked at Han Xiao in disbelief.

Holy, I didn't know you are this kind of Black Phantom!

We're the same type of people!

Bun-Hit-Dog recorded it with glee. He was very satisfied; this was way too explosive!

Aroshia tilted her head and mumbled, "This should be the humans' action of sending a mating signal."

Han Xiao almost could not keep a straight face after hearing what Aroshia said. He narrowed his eyes and said, "What are you people thinking? I have no interest in your body; I want your freedom."

Sylvia immediately breathed a sigh of relief. She looked at Han Xiao apprehensively. "Freedom? What do you mean?"

"You have to work for me for ten years."

"Ten is too long. Can you make it a little bit shorter?" Sylvia made the hand sign of 'a little bit' as she spoke with a fawning tone.

"Twelve years."

"No no no, ten years is good." Sylvia hastily waved her hands.

"In these ten years, you'll be my subordinate. If you want to escape or betray me, I won't give you a second chance. Maybe you can escape, but your father has nowhere to run," Han Xiao said coldly.

Hearing the threat, Sylvia's face became serious for a second. She wanted to be angry but felt powerless to do so. With her emotions in turmoil, she lowered her head and said softly, "I won't run from my own mistakes. It's just ten years. I'm still young, so I can afford it... I don't have anywhere else to go now anyway."

Since Han Xiao had chosen to let Sylvia live, he definitely had to make use of her value and create more profit than killing her would. Sylvia was at least a grade A Super at her peak in his previous life, so she was quite a good potential stock. By recruiting her, he could consider it as having another high-quality officer. Furthermore, she was talented in the Mechanic class, which suited his abilities. She could become his assistant. Although she needed time to grow, it was worth the investment.

Han Xiao wanted mature grade A Supers too, but tricking someone with a higher grade was way too difficult. There were not that many people who were as easy to trick as Herlous, and even tricking Herlous had not been that easy.

According to Sylvia's personality in his previous life, although she was sometimes extreme, she could be considered as normal after giving up on vengeance. Now, this process had been completed many years in advance, which could only be for the better.

Furthermore, no matter what, Sylvia was a popular character. This could indirectly increase the popularity of his faction among the players, giving his faction more 'fame'.

After she joined him, her galactic pirate career would no longer occur. However, she had the fundamentals after all. As long as she was tuned properly, her flavor would definitely not be worse than the previous life...

For the possibility of not being able to control her in the future, the Great Mechanic Han was not worried at all. Not because he was arrogant, but even the players' growth speed could not match his. If he did not have this tiny bit of confidence, he might as well go back to Planet Aquamarine and open a pig farm.

Chapter 437: Conclusion of the Pro League

Han Xiao and the others returned to the spaceship. Sylvia was clearly not used to her new identity and looked cautious. Han Xiao told the Volga brothers to teach her the basic knowledge, and he was pulled aside by Herlous.

"You let her join our team?" Herlous asked in surprise.

Han Xiao described the process briefly and gave Herlous a look. "You got a problem?"

"No, I don't have a problem with a little girl, but she can't fight—how can she become a mercenary?"

"She's talented. She won't be worse than you with some training."

Herlous' mouth twitched. "Comparing me with a small girl... I feel like you're shaming me."

"Hehe, you're overthinking it. I'll only shame you during training."

Han Xiao joked around. He turned and looked at Sylvia. She was surrounded by the players, who were trying to start a conversation with her, and did not know what to do. This was Black Star's traditional welcome ceremony.

In Han Xiao's previous life, Sylvia had joined and left many organizations to acquire Super knowledges, showcasing her potential. Since now she had joined his faction, Han Xiao was naturally going to pass on his knowledges to her if he wanted her to be of some use. According to the path that she took in her previous life, she was most suitable for the Mechanic Class. Han Xiao rubbed his chain and decided to personally tune... train her.

At that time, Floating Dragon Island was also in the Rain Star System. Han Xiao set the auto navigation of the spaceship, left the New Phylen Alliance, and arrived at Floating Dragon Island to handover the supplies.

Although Dekker had been threatened, he had been involved in the assassination. Tyrell was furious when he found out and fired Dekker on the spot. Even if Dekker had his reasons, Tyrell did not want to use someone that had damaged the profit of the organization.

After this, Tyrell expressed his sincere apologies. Han Xiao would never give up on an opportunity to gain profit. The compensation that he demanded this time was a higher discount, which Tyrell agreed to instantly. He was different from the travel agency that Rainbow Conch belonged to—his business partnership with Floating Dragon was much tighter so things were easier.

Speaking of the travel agency, a group of lizardmen went to Floating Dragon to retrieve the spaceship. On the docks, the travel agency's team had already arrived. They sent compensation to Han Xiao's account and retrieved Rainbow Conch after all the goods were unloaded. Han Xiao watched as those people left with the spaceship. He shook his head, took out his Galactic Communicator, and was going to call for a spaceship.

This time, Floating Dragon's Guard Captain Wilsander came and said with a light-hearted tone, "I heard someone tried to assassinate you."

"Just kid's play." Han Xiao glanced at him. "Are you interested?"

"Of course. I have to stay on this island every day to maintain order. Do you think my life is very interesting?" Wilsander said bitterly.

After chatting awhile, Han Xiao sent Wilsander away and went aside alone. He opened the forums and paid attention to the competition. After the incident with Sylvia, the Pro League had finally ended. The discussion on the forums was lively and passionate. He looked through the competition process roughly.

In the battle between the top four teams, Dynasty defeated Hydra 3:2, advancing to the finals. On the other side, Tulips won against Devil. In the champion deciding match between Dynasty and Tulips, the popularity and broadcast rating went above the roof. Han Xiao did not watch the videos, but according to the content in these discussion posts, the matches seemed to be very interesting and close. They fought back and forth time after time, performing at the highest level of pro players, bringing a feast to the viewers' eyes.

Sadly, in the end, during the match point when the score was 2:2, Dynasty made a small mistake, and Tulips caught that opportunity. Using that momentum, they won the match. Dynasty lost the match. Tulips were horrifyingly steady. When fighting against them, any small flaw or mistake would be taken advantage of and turned into the key of turning the tables.

As the final result was decided, the first season Pro League ended. Tulips was the champion, Dynasty was the runner up, and the other two top-four teams were Devil and Hydra. In the Singles, the champion was a German player who showcased how terrifyingly accurate and precise the Germans were. King Admiral was in the top four. Of all the China players, King Admiral's result in the Pro League was the highest—it was top-notch in the entire world. As the top one player in China for many years, this result undoubtedly made his position even firmer.

On the forums, spectators from all the nations discussed their nation's teams. Although Dynasty did not win the championship, the Chinese players were still very joyful. At least they were the runners-up, which was better than most of the teams. The first Pro League season was very encouraging. Even some foreign spectators became fans after seeing the Chinese teams' performance.

Compared to the ranking in his previous life, the results this time were way better. In his previous life, China only had one place in the top eight, and now there were two teams in the top eight. There was an improvement in the Singles as well. In Han Xiao's previous life, King Admiral was the only Chinese contestant that made it to top sixteen, but now there was also Frenzied Sword. They had brought pride to their nation.

The noticeable improvement in the results as compared to the previous life was only because of the Great Mechanic Han.

The players who followed him came back with good results, so his influence would be increased indirectly as well. His potential market had expanded, so Han Xiao was satisfied with the performance of the players.

With this result, Dynasty was overjoyed. Even Second Prince, who usually complained all the time, had a content smile on his face. He surprisingly did not degrade his captain. Long Sky's ranking was not bad either, but Hao Tian was not satisfied with that; his attitude for continuous improvements never changed. Frenzied Sword was in the top sixteen in Singles and was satisfied as well. This was a result that he had never even dared to imagine before. Most of the Chinese players were satisfied with what they had achieved. Temple of God was a little jealous of Dynasty and Long Sky's results. In comparison, Temple of God's performance in the first season looked bleak.

After the league ended, all sorts of shows started one after another. The shows reported and discussed the Pro League, the teams hosted press conferences, and there was also the awards ceremony. However, none of that was what Han Xiao focused on. The first season's ending meant that... the version update was going to arrive.

The last version update was three years ago. To Planet Aquamarine, the players that suddenly appeared sparkled waves of terror. During the update from Version 1.0 to Version 2.0, the players would disappear once again.

Normally, six days in in-game time was equivalent to one day in the players' 'real' time. The flow of time was constant, but when there was a version update, the connection between their time would be cut off. In the Version 1.0 update, the time passed in-game was one year. To players, it was only about two to three days.

Every version update's time skip was different; the players would enter Galaxy at different times. Usually, the versions were all large events or disasters.

During the version update, these players will not be here. Without these 'immortal' and convenient players, I will have to be more cautious with my actions. Furthermore, there aren't any methods to quickly earn experience or money in the one-year period. Hence, it will be better for me to dig up those missions with high potential. The details need to be planned...

Chapter 438: Goddess of Luck

The main members of the mercenary group were temporarily the players. When they disappeared, the team that he could command was only the Sunil Division. There were too few NPCs.

While the players are away, the income of the mercenary group will decrease. I can halt our operations temporarily and make time to recruit more people. When Version 2.0 starts, the Mutation Disaster will break out. The players on Planet Aquamarine will start to connect to the galaxy. During the version update, I'll have time to make preparations.

He had only brought along fifty players for now, and they had already made a huge profit for him. Version 2.0 was the time where his profit would rocket through the sky. The players were mountains full of green leeks—he would not even be able to harvest all of them before they grew again. Just thinking about it made the Great Mechanic Han look forward to the profit that he was going to make.

His target was the tens of thousands of players. He wanted to make Black Star Mercenary Group a guiding faction for the players to enter space. Of course, it was easier said than done. He had hidden competitors—Godora and DarkStar.

These two forces would use planets as battlefields to fight each other, and the players would then choose a faction in this situation. Han Xiao would be snatching meat from the mouth of a tiger by interfering.

However, he also had some obvious advantages. These two sides would be focusing on fighting with each other, so he was the only one that would focus on the players. Plus, the impact and sense of belonging that he had built through Bun-Hit-Dog's shows, as well as his position in the hearts of the players, would attract them to him.

The more players that he recruited, the better. Therefore, he had to make abundant preparations. First was benefits such as equipment missions, rewards, and so on, enhancing his power and strength. Second was measures for the Mutation Disaster. The former was targeted at the players; the latter was targeted at the main storyline.

I have more than 800,000 Enas, enough to buy two advanced knowledges and complete the class advancement mission. However, I'm now at level 95, and there'll be a promotion mission at level 100, meaning I can only increase my level by five after spending all my money. It's best to first get a subclass, reach level 100, and look at the promotion mission. If it can't be completed in a short time, there's no hurry to spend this 800,000, and I can save it as funds. I have about 1.5 billion experience, which is not enough to level up to 120 straight away. Plus, I still need to leave some experience to gamble blueprints and upgrade abilities.

Since there would be no players for him to harvest in the next year, Han Xiao had to be more calculating. The promotion at level 100 was the second chance of race evolution. He had received Void Genes from the Void Dragon Bone Marrow, which would largely affect his race evolution choices, so he was quite looking forward to promotion.

Subclasses are easy to find, but the rare ones are rather troublesome...

Han Xiao searched his memories. These rare subclasses could usually only be acquired after very complex processes. The difficult ones were too time-consuming, but the easier ones were not suitable for the Mechanic class. Subclasses were just an add-on for him; he did not need them to be rare, but they had to be suitable for the Mechanic class.

Since that's the case, attribute classes are not a bad choice. Luckily, I can get this class right in Juberly Hub. Although it's not rare, its effect is simple and straightforward.

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

...

After completing Floating Dragon's daily escorting missions, Han Xiao was summoned by Ames to her house, as usual, to ask him about the progress of looking for her teacher. He then took the others back to Juberly Hub to rest.

The pro players had just finished their competition and were exhausted, so they completely loved the idea. Doing missions in Hub City was much more relaxing, almost like having a holiday.

Obviously, Han Xiao did not do this to let them rest; it was mainly because it was almost the version update, so he wanted to use this opportunity to make one last push for profits.

Han Xiao was planning to sell some machinery that he did not need anymore to the players, as well as some elite machinery from time to time, then take one the enhancing and repairing services. For this, Han Xiao isolated himself for a few days to build more machinery. When there were so many players, no matter how quickly he could build the machinery, he would definitely not be able to meet the demands of all these players... unless he had assembly lines, but that was a plan for further in the future.

However, Han Xiao had a solution for this problem long ago—enhance the NPC resources of the faction, then use the connections with these NPCs to give the players opportunities to go to other places for missions and income. Sunil was one of the training bases that he had prepared for the players.

After selling things for a few days, Han Xiao took a flying disc carrier to the fifty-seventh floor of a tall building in the middle of the hub city. This place was an absolutely neutral agency called [Spacetime Research Council]. The name sounded very high-class, but it actually had nothing to do with spacetime. This was a scholar association for people to store their knowledge and discuss their findings. They had agencies in various Star Fields, and it was based on a membership structure, so it was very liberal.

The purpose of the Spacetime Research Council was to store the information and history of all the civilizations in the universe, similar to a knowledge base. Also, to provide a platform for the scholar members to exchange new research topics. This kind of organization, of course, was a public and neutral organization. The Arcane Church was the one that started it. The Arcane Church was the Universal Civilization that focused most on culture and knowledge. They had countless members across many Star Fields. Even the Federation of Light and Crimson Empire were among the executives of this association.

The inventory of the Spacetime Research Council included very practical knowledge, such as the technology, magic, and Super knowledges of different civilizations. Practical knowledge was more precious, and the sensitive parts would usually not be showcased to the outside world. This was a request from advanced civilizations as well. If someone wanted to browse that important information, they had to have higher authorization.

The only way to increase the faction relationship with this association was to donate unknown knowledge and literature, but to gain higher authorization was much more complicated. There was no clear path, and one had to wait for the executives to make the selection. Firstly, one had to attend all kinds of networking gatherings hosted by the association, suggest new understandings, and make one's existence more known, increasing one's position and reputation among then members.

When one's faction relationship was high enough, had been a member for long enough, had made actual contributions to the society, and did not have a criminal background, then there was a chance that the executives would make that person's authorization level higher. In conclusion, it was very complicated.

In his previous life, when the players started to pay attention to the Spacetime Research Council, it was already the later stages. Back then, the players had been looking for the highest-level knowledges for their classes, but these were extremely rare, and the research council had related information for them. This was one of the ways that one could obtain the highest-level class knowledges. However, it required a tremendous amount of time and energy, and there were no shortcuts. Anyway, Han Xiao did not have to worry about that for a very long time to come, and it was better to join this association earlier, so he might as well join now.

There was not any requirement to becoming a member; he just had to pay some money. Compared to the standard of the research council, the membership fee was really low, just 500 Enas.

Of course, at that moment, Han Xiao's target was only the subclass that could be acquired just by joining the research council, and that was what he wanted.

...

There were no twists and turns during the admission procedures—enter information, submit the form, pay the fee, tease the lady receptionist, and it was done. The entire process took less than ten minutes.

After walking out of the research council agency, Han Xiao opened his interface. He now had a new entry under his subclasses—[Scholar]!

He directly leveled it up to level five and reached the promotion criteria of level 100.

[Scholar] leveled up to LV5.

+10 INT.

You have received 1 Potential point.

One type of subclass was known as the 'attribute subclasses', such as this [Scholar]. Every time it leveled up, it would hugely increase an individual attribute, and there were no Free Attribute Points, only Potential Points.

Every level of [Scholar] provided an increase of ten Intelligence. The five levels that Han Xiao had just acquired gave him fifty Intelligence.

Intelligence was the core attribute of the Mechanic class as it was related to Machinery Affinity. Han Xiao currently had an ability called [Machinery Analytical Comprehension], which provided one percent Machinery Affinity for every ten points of Intelligence.

Han Xiao basically spent all his Free Attribute Points in Intelligence. He now had more than six hundred Intelligence, which was more than sixty percent increase in Machinery Affinity. This was a core ability, and Han Xiao knew that this was just one of the Mechanic abilities that were related to the Intelligence attribute. There were more class abilities in the later stages.

Furthermore, the subclass [Scholar] gave him another ability—[Research Theory]. Its effect was to increase his Intelligence by one for every three abilities that he possessed. It was extremely suitable for the Mechanic and Mage class. These two classes were known to have a ton of abilities, and the combat power of both was enhanced by Intelligence. Compared to the Mage class, which also needed the Mystic attribute, the Mechanic class received the most benefits from [Scholar]. The two of them were a perfect fit.

For the Mechanic class, every blueprint was considered as an ability. Han Xiao knew more than a hundred blueprints, so the level 5 [Scholar] alone gave him ninety INT.

Among all the subclasses that were easy to obtain at the moment, Han Xiao felt that the attribute subclasses were the most useful options.

Every player could easily obtain this kind of attribute subclasses—if they knew that it existed. Their effects were all very useful, and they also gave attribute abilities with growing potential that would still be useful even in the late stages. In his previous life, many top pro players would have one or two attribute subclasses.

The most impressive one was the attribute subclass that was related to the Luck attribute, which had a very clear and straightforward name—[Gambler]!

He still remembered [Gambler]'s ability effect—the things won through gambling and betting would increase the LUK attribute. The more one won, the more Luck attribute this ability gave, while losing would decrease it. It perfectly explained the name of this subclass and what the Luck attribute meant.

Actually, Han Xiao did want the [Gambler] subclass somewhat. After all, no matter how much his Luck decreased, it would only go from one to zero, which would have no impact at all, but if he won, he would benefit greatly!

After experiencing the clarity of mind given by leveling up, Han Xiao looked at his interface. Seeing the Promotion Mission for level 100 was his main goal.

With just one look, Han Xiao suddenly started to question life.

I should probably learn the [Gambler] subclass...

Chapter 439: Version 1.0 Update (1)

Your total level has reached 100. Complete the promotion mission to continue leveling up.

[Trail of the Strong]: Kill an enemy that's one grade above you.

Note: This mission can be completed with a team, but the team members cannot have a higher grade than you.

Progress: 0/1

God damn it... Han Xiao clenched his teeth. This promotion mission was not the most difficult one, but due to his grade, its difficulty multiplied many times.

He had met a similar promotion mission before when he was level 40. Its requirement was to kill three targets that were five levels above him. Compared to an entire grade, five levels was nothing.

I'm now at Grade B. Doesn't that mean I have to kill a Grade A enemy‽

Han Xiao's mouth twitched. If this mission appeared at a lower level, it would only have been a little challenging, but it became multiple times more difficult as the levels increased.

[Trial of the Strong] only appeared in Grade B to Grade E promotion missions. At Grade A, this mission would no longer appear. If he was Grade B+, the strength difference would not be that huge, but he was only level 100, and level 100 usually meant that one had the strength of lower to medium Grade B. However, it just so happened that this requirement appeared when he was at this level. It felt like the goddess of luck was kicking him in the face.

What did Grade A represent? It meant that the individual could cause a destructive disaster on an entire planet surface, had strength only below Grade S, and was more than enough to rule one place alone. Grade B was the backbone level power in the galaxy, while Grade A was the high-end power. The number of Grade Bs in the galaxy was tens of thousands of times greater than Grade As.

The strength difference was too vast!

Han Xiao sighed. The mission was already determined, so there was no use in being annoyed by it. He needed to get promoted one way or another, so he had no choice but to think of a way to fulfill the requirement.

The difference between Grade A Supers is large. If I want to complete the mission, I have to pick the weaker ones... but no matter how weak, Grade A is still much stronger than me. I will definitely lose if I fight head-on, so I have to plot. Luckily, there's no need to fight one on one, and there are no restrictions to how the mission can be completed.

Han Xiao contemplated.

First, I have to choose a target and search for an opportunity from what I remember. Then, I have to make a plan to weaken the enemy as much as possible before the battle, or it will be impossible to kill a Grade A at their peak.

Since the killing method was not limited, it meant that he just had to be the one killing the target. The most idealistic way, of course, was to kill a prisoner that was unable to resist. This might have worked at lower levels, but it was impossible at his level. Even if some organizations might have imprisoned Grade A prisoners, they would not kill them out of nowhere, and of course, they would not let anyone else kill them. Therefore, the only way to complete the mission was through battle.

This was like a hunt. The hunter had his eyes on strong prey, so he hid in the dark and waited for the prey to fall into the trap. It required a huge amount of patience.

It was impossible to complete the Promotion mission any time soon. Han Xiao was glad that he did not advance his class, or he would have been much more frustrated.

There are many targets, but none of them can be messed with easily. This needs a long-term plan...

When he returned to the stronghold, most of the players were not there. As the first competitive season had ended, there were many follow up activities. The time that those pro players spent online was obviously much less. Only Bun-Hit-Dog, Maple Moon, and a few other players maintained the same play time. However, they were not in the stronghold; they were outside, doing daily missions.

Han Xiao knocked on the doors of the others. Herlous, Aroshia, and the others had all gone out, so he was the only one home.

The enormous stronghold hall felt deserted.

Han Xiao looked at the time—time for dinner. He took out a bright silver colored alcoholic drink from the drawer and activated the portable food box. After one minute, a box of food covered in tinfoil was made, inside of which was some meat and beans with black sauce.

Han Xiao placed the food and drink on the table in the middle of the hall, sat down on the sofa, and ate slowly. Such simple food was his dinner.

After eating for a while, the stronghold door opened, and the officers returned together. Herlous walked at the front with a toothpick between his teeth and chatted with the three brothers of Volga. Sylvia carried many bags and clung to Aroshia, who was expressionless, talking non-stop. Aroshia's replies were never more than five words, yet Sylvia did not get tired of it. She had walked out of her negativity faster than Han Xiao expected. After all, her father was still alive, and things would only be treasured when they were lost. She understood her father's intention to want her to have a new life, so she did not want to keep being so negative.

Aroshia wore a new dress, and from what Han Xiao knew about her, it was most likely Sylvia who had chosen it.

When Han Xiao was doing his things, these officers went shopping and had dinner together, or Aroshia would have preferred to stay at home.

As soon as they entered, they saw Han Xiao sitting on the sofa eating a box of fast food.

Han Xiao looked up and glanced at them. "You're back."

They hastily wiped the smiles off their faces and nodded.

"Herlous, go check on the recent mission report of the Sunil Division. Volga brothers, remember to enchant the batch of machinery that I gave you. Aroshia, don't transform in the stronghold for the next two days, or it'll be very difficult to clean." Han Xiao put down the spoon, stood up, walked toward the machinery modification room, and said, "Sylvia, follow me."

Sylvia's face tightened, and she hurriedly followed behind Han Xiao into the machinery modification room. The door closed.

Han Xiao kicked away the waste parts on the floor, found a box, and sat down. He sized Sylvia up and did not speak.

Sylvia was very uncomfortable from being looked at. "May I know why you've called me here?"

Han Xiao tapped the table and said in a deep voice, "I wanted ten years from you. You're now my subordinate, not having a holiday. What use do you think you can provide me?"

"I don't know..." Sylvia lowered her head. She did not understand why Han Xiao wanted her to work for him for ten years. Clearly, she was just a child and could not help in any way.

"You're not of any use now, so in the days to come, I will teach you the knowledge of a Mechanic. Only when you're stronger will you be of use to me. If you refuse to learn and do not want to work for me, don't think I will allow you to laze around in my mercenary group. I don't need flops." Han Xiao was very direct.

"Yo—you want to teach me Super knowledges?" Sylvia froze and struggled to speak coherently. "I thought you just wanted a maid."

Han Xiao frowned and said, "What do I need a maid for? Can you do it better than the cleaning robots?"

Sylvia's eyes swayed and said with uncertainty, "I—I never thought of that. Super... can I really be one? I mean... do I have the talent?"

"My eyes can see a rough image of the future, and I saw potential in you," Han Xiao said calmly. "Langley never let you set foot in the areas of Supers, how foolish. Ever since you were born, the Super-Gene has been lurking in your body, waiting to be awakened. Your asshole father wasted many years."

"You can't call him an asshole," Sylvia said unhappily. "That's my father."

"I haven't lost my memories." Han Xiao raised his eyebrows. "He is accused of seventeen major crimes, including but not limited to betraya..."

"Okay, he is an asshole." Sylvia bit her lips. "But you can't call him that, only I can!"

"Stop talking nonsense and get back to business. I will let you awaken Magnetic Energy and teach you Mechanic knowledge."

Sylvia straightened her back uncontrollably. She felt like she was about to enter a new world. She looked forward to it, but she was understandably nervous.

"Then... what should I do?"

Han Xiao took out four thick, heavy books and stacked them up. Combined, the four books were about forty centimeters thick. Those four books were all basic machinery theories written by different people. The interface allowed him to not need to read them and study them, but for others, it was not that convenient.

It took months and years of learning to become a Mechanic. Even though Sylvia was very talented, this step could not be skipped.

"First, memorize these four books."

Sylvia's mouth opened widely as she looked at the thick books. This was very different from how she had thought it would be. "That's too much..."

Ignoring her suggestion, Han Xiao continued. "I'll give you ten days, after which, there'll be a test. If you fail, you'll have to memorize one more book. This will repeat until you pass."

Sylvia's face immediately turned dropped. She felt that even if she exhausted herself, she would not be able to memorize so much in just ten days. Furthermore, she had never come into contact with anything related to it. How was she going to even understand the content of those books?

"Anything you don't understand, ask me. When you pass the test, I will teach you the way to awaken Mechanical Force."

Han Xiao waved his hands. Sylvia had no choice but to walk out with a long face holding the books, quickly heading off to memorize these books.

Although Han Xiao did not have to study this way, the knowledge did exist in his brain, and he had gone through it before. Teaching someone else Mechanic class knowledge was certainly not a problem.

I wonder how long she needs to grow to a level where she can be of use.

Han Xiao shook his head.

This was what long-term investments were like; earning back the investment was not that quick. Luckily, patience was something that he was not short of at all.

The aftertaste of the league lingered, and players reveled in it. A few days after, an official update announcement suddenly appeared on the forums and instantly became the top post. The players were surprised once again. This was translated into many languages, and players from all areas could understand it. Within one minute, the number of replies had already exceeded ten thousand and was quickly growing.

In summary, the content of the announcement was that at midnight twelve days later, in game time, Version 1.0 update would officially end. At that time, all accounts would be unable to log in, so they suggested that players log out in advance to avoid unnecessary damage.

As for what was new in the update, nothing was mentioned at all. The players thought that it was very mysterious—the unknown new version made the players look forward to it even more.

The main storylines in the various novice planets were all completed, and popular characters in these planets had already showcased their charm and all had some fans. After the main storyline was completed, the players were in the stage of exploring freely and were still excited. Even the side missions had a lot of related storylines and felt very real. Compared to fighting monsters and beating levels, this was more like a journey full of experiences. Therefore, many players could not wait to find out what new storyline would unfold on their planet. They were interested in the fate of the planet and the people in it, as well as the look of the entire universe.

The unknown content of the next version sparked discussions and speculations from players on all planets. Many people guessed what would come next by referring to what had happened in Version 1.0, which was all recorded in the chronicle posts of the various planets that recorded the history.

When the main storyline ended in Version 1.0 across the areas, some players finally had the idea of posting such a post. This sparked interest from countless players, and the chronicles of these planets were born.

All the players came together to contribute, posting the missions, events, and characters that they had met, trying to record everything that had happened on the planet, regardless of whether they were main storylines or side missions. Even the most ordinary NPCs had been recorded by some players.

Everyone contributing to the same thing made the players have a lot of fun, and the sense of belonging was very strong.

This was the first batch of senior players and loyal players in Galaxy. In Han Xiao's previous life, even when some players could not play Galaxy anymore due to being busy or other reasons, they would still log in occasionally to see how the storyline had progressed. There were way too many things, so it was incomparably immersive and real. It felt both like a game and a drama series.

Not long after, Galaxy Times dedicated an episode to the unknown new version, analyzing the speculations.

Chapter 440: Version 1.0 Update (2)

"Hello players, this is Galaxy Times, dedicated to sharing first-hand game information. Your gaming career is our top priority."

The male and female host read the familiar opening line. The moment the show started, tens of thousands of viewers flooded in and started the usual comments began floating along the top of the video.

"Looking forward to the discussion of the version update."

"Galaxy Time rules."

"Spam the comments and cover the cold joke!"

The usual extremely awkward opening joke passed by quickly, and they got to the main topic.

"In a few days in game time, the Version 2.0 update will arrive," Male host said. "Galaxy will enter the storyline of the next version. In regard to this, we have obtained first-hand intel and some unproven information, which we will be filtering and sharing with the audience in this episode, speculating and analyzing what the next version will entail.

"So, before the analysis starts, let's first do a summary for the storylines across the various planets in this version. A very big part of our data comes from the planet chronicles, which the players arranged and added to. For this, we sincerely thank these players—this data has helped us a lot in our work."

The players felt joyful as they were mentioned.

Next, the two hosts summarized the storylines of the various novice planets. By this point, the main storyline of every planet had already ended, so they went through the storylines from head to toe, including the major events and characters involved. They also discussed and commented on various parts. Of course, it was not just them speaking—images and videos were also shown to aid the process.

Every time the history of a planet was mentioned, the players of that planet would be the most active ones. The Version 1.0 storylines of these planets were very diverse as well—Lord Singelase's incident on Planet Winterfrost, Arcane Tide on Planet Brighton, Dynasty Divergence on Planet Lasting Song, Shadow Group incident on Planet Summer, Chaos Expedition in Planet Sourne, and many more. These were all core main storylines, and there were also the side storylines. For example, in the case of Planet Aquamarine, the core storyline was the Six Nations and Germinal Organization, while the sub main storyline was Bennett's sanctuary construction.

Due to the different backgrounds of these planets, the feeling that their main storyline gave was also very different. Some were filled with technology; some were surrounded by magic; some were mysterious. The vast majority of players had not entered space, so they did not know where their planet was in the universe, but Han Xiao did. The novice planets were quite evenly spread among the Star Fields, and Planet Aquamarine was the only novice planet in Shattered Star Ring.

In all the core main storylines, the one on Planet Aquamarine ended the earliest, and it received the most attention. There was definitely a main character in these storylines that was very connected to the storyline. The two hosts continued their speech, and it was finally Planet Aquamarine's turn.

"Speaking of Planet Aquamarine's main storyline, we must mention someone no matter what. After the Planet Aquamarine storyline ended, he's still been active in the eyes of the players. He was the first to take players into space. I'm sure our regular viewers are familiar with his name..."

The comments rampaged. Maybe they did not know the storyline of other planets, but almost everyone knew Han Xiao. These fans had a common topic instantly.

"It's Black Star!"

"Is that 'Black Phantom' Han Xiao, Destroyer of the Germinal Organization, Sanctuary Owner, Interstellar Explorer, Prophet, Black Star Mercenary Group Captain, Supporter of Materialism, Manipulator of Loot Boxes?

"Black Star: You kids are talking behind my back again."

"Thirty Second True Men Group requests to battle!"

"Ahhh! I want the Dragon Emperor! I want Aroshia! I'm going to lick them to my last breath!"

"Go away, screen licking monsters!"

It was the Planet Aquamarine players' turn to be active. The density of the comments increased to another level. The Chinese players had leveled up the useful ability to spam comments to the max level.

The male host continued to read the script and explained Han Xiao's background briefly.

"Original name Han Xiao. Member of the Alumera family, almost killed during an accident but was captured by the Germinal Organization. The Germinal Organization made him into a test subject but failed the brainwashing. He disguised himself for a very long time, and in the end, he found the opportunity and escaped from the Germinal Organization's control.

"From then on, he acted against the Germinal Organization. He once joined Stardragon but left later and became a contract killer for the Dark Net, code name [Black Phantom]. The Germinal Organization chased after him for many years but only saw his shadow. He awakened some kind of foresight ability that allows him to obtain benefits as well as avoid danger.

"After a period of hiding, he started his revenge. He alone directed the Six Nations' expedition against the Germinal Organization. In this war, he infiltrated the Germinal Organization Headquarters and stole all their confidential intel, bringing the Six Nations' victory. He became a hero of Planet Aquamarine, but his journey did not end there.

"One day, he foresaw that a disaster is going to break out in Planet Aquamarine. So, he summoned a spaceship in some way and led the warriors that he had carefully selected and handpicked into the galaxy, looking for a solution...

"As before, most of our data comes from the chronicles provided by players."

The players searched for a lot of intel during the exploration times. Han Xiao's history had already been made public. In the things that had happened on Planet Aquamarine, Han Xiao was like a puppeteer behind doors, and many things were connected to him. In the chronicles, Han Xiao's name was mentioned countless times. This had led the new players to know what happened in the storyline before, continuing to increase Han Xiao's reputation.

The chronicles of Version 1.0 were enormous, but Han Xiao was still a bright star among all the storylines.

After the hosts finished talking about Planet Aquamarine, the summary of the Version 1.0 storyline had come to an end. The hosts started the next topic, which was the main theme of this episode—analyzing the new version.

"According to the intel we have, we have made a few deductions. First, in the new version, the players will definitely connect with the galaxy and be able to leave their original planet, starting to explore the universe.

"Second, other than the current thirteen novice planets, the new version will add more birth planets. Due to what we have mentioned, the new birth planets should be planets that allow the players to enter the galaxy directly. Therefore, we have made a daring guess that the difference between the new and the old novice planets is that players in the old planets will only be able to enter the galaxy after going through the new storyline, while players in the new planets can enter the galaxy directly. The price is that these players have to start with a new account, while the old planet players can continue to use their high-level account. Hence, old or new, they have their advantages.

"Third, although the new storyline of the planets is unknown, there will definitely be someone that will lead the players to the new storyline. The clues of the new storyline are definitely hidden in some characters. We suggest looking for clues from NPCs in order to guess who will lead the next version's storyline. What role will the main character of Version 1.0 play in the new version? The clues are limited in most planets, except for one—Planet Aquamarine!

"Before Black Star left, he left behind a frozen mission—[The Last Bastion]! The mission introduction is as follows.

"Someday in the future, a calamity will strike this world, and Sanctuary Three will become the last remaining bastion for humanity. Protect this dwindling flame from the encroaching darkness. Only then will there be hope to overcome this calamity.

"The mission requirement is to protect Sanctuary Three and make sure its destruction rate is not above fifty percent. So, we have reason to believe that this mission is a hint to what will happen to Planet Aquamarine in Version 2.0. There will be an unknown calamity, and the entire planet will be affected. Black Star will definitely play a role in this disaster..."

The reason that Han Xiao had left the frozen mission was exactly to give the players direction for imagination so that he could increase his fame. In his previous life, every time there was a version upgrade, there would definitely be a wave of speculation over the new versions. This was within his expectations.

In Planet Aquamarine, Sanctuary Three...

With the tall, metal walls and tight air defenses, the current sanctuary was fully complete like a huge fortress standing on a desolate land. Han Xiao had been gone for more than a year, and the current manager of the sanctuary was Huang Yu. He had constructed the sanctuary as planned and had already taken in more than three million refugees. Other than those who sought protection, there were also hundreds of thousands mobile inhabitants, the Inhumans.

Countless players took Sanctuary Three as the main city, not only because there were more than enough daily missions and rewards there, but also because the decisions that Han Xiao had made when he was there had developed the players' habit. After they developed a habit, the players liked to gather there and interact with each other.

The feeling of the residents toward the Inhumans was very conflicted. On one hand, the Inhumans like to help them do stuff; on the other hand, most people envied the Inhumans and saw them as outsiders, so there was always a sense of alienation. In the eyes of some residents, the square where the players gathered was very dangerous, and they did not dare get close.

The Inhumans had helped Bennett build many sanctuaries, but after that, most Inhumans returned to Sanctuary Three. Huang Yu could not understand why they did this, so he thought it had to be because of his boss. He felt that only Black Phantom would know the reason.

However, over the past few days, a huge number of Inhumans had migrated to the sanctuary from all areas without any warning. Huang Yu took this phenomenon very seriously.

In the sanctuary meeting room, Huang Yu asked his subordinate, "Have we found the reason?"

After he took control of the sanctuary, he had built a group of subordinates himself. The people here were all members of Dark Net and worked directly for Bennett.

"No. We gathered intel from all areas and still have yet to find out why the Inhumans have mass migrated. Currently, the number of Inhumans in Sanctuary Three has exceeded 800,000, and it's still growing."

"This is not a good sign." Huang Yu was very troubled. "Although most Inhumans are peaceful, there are destructive ones as well. We have already been attacked a few times in the past year. If these Inhumans have an ulterior motive, the damage that 800,000 Supers can cause is unimaginable. If not handled properly, the Sanctuary Three that took two years to build might be gone within a night."

Of course, there was no way for him to know that the reason that the players had gathered in Sanctuary Three was because of the speculation that Galaxy Times made from the mission that Han Xiao had left behind. Sanctuary Three would very likely be a key area in the upcoming main storyline, and there was a very high chance for it to be a safe area.

Therefore, most players had decided to go to the sanctuary before the update. This way, not only could they get into the main storyline as soon as the new version arrived, but they would be safer than those in other places.

"We have to prepare measures for this kind of hidden threat," Huang Yu said.

"But... the order that Black Phantom left was not to use any hostile strategy against the Inhumans and not try to control their freedom, except for those who cause trouble. We're going against his words by doing this."

Huang Yu shook his head. "I know, but we cannot not guard against the Inhuman because of that. Black Phantom has been gone for more than a year. If he was here, I would not worry about anything at all, but he's not. Therefore, we need to be flexible."

"Then what do you plan to do?"

"Split them," Huang Yu said with a deep voice. "Forbid some Inhumans from entering the sanctuary main city and chase them to the two guard cities nearby. Alumera and Black Pine are both fine. This way, even if a riot breaks out, it won't happen in the most important place."

They exchanged looks.

"That's my decision. Report this to the rulers of the two guard cities, and tell them to gather an army just in case. We'll start to split the Inhumans in three days," Huang Yu said firmly.

Suddenly, he felt very sleepy and yawned uncontrollably.

In the dark conference room of a certain DarkStar mothership that was in stealth mode, the display screens were giving off a dim light.

These people were the superiors of DarkStar. Every screen was showing a blurry outline of a person and no face—it was very mysterious. Even for Godora, who had been an enemy of DarkStar for many years, they only knew a few of the superiors. DarkStar was like a mysterious fog, always hidden in the darkness.

The middle screen was DarkStar's leader. It was blurry as well, and the voice also went through a mechanical voice changer.

"What stage have the Mutation Sources that we planted developed to?"

"Based on the time, the larval stage has passed. All Mutation Sources will enter the pupa stage, and the impacts have already been done. In an estimated time of around one year, the Mutation Source will enter the eruption stage. However, the time predicted is not too accurate. After all, we cannot control the thoughts of the Mutation Sources."

"Maintain the observation," DarkStar's leader said. "Godora has obtained a Mutation Source, and we don't know how much headway they have made in their research. The plan needs to be improved; we can't wait for the Mutation Sources to grow on their own. After the symptoms break out, we need to take action. The details will be discussed again. Anur, how's Ember?"

The last question was directed at Anur, one of the Grade A Supers in DarkStar, Ember's teacher.

A voice came out of the screen that represented Anur. "I made him focus on training his power, and it's going quite well. His strength has increased visibly. There's more than a twenty percent chance that he can enter Calamity Grade."

"Hmm. Rogue died in battle, and Vivira is imprisoned in Rainbow Prison, so we have an imminent need to add high grade combat power. Esper currently has the highest chance to reach Grade A, and his Esper power is very strong. Tell him I have high hopes for him... Meeting dismissed."

The screens turned black one after another. The dark room returned to dead silence.

Chapter 441: Version 1.0 Update (3)

In unknown chaos, the first beam of light pierced through the everlasting fog of darkness. The sense called 'vision' awoke the obscure consciousness. Through the 'eyes' of its 'body', vibrant colors shattered the world made of black and white. Everything was fresh and interesting.

Then, more information came. The noise, the cold air, and the pungent metal.

It insatiably wanted to feel more things, but it could only see through the eyes of this body. It tried to turn its head, but its body did not move as its mind commanded. It could only feel but not control.

It anxiously wanted to move but could not. It started crying silently like a baby, but no one could hear it.

An unknown amount of time had passed since it awoke. Through this body, it saw countless upright creatures come and go, carrying out activities that it could not understand.

I want... I want more...

After some time, the number of visions started to slowly increase.

Water fell onto the leaf and slowly rolled down it. It stared at the droplet, wondering why it did not tickle.

Roots dug into the soil, and the fertilizer brought a sense of satisfaction, like the feeling the upright creatures felt when consuming food.

Its nose sniffed, and its hypersensitive sense of smell drew out the prey's escape route.

More and more senses brought a raging stream of data. It greedily accepted everything.

Then, a new sense was born. It felt microorganisms like a running stream. To its surprise, it discovered that this was the first thing that it could control, like an obedient army.

Is this the sense that belongs to me?

No, it's not.

I am all; all is me.

...

In Sanctuary Three, ever since an officer breathed in some leaked paralyzing gas and ended up lying in bed for seventeen days and three hours, Emerald Grass' alchemy room was deemed a forbidden area.

Compared to when Han Xiao left, the size of the alchemy room was many times larger with more precise devices. Rows of colorful liquid drugs were placed on the shelves. On the table were transparent glass drawers with different plants inside, all original materials used to make drugs.

"Hmm..." Emerald Grass wore a white coat, anti-corrosion gloves, and a pair of glasses, humming and blending some kind of plant drug.

Her power to control plants allowed her to feel the plants, and thus accurately control the dose of drugs.

Sweeping aside her hair, she reached out, opened a drawer, and tore off a petal. As she was going to throw it into the device and use it as the raw material, her movements suddenly stopped.

Her power sensed something peeking, but it disappeared after a very short instant, almost like an illusion. Emerald Grass furrowed her brows slightly and looked toward the source of that feeling, but it was the plant that she had taken the petal from.

"Strange," Emerald Grass mumbled. She pondered and reached out to touch the plant again.

The instant her fingers touched the plant, a shiver passed through her Esper power sense like an electric current and stabbed her heart deeply.

Quickly pulling her hand away, Emerald Grass took a few steps back and looked at the plant with shock and suspicion.

"It's not an illusion... there's a very real sense of peeking when I touched it..."

If not for her power to observe the tiniest changes in plants, she would not have felt the change.

Disbelief flashed through her eyes.

"This plant, is it consciously sensing me?"

Emerald Grass suddenly thought of something. Her expression changed, and she hastily touched every plant in the room. Most plants did not change, but a quarter of the plants gave her the same feeling.

In the enormous alchemy room with not a single other person, she felt like she was surrounded by countless eyes peeking at her silently.

A shiver went down her spine uncontrollably.

These immobile plants seemed to have grown eyes, looking at and observing her.

"Something's wrong... something's very wrong..." Emerald Grass murmured.

...

It was late at night.

In the Internal Personnel Residential Area inside the sanctuary core area, Hila, who was in a black windbreaker, was sitting on the rooftop, looking up at the starry night.

Ever since Han Xiao left, she would go up to the rooftop occasionally and look up at the stars blankly.

In the past year, Hila had not left the sanctuary, and Aurora's health had recovered.

"Whoo..." A four-meter-tall gigantic white bear growled softly. This bear was circling around the courtyard on its fours, and a blonde girl was sitting on its back, smiling and laughing brightly. Her voice was young, energetic, and full of life.

Aurora's power was recovering slowly, and she was gradually growing taller. She was not skinny and tiny like before anymore; her skin became whiter and smoother with a tint of healthy redness. Bear Cub, who followed her around, was growing quickly, too. Its fur was smooth, soft, and slightly reflective. On its forehead, chest, arms, and thighs, there were scales that looked like ice crystals. It looked tough and muscular, and its tiny eyes looked both cute and fearsome.

Hila looked down, furrowed her brows, and said, "Don't run too fast and be careful not to fall."

"Are you looking at the moon again, Sis?" Aurora looked up.

"The moon isn't what I'm looking at."

"I know, you must be thinking of uncle Black Phantom." Aurora smiled and said, "I miss him, too."

"Who says I'm missing him." Hila snorted. "I'm just curious about what the universe looks like. Hmm... I only occasionally guess what he's doing in space. That guy left a strange disaster prophecy and left us afraid while he's having fun in space."

Aurora's eyes moved around and blew a shining kiss, which flew to Hila's cheeks.

Hila waved her hands and dissipated the rune of light in front of her. "Stop it."

At this moment, Aurora's movement suddenly stopped. Her smile froze on her face, and her body started to shiver uncontrollably.

"Si—sis..."

"Hmm?" Hila looked down. Her expression immediately dropped, and with a flash of red glow, she appeared beside Aurora in an instant, holding her in her arms. She reached for her forehead and said anxiously, "What's wrong? Are you sick? I'll go find that Pharmacist."

"No..." Aurora opened her mouth with some difficulty, her tiny body still shivering. "My power sensed a very strange creature. No, that thing can't be considered a creature. I don't know what is that either..."

Hila was bewildered. Aurora's power could sense signs of life—she had never seen Aurora get so horrified just because she sensed a certain life form.

"What did you sense?"

Aurora closed her eyes, her lips pale.

"It's very tiny... but very huge too... it's spreading..."

When her eyes reopened, they were filled with horror.

"It's everywhere!"

...

In the Black Star stronghold hall, all the players of the mercenary group were gathered together.

"It's about time." King Admiral looked at the interface. "The version update will start in an hour, let's log off here."

"It's safer here." Hao Tian nodded.

"Hmm, we will experience a time skip because of the update. There will be unknown changes, so it's best to stay in the stronghold," Frenzied Sword said earnestly.

As one of the players from the closed beta, he knew that there would be a time skip after the update. The original characters and factions would act alone and go through various changes. When the public beta started, he had even been separated from Han Xiao because of this.

No one knew what the duration of the time skip in this version update would be, nor did they know what Black Star would become.

Frenzied Sword only hoped not to be separated from Han Xiao again. He had only narrowly found Han Xiao on Planet Aquamarine, but if they scattered in space, he would probably end up playing the game as if it was a single-player game. Therefore, staying in the Black Star stronghold was the safest choice.

Throughout the whole of Version 1.0, it was the benefits that Black Star had provided that led them to be this strong. Even the players with a different class from Han Xiao became stronger because of Han Xiao's equipment, not to mention those high reward missions. All the players wanted to continue following Black Star in the next version.

Not only them but the Planet Aquamarine players as well. Every time they watched Bun-Hit-Dog's videos, they lamented over not being able to be a member of the mercenary group. The fun and adventures came second—the main reason was that there were so many rewards!

We are so jealous!

"Brothers, I shall go first. Let's have a meal together when there's a chance." Bun-Hit-Dog logged off first.

Maple Moon gave a reserved smile, waved goodbye, and disappeared on the spot.

They said goodbye to each other and logged off one after another. Soon, all the players in the mercenary group disappeared.

They were not the only ones—the same thing happened at the same time on all thirteen novice planets. Close to ten million players disappeared together within a short period of time!

The officers of the sanctuary were stunned, and Huang Yu was completely clueless. He had made preparations privately for three entire days, and just as he was about to split the increasing number of Inhumans, they had all disappeared without warning!

What on earth is this!

The once crowded and boisterous player square had become deserted and quiet. There was not a single person there. A chill wind blew past, and an old newspaper rolled on the street.

The residents from a distance walked into the streets one after another and looked over in shock and bewilderment.

Many people thought of the same thing—the Inhumans disappeared the same sudden way that they had appeared like they had never existed before...

But the marks and changes left by the Inhumans were real and could not be ignored—these were the signs that they had existed.

Far away, in Juberly Hub, the Great Mechanic Han was punishing Sylvia in the machinery modification room as he suddenly moved his eyebrows. He opened the interface, and a new notification entered his sight.

_____________________

Version 1.0 Update Activated

Saving data... saving completed!

Player forums closed.

Update Duration: Unknown. Please wait patiently.

_____________________

Han Xiao tried to enter the forums, but the link had become gray, and he could not enter it anymore, just like when the closed beta ended.

Han Xiao closed the books, shook his head, sighed. Sipping on a cup of tea, he calmed his thoughts.

"It's finally here. Sigh, tough days..."

Chapter 442: Radical Promotion Idea

Han Xiao counted his assets. He had 1.5 billion experience and about 900 thousand Enas. In the next year without players, he would have no choice but to do missions if he wanted experience, and the speed of obtaining rewards had drastically decreased. When the players were there, it was like he was dining at luxurious restaurants every day, but now he would have to eat buns and vegetables.

"Black Star?" Sylvia finally finished reading an entire paragraph of machinery theories that she memorized, but she saw Han Xiao had no reaction to it and looked like he was dozing, so she called him.

"I'm listening." Han Xiao raised his eyes. He contemplated for a while, then put down the book and said, "We will leave Juberly Hub in two days, and you'll come with us. I will help you to awaken your energy tomorrow. That's it for today, you can go back."

After Sylvia left, Han Xiao locked the machinery modification room door, took out a pen and paper, and wrote down some of his thoughts.

"Now that the players have disappeared, the force at my command is only the officers around me and the Sunil warriors. They're only mortal, so I have to act carefully. This year is the preparation stage for Version 2.0. In order to have the upper hand, I have many jobs I need to complete.

"First and foremost is my Promotion mission. The stronger I am, the safer it is, and the easier it will be to act. I must find a relatively weaker opponent in Grade A. Even so, the risk is still very high... but so are the benefits. Once I complete my level 100 Promotion, I will have the chance for a Race Evolution again, and my combat ability will increase tremendously."

Han Xiao tapped the table with his pen, furrowed his brow, and contemplated. He searched for a suitable choice in his memories. Names of characters flashed past one after another but were all quickly eliminated. Some were too strong, some were too far away, and some suitable ones had yet to appear.

In his mind, the best target would, of course, be Ember, whom he had fought before. He could counter that guy's Esper ability, but Ember had yet to reach Grade A and seemed to have died under the bombardment from the fleet. Thus, he could only eliminate this choice as well."

"Sigh, there are no suitable targets, what should I do?" Han Xiao scratched his head in frustration.

The difficulty mainly came from the strength difference between him and a Grade A Super. Plus, having anyone above his grade interfere and help was restricted. This meant he could not ask the Dragon Emperor for help. In order to kill a Grade A with a group of Grade Bs, it would be many times more difficult than when Sylvia tried to assassinate him. The resistance and health of Grade A Supers meant that many schemes would not work on them. Furthermore, none of those who could reach Grade A would be not cautious and alert; it was impossible for them to fall into traps easily.

With his level, if he wanted to kill them directly, he could only use extremely powerful weapons or traps with significantly high technology, such as a Destroyer Level Battleship Quantum Annihilation Cannon, the Forbidden Doomsday Electric Ring Spell Scroll, or something of the same level. However, he did not have any way to buy those.

Furthermore, his officers were not players. If they knew that they were going to go against a Grade A Super, they would definitely have issues with it and might not be willing to take the risk to do something so meaningless, unless they had incomparable hatred toward the target. If he chose a Grade A DarkStar member, then Herlous would not oppose it.

Although Han Xiao knew the abilities of DarkStar's Grade A Supers, such as 'Wind Demon' Anur, 'Psychic Explosion' Vivira, and 'Mountain Hammer' Rogue, he did not have the confidence to mess with any of them. Furthermore, DarkStar's forces were strong, stealthy, and swift, so it was impractical to choose one of them.

He could wait till Version 2.0 started and command the players to fight the opponent. However, wasting a year of not becoming stronger would place him in a very dangerous situation when facing DarkStar in Version 2.0. Secondly, even if a thousand of those Grade C players fought against one Grade A, they would still be wiped out in an instant. Sure, they could revive, but they would not be of any use.

Not to mention Grade A, even the Great Mechanic Han could beat a group of players himself.

Han Xiao was very troubled by his level 100 Promotion mission as he did not know what he could do.

It's so damn difficult!

If he could revive like the players, he might still have had a chance and would not have been so frustrated. However, he only had one chance, and once he failed, it would be his end. These various factors caused this Promotion to be almost impossible to complete.

"Then there's no choice but to take a shortcut..." Han Xiao held his forehead and sighed.

The chance to complete the Promotion mission through regular means was almost negligible. Luckily, he had the radical method.

Mission Completion Card!

Its effect was to grant the mission reward of a mission and deem the mission as completed with the lowest rating.

This was indeed suitable for Promotion missions with no mission rating. As long as it was completed, he could be promoted.

To the players, the effect of the Mission Completion Card was very ordinary—they usually used it on extremely difficult missions. However, the lowest rating reward would not be a lot anyway, so they might as well try the mission themselves and see if they could get a higher rating. Therefore, despite this item being very rare, it was not scarce. The Mission Completion Card had once appeared in the random reward after Han Xiao completed the Germinal Organization main storyline, but he had chosen the other choice, which was Esper Ability Potential Enhancing Fluid. Although he needed the Mission Completion Card, the Esper Ability Potential Enhancing Fluid had undoubtedly been the right choice back then.

"There are three methods to obtain Mission Completion Cards. First, it might appear as a random reward, and random rewards are only given when a difficult mission is completed with a high rating. Second, reward from specific missions. Third, cash in and buy from the store, limited to five per month..."

The third method was eliminated straight away without a doubt, and the second method would not work as well, as these specific missions were in other Star Fields—it was way too far. Thus, he could only use the first method.

"The pro is that I can avoid the risk of fighting a Grade A Super—the con is that there's too much uncertainty."

Han Xiao shook his head.

Adventures are for the youngsters, old people like me should do it the stable way.

...

The next day, Sylvia came as promised. Han Xiao agreed to help her awaken energy today, so she had hardly slept the previous night. She was looking forward to it, nervous and anxious.

"Sit." Han Xiao pointed at the chair beside him. The chair had bondage straps on its armrests, back, and legs—it looked like an electric chair.

"Wha—what is this?" Sylvia swallowed her saliva uncontrollably and forced a smile. "I remember being told that awakening Mechanical Force only needs simple training..."

The Mage class could generate magic power through mediation. Although the Mechanic class was focused on external objects, there were also similar methods to awaken their exclusive Mechanical Force.

"You're talking about the regular way. It's too slow. I've said before, you already have Super-Genes, and you're talented in Mechanic class. I have a much quicker way."

Han Xiao's tone was very calm. If someone was confirmed to have the potential for the Mechanic class, there was a method to quickly awaken the Mechanical Force—have another Mechanic stimulate their body. This way, the speed of awakening would be much quicker. This was what he had found by searching through the Mechanic class articles. Of course, if the target did not have the potential, it was not much different from electrocution.

Although the players grew in a different way and did not have to experience these stages, many articles had recorded the training methods for different classes. To the players, these 'details' made it more immersive and real.

Han Xiao tied Sylvia to the chair and spread his palm. Dense electric snakes appeared on his hand and formed a lump of light with shifting shape, flashing terrifying electric light. He glanced at Sylvia, whose body was stiff and face was filled with terror.

"Relax, don't be nervous."

Sylvia struggle continuously in terror and yelled, "Do—don't come here... Ahhh!"

Before she finished talking, Han Xiao's hand grabbed onto Sylvia's forehead. The electric light surged into her body and coursed through her, flickering.

Buzz!

Sylvia's entire body was trembling like a fish being electrocuted. Her body was penetrated by electric currents from head to toe, her muscles were retracting, and she was numb from the pain. It felt like her body was not hers anymore.

"This should be enough, or she might be electrocuted..."

Han Xiao counted the time, pulled his hands away, and stepped back.

Sylvia slumped against the chair with her head dangling from her neck. White smoke floated from all over her body, and she had yet to recover from the pain. She wanted to speak, but her entire body was numb, and her tongue could not move.

A special sense was born in her body—it was very weak, but it was there. Sylvia struggled to focus and tried to control it. A tiny and almost unnoticeable electric current flashed under her skin.

"I activated your Super-Gene; you now have the magnetic-type energy. Keep training, and you will grow. I will teach you the ways to train energy in a few days. Go back and memorize another machinery theory book first."

Sylvia finally stood up. She looked down, and her face twitched. In the end, she could not hold it back and cried out loud as she ran out of the room.

Coincidentally, Herlous happened to be at the door and almost bumped into her. Surprised, he said, "What did you do to her... Wait a minute, what's the smell in this room?"

The next moment, Herlous' expression became strange. With shock and suspicion, he looked at Han Xiao from head to toe, again and again, looking like he wanted to say something but did not.

"I know what you want to say, shut up." Han Xiao rolled his eyes. "Get to business, what do you want?"

"By the way, all your subordinates disappeared and still have yet to return after one day," Herlous said.

Players logged on and off regularly—Han Xiao had given a perfunctory explanation, saying that it was the side effect of their immortal body. The other officers were used to it, but they had never seen all the players disappearing together and not appearing after an entire day, so Herlous came to ask Han Xiao about it.

Han Xiao contemplated and found an excuse to get it over with. Roughly, he meant that the price of being immortal was that they had to sleep every once in a certain period, and when they stayed active for too long, they would have to take a very long sleep. They would not appear again for a very long time. Herlous had doubts but had no choice but to convince himself to believe it.

"They won't be around for the time being, so I'm preparing to stop the mercenary group's business... not including your Sunils. I'm talking about us."

"Then what are we going to do?"

Han Xiao pointed at his own eyes and mysteriously said, "It saw some things again. Remember my promise to you? I can feel it, the time is near."

Herlous' eyes turned bright.

"But... I need to make some preparations. We will go to the Taralam Star Cluster next," Han Xiao said.

"That's the closest Star Cluster to the wormhole cluster at the middle of Shattered Star Ring and the area with the largest scavenger forces. It's very dangerous, what are we going there for?"

"To find something," Han Xiao said with a deep voice.

A random reward would only be given after completing a mission with a high rating. Based on this, Han Xiao confirmed his action plan. He was going to target the missions that he knew extremely well, and he was going to choose the ones that were not too difficult but definitely would be intricate to complete through normal means. This way, he could make full use of the advantage of knowing the mission well and obtain a very high rating!

What he was going to find on this trip was an item to trigger a mission. In his previous life, the players had acquired this item coincidentally—the item introduction indicated that this item could trigger a mission—and had gone to look for the person to trigger the mission. Only then did they receive the mission. Han Xiao, however, was very familiar with the process. He did not need a coincidence; he knew exactly what he had to do.

Han Xiao had already calculated everything. The missions that he now had also had a chance of giving a random reward. However, they were either not activated or needed time. What he needed was only the chance to receive random rewards; the mission reward came second. He remembered many missions, and these all had chances to receive random rewards.

Although obtaining a [Mission Completion Card] was full of uncertainties, it was at least much safer than facing a Grade A Super directly.

Chapter 443: Backdoor

In the Taralam Star Cluster, a spaceship hovered outside the atmosphere of the small planet numbered 51687. This was a deserted planet marked as a resource planet in the database.

"Low oxygen density in the atmosphere, an average temperature of sixty degrees, not suitable for human habitation. A large amount of heat-preferring plants covering a large area of the surface. The soil contains rich nitrogen, phosphorus, and potassium, suitable for plant growth..."

Han Xiao looked through the planet information, pointed at a tall forest on the map, and said, "There's a secret stronghold of a small group of scavengers here—they're our target of this trip. They have something that I need."

His target of this trip was an item that could trigger a high rating mission, and that item was in the hands of this scavenger group.

"You're planning to break in? How strong are they?" Herlous asked.

"Not strong, just one Grade B. The main issue is that their defensive measures are quite tight, but they have a secret pathway that leads to the underground spaceship garage, which is located here." Han Xiao drew a circle on the map.

"How did you even know this?" Herlous was surprised.

Without speaking, Han Xiao answered by pointing to his eyes. "The plan is simple. I'll kick the door open and crush the enemies—you'll go to the garage and wait for them. Don't let anyone go. Everyone else, standby on the ship."

After quickly finalizing the plan, the spaceship ejected two egg-shaped airdrop cabins. They penetrated the atmosphere like two meteors, falling down to the forest.

The descent was full of turbulence.

Boom!

The airdrop cabins crashed through a few trees and buried themselves deep in the ground. Soil and wood splattered all over the place and created a mess.

The cabin door opened. Han Xiao walked out, identified their location, and said, "The landing location is about four hundred meters from the enemy's base. There are many automatic machine gun traps ahead. Hmm... there's not much oxygen, so breathing is a little difficult."

The bone-white Void Dragon shrouded his body and filtered the air. Han Xiao inhaled a full mouth of oxygen, and mechanical energy flew into the compressed orbs as they fell onto the floor. With the sound of mechanical parts moving, the compressed orbs expanded into thirty mechanical Black Panther mechanical beasts and surrounded him.

"Go."

With a snap of his fingers, the mechanical beasts charged forward into the alert area of the enemy's base. Gaps quickly opened up one after another on the ground, exposing ten or so automatic machine guns that started to fire immediately. Blazing red bullets landed on the mechanical beasts' armor, causing fire sparkles and continuous clanks.

This extent of damage was nothing worth mentioning to the enhanced mechanical Black Panther beasts. Thirty mechanical beasts culled the enemies one after another, cutting through muzzles quickly and swiftly with their sharp blade tails. The sound of gunshots disappeared very soon—all the automatic machine guns became scrap metal.

The other benefit of the Hounds Style was that the mechanical beasts could be used to scout ahead.

After Han Xiao learned the advanced artificial intelligence knowledge, he swapped the mechanical beasts' smart chip. Previously, the mechanical beasts could only carry out combat tactics in groups of four, but it had become sixteen, making them much more flexible and swift.

Crossing through the machine guns, Han Xiao activated the metal detection device in his helmet. The full structure of the base showed on the analyzing screen. He found the door on the ground and pulled it open. Inside was a pitch-black path toward inside of the base. A faint buzzing sound came from within—the alarm.

"Looks like they already know I'm here."

His fingers moved. The shoulder armor plate opened, and three mini mechanical flying insects flew out into the path. These flying insects were equipped with all kinds of detection devices that could be used to find traps, among many other things.

"One Laser Corridor with more automatic machine guns... Mobile Crushing Walls and Vacuum Seals... quite many defensive measures I see. One-meter thick gate made by high strength alloy, cannot be opened by hand."

The analyzing screen was showing the view of the detection flying insects. They were very small, and they were covered in coatings that could block all sorts of detection methods, so they safely passed through the infrared detection of the corridor and came to the gate. Beside the gate was a password device.

Han Xiao sent a new order. The two flying insects suddenly stuck onto the edge of the device. Mini rotary saws popped out from a flying insect's mouth and pried open the exterior of the password device. A chip plug popped up from the other flying insect's tail and connected to the password device. The pair of flying insects were tiny cuties made from another advanced knowledge, [Mini Machinery Modification], which he had bought some point in the prior nine months. They had very rich functions, capable of scouting, detecting, and remote hacking.

The data stream of the base appeared on the analyzing screen. Han Xiao started to hack it while keeping an eye out for enemies to suddenly strike. However, as he hacked through the gate's program, no one appeared.

This time, Herlous' communication came with a sigh. "I've arrived at the garage; there's no spaceship here. Don't bother wasting your time; there's no one here."

Han Xiao's eyes twitched. The player in his previous life had needed to break into this scavenger base to get the mission item, but luckily for him, none of the enemies were even home.

No wonder no one had appeared despite him having already arrived at their gate.

"We really came at a good time..."

Han Xiao was speechless. It turned out that he was fighting with the air all along. He quickly stood up and walked into the base casually. He had already shut down all the defensive measures. After he entered the stronghold, there was indeed no one inside.

Although the base was not huge, it had everything it needed. Han Xiao spent some time and completely hacked the system firewall, took over control of the base, and went straight to the warehouse.

The warehouse was stacked with things collected by the scavengers, most of which was useless. Han Xiao was mainly looking for the item that could trigger the mission, and after searching for a while, he found it without any twists and turns.

It was a beautiful and detailed mini statue that looked like it was made by some kind of brown wood, yet it was as strong as high strength alloys. It was the statue of a very strange creature. If it had to be described, it kind of looked like a distorted mantis. As Han Xiao picked it up, a low and unclear voice suddenly appeared in his mind.

You have received [Mysterious Statue].

Item Introduction: This is a statue that you have never seen before. You don't know what it represents or what meaning it has, but when you touch it, you hear a soft, faint voice speaking to you in your mind. Yet, when you focus on that voice, it disappears.

Remarks: This item seems to possess certain secret knowledge. Some people might be interested in it.

"This is it." Han Xiao's eyes sparkled. This was a mission triggering item, and he knew the origins of it. This statue was one item included in an item set that came from the Arcane Church and arrived at the central wormhole of the Shattered Star Ring from a distant Star Field. Then, it wandered and ended up there. The players could receive the related mission through two methods. One was, of course, to get this item first then meet the person that would trigger the mission later, and the other was to first get clues from that person then find the item that would trigger the mission. In conclusion, no matter which method was used, it required a certain amount of luck. However, Han Xiao did not need to go through such trouble—he could head straight for the key item.

This phenomenon of giving someone an illusion of hearing voices in their head was a characteristic of the Psychic Current. The Psychic Current was very unique and could occur through various means, such as the thoughts of many creatures being enchanted onto on target. After a certain amount of time, this item would produce Psychic Current once it had gathered enough thoughts, like a container of gathered thoughts. The most well-known example would be sacrifices and prayers, and this statue was made from exactly that.

"I've got the item," Han Xiao said.

"That's quick, shall we leave now?" Herlous asked.

Han Xiao was just about to reply, but suddenly, his movement paused. He looked around, and a daring idea appeared in his mind. "Don't be in such a hurry. There's no one here, and we have plenty of time."

Since they had arrived while the enemy was out, they definitely had to take more things with them.

No, that was too petty.

They should take the entire place!

Without hesitation, Han Xiao called Herlous and came to help those scavengers 'move house'.

Base System Chip? Take it!

Defensive devices? Take it!

Alloy wall? Take it!

After quite some time of tearing things down, whatever could be taken from the base was removed and put into more than a dozen supply boxes. For a Mechanic at Han Xiao's level, the speed of tearing things down was extremely fast.

He roughly estimated that those items could be recycled and turned into more than 2,000 Enas worth of machinery parts.

Han Xiao looked back. The scavenger base had already become an empty shell with opened gates... no, the gates were already gone. Even the floor had been pried open, exposing the wires below the ground. The central computer and energy core had all been dismantled. The rather huge base was only left with walls.

Han Xiao smiled with satisfaction. He ordered the spaceship to land and loaded the full supply boxes into the spaceship.

A few days later, the scavenger spaceships finally returned to the planet. They had made quite a good profit from picking up trash near the wormhole clusters, so they were rather joyful.

However, when the base with missing gates and an empty interior entered their visions, everyone froze in place.

What the hell? Where's our base‽

The scavenger captain rubbed his eyes and made sure that he was not seeing an illusion. His face turned furious, and he howled, "Who tore down our base‽"

This planet was completely unpopulated, and it was in a very rural area. They had spent quite a lot of resources to build a secret base there and never exposed its position. How could anyone know where their base was ‽

In the Taralam Star Cluster, they were just a small group of scavengers. Who would bother to go against them? It had to be a petty thief that got lucky!

"Search! Search for the petty thief who did this!" the captain yelled furiously and regretfully. If he had been in the base, he could have prevented it from happening.

They barely gathered the intel fee and contacted the information seller. After searching, they found out that there was only one spaceship that visited this planet during that period. After uncovering the identity of the passengers of that spaceship, the rage of those scavengers immediately disappeared. In fact, they were dumbfounded.

"Bla—Black Star‽" The scavenger captain was stuttering. "What were galactic mercenaries of that level doing here?"

They exchanged looks and were immediately discouraged. Now, they suddenly felt glad they had not been in the base when it happened.

If they had faced Black Star, they certainly would have died.

Suddenly, the scavengers felt that losing a base was not so unacceptable.

As the scavengers were feeling glad, Han Xiao and the others passed through the Star Cluster teleportation stargate and came to the Rain Star System of the Colton Star Cluster. The person that could trigger the mission was there... temporarily.

The ruling civilization of Rain Star System, the New Phylen Alliance, had invited a galactic celebrity that was very popular in Shattered Star Ring to tour the place. The entertainment industry in the galaxy was very developed as well. There were singers, actors, and many other industries that brought entertainment to various civilizations.

The different entertainment shows could be watched from the paid channel in the Galactic Communicator. Although Han Xiao did not watch it much, many galactic residents spent their days watching television. After all, with how developed some civilizations were, most people did not have to work, unless they wanted higher positions or better quality of life.

The person to trigger this mission was rather special—it was indeed the galactic celebrity that had been invited.

Chapter 444: Chen Xing and Statue Mission (1)

This celebrity had a huge number of fans in various Star Clusters in the Shattered Star Ring. He was a singer, and because of how developed the transmission technology was, his influence was not limited by physical distance.

This performance was for the traditional yearly celebration of the New Phylen Alliance being reunited, and this singer was the most famous one among all the invited guests.

The venue of the performance was a vacation spaceship called 'Wine and Celebration'. Those who could watch it live were all either wealthy or had a very high position in the New Phylen Alliance. If Han Xiao wanted to come into contact with the target, it had to be at the venue, but the problem was... how were they going to get the ticket for the show?

"Are you going to the Union Day Celebration?"

When Sylvia heard about the destination of their spaceship, she rolled her eyes and said, "Stop dreaming. Every year, those that can enter the venue to watch it live are all very important people. Such as leaders of political parties, higher-ups in the army, high level government officials, businessmen that pay tons of taxes every year, and so on. With so many important people gathered in one place, the security is extremely tight. Don't even think about sneaking in—you might be mistaken for an assassin."

Han Xiao glanced at her and said, "Have you finished memorizing the books I gave you?"

Sylvia's tone instantly turned soft, and she murmured, "Isn't there one more day before the test..."

"By the way, you're a New Phylen citizen. Don't you want to watch it live at the scene?"

Sylvia curled her lips and said with a yearning tone, "Who doesn't want to? But us ordinary people can only watch on television."

The Union Day was a memorial for the day that the nations of the New Phylen Alliance reunited after their split; it was very meaningful to the New Phylen people, similar to National Day in China. Sylvia wanted to go every year, and in fact, Langley's position had been high enough to get her into the venue. Unfortunately, he was a traitor and a spy.

Now that she had become a mercenary, she would never have the chance to attend it again, so she could only bury this tiny dream of hers.

Mercenaries were powerful and strong indeed, but they did not have a high position in society. After all, for the most part, the lives of galactic citizens were peaceful. Only when they faced problems that could only be solved with violence would they think of the professionals in this field. Other than that, they would not want to have any contact with such dangerous mercenaries.

Furthermore, most mercenaries were free citizens of the universe that did not have a nationality. Although Han Xiao had worked with the New Phylen Alliance before, this small of relationship was only enough for him to request to see prisoners at most—it was far from enough to attend such a huge celebration.

Of course, nothing was absolute. With the backing of Floating Dragon Island, if Han Xiao could drag Ames there, he did not believe that the New Phylen Alliance would not invite the Dragon Emperor in. In fact, not only would they be invited, they would definitely be sitting in the top VIP seats beside the alliance leader.

What? You don't give me, the Dragon Emperor, face?

Well then, have you ever seen a brick the size of a planet?

When one's strength reached a certain level, there would be no need to even showcase it; just showing up would be enough.

Han Xiao rubbed his chin, pondered, and said, "Since you want to go to the venue, I'll bring you along then. It's not much trouble anyway."

Sylvia was dazed. She asked uncertainly, "Do you really have the ticket? Impossible..."

"There's no need for a ticket." Han Xiao waved his hands and said, "Someone will invite me in."

"As if I believe you."

Sylvia was obviously doubtful. She paused and said unhappily, "Plus, I still need to memorize the books..."

"Alright fine, I'll give you a day's holiday."

Han Xiao shook his head and smiled.

Herlous came closer and said with an expressionless face, "Let me guess, I'll be staying here and looking after the ship?"

"Wow, my brother, we really have good chemistry; you basically read my mind."

Han Xiao clapped with exaggeration, and Herlous resigned to his fate.

Wine and Celebration was docked on the main planet of the New Phylen Alliance. This was an enormous spaceship that had a flat hexagonal shape and surrounded by countess guard ships. For the Union Day Celebration, the dock had stopped its service for the day and was used solely to welcome all the attendees.

In the hall of the dock, a huge number of people were gathered. They were all New Phylen citizens, there to watch the boarding ceremony.

All the performers and political leaders would enter from the same path on the dock. This was a ceremony representing the start of the Union Day Celebration and the only chance that normal citizens had to be close to the venue. Hence, there were a lot of people and it was very crowded.

Han Xiao was in the crowd at this moment. Despite the wave of the crowd moving around him, he stood in his place without budging. Sylvia had to hold on to his shirt tightly so that she would not be pushed away.

At the edge of the crowd were rows of soldiers regulating the order and preventing anyone from rushing into the boarding path. These soldiers frequently glanced at Han Xiao with warning and alertness in their eyes—it was clear that they could tell Han Xiao was a Super with a high threat.

"Bla—Black Star... I want to ask you for the last time..." Sylvia said while shivering. She kept swallowing her saliva and spoke anxiously. "We're not really going to cause a commotion and rush into the spaceship, are we? Although I gave you my next ten years, you don't have to let cut it this short..."

Han Xiao could not be bothered to reply. He waited patiently and silently.

After some time, a commotion erupted among the crowd in a distance. Accompanied by the guards, the important personnel boarded the ship one after another. The crowd was cheering so loud that it was almost deafening. Those people walked with smiles on their faces while waving and greeting the crowd.

"They've started boarding the ship..." Sylvia craned her neck and exclaimed, "Wow, that's the alliance chancellor. I used to see him a lot on television."

She did not believe that Han Xiao could enter the venue. Now that the boarding had started, the fact that Han Xiao was still there proved that he was not one of the people that was boarding, but Sylvia did not call him out on it. She was already satisfied that she could go to watch the boarding ceremony. Her father had not allowed her to go in the past, so this was the first time that she had seen the Union Day Celebration spaceship so closely. Although she could not enter the spaceship, she was content.

Although Langley was a rebel, he had taught his daughter to love her country.

Suddenly, a louder cheer came from afar and rippled closer like a wave. Han Xiao looked up. A human-shaped creature in a veil who was surrounded by a group of assistants was walking here slowly. A pair of extremely attractive eyes smeared with black eye shadow could be seen from under the veil. Even the solemn blue robe could not cover his attractiveness.

"Chen Xing! Chen Xing!"

The cheering was thunderous.

Han Xiao nodded in his mind. This was the person that would trigger the mission, a singer with the stage name of 'Morning Star[1]'. From the almost ear-shattering cheer, it was clear how successful this person's celebrity career was.

By the way, this person was a male.

While passing by where Han Xiao was, Chen Xing suddenly stopped and turned his head slowly. His eyes passed through the crowd and locked accurately onto Han Xiao. The next moment, he directly walked toward this direction.

The crowd instantly became feverish and wanted to touch their idol. The soldiers stopped the wave of people with all their might, and one soldier said, "Your Excellency Chen Xing, please do not come close. It's not safe here."

"It's okay, they will not hurt me."

Chen Xing opened his mouth. His voice was gentle, soothing, and pure like water. The people who heard it felt calm. The commotion mysteriously stopped, and he walked into the crowd.

The crowd opened up a path willingly.

In the end, Chen Xing stopped before Han Xiao. Under the eyes of countless people, he smiled and said, "Hello, I hope to have the honor to invite you to watch my performance live at the scene personally."

[1] Morning Star is Chen Xing in Chinese. Back

Chapter 445: Chen Xing and Statue Mission (2)

"Hiss!"

The crowd inhaled deeply and looked at Han Xiao in disbelief and envy. The people around Han Xiao instantly backed off and isolated him, making him extremely conspicuous.

"Who is this guy? What is his relationship with Chen Xing?"

"Why is he chosen?"

"What a lucky guy."

Han Xiao nodded without changing expression and said, "Sure."

"Please follow me."

Chen Xing turned around, and Han Xiao followed behind the group. Chen Xing's assistant contacted the organizers, and the government found Han Xiao's identity very quickly. It turned out that he was a mercenary who had worked with them before and belonged to Floating Dragon. Thus, he was trustworthy. Although it was not very suitable to let a mercenary into the venue, for the sake of giving Chen Xing face and the fact that Han Xiao had no negative background, they agreed to let him in.

They walked through the path and boarded the celebration spaceship. Sylvia was completely stunned on the way, unable to understand what was happening and dumbfounded at the fact that she had entered the celebration venue, which she had dreamed of for years, so easily. When she finally regained consciousness, she hastily pulled Han Xiao's shirt and said, "You really did it!"

"From what I know about you, your memory isn't that bad. Maybe I should give you more books to train it." Han Xiao stared at Chen Xing's back.

"I—I thought you were lying..." Sylvia did not know what to say. It had happened exactly as Han Xiao had said—they were invited onto the ship. However, she never would have thought that the person inviting them would be Chen Xing, and it looked like it was a last-minute decision.

She suppressed her excitement and asked with anticipation, "How did you do it?"

"No crowd can cover up my attractiveness." Han Xiao gave a perfunctory response.

The real reason, of course, was the [Mysterious Statue] that Han Xiao had with him. Chen Xing had a special sense toward the Psychic Current of the statue. As long as it was within a certain distance, he would definitely notice it. Hence, Han Xiao had known that Chen Xing would invite him onto the ship.

...

After everyone boarded, the various large cities on the main planet lit fireworks as Wine and Celebration took off and circled around the main planet. The spaceship was covered in streams of colorful lights, and the people on the surface could see the enormous spaceship when they looked up.

Han Xiao was arranged to be in the VIP room of Chen Xing's team. Chen Xing did not speak to him immediately but went to prepare for the show. He told his assistant that if Han Xiao asked why he was invited, tell him that he would meet him privately after the celebration.

However, the assistant waited and waited, yet Han Xiao did not express any curiosity. He closed his eyes and rested from the moment that he entered the room like he was completely uninterested in knowing why he had been invited. After waiting for a long time without receiving any response, the assistant had no choice but to speak first.

"Your... Excellency, Chen Xing wanted to talk to you after the celebration ends. Please wait patiently and enjoy the show."

"Hmm." Han Xiao gave a very short reply.

He knew Chen Xing extremely well, so he had no intention of asking anything.

After some time, the audience was all seated. The roof suddenly opened, showing the universe full of stars. A thick energy shield blocked the vacuum. This was the center of the spaceship, and it was an enormous outdoor stage!

The VIP rooms shook slightly as they slowly rose and hovered in midair, slanting toward the stage at forty-five degrees. One side of the wall was a transparent screen looking down at the entire stage. The VIP rooms had gravitational stabilizers equipped, so although the rooms were slanted, the people inside were sitting firmly in their chairs. There were more than two hundred VIP rooms like this, and they were like balloons floating above the stage.

With the magnificent and beautiful light starting to shine from the stage, an enormous performance commenced.

At the same time, the countless citizens of New Phylen were watching this scene from their devices. It was a celebration shared by hundreds of billions of people.

Sylvia was completely astounded by such a magnificent view. This was her first time being at the scene and attending the celebration in person.

She had begged her father many times, but she had always been rejected. Yet, Han Xiao had done what her father did not do—fulfilled her dream.

Filled with complex emotions, Sylvia turned her head and looked at Han Xiao.

This person was her enemy, her savior, her creditor, and her teacher...

Noticing her sight, Han Xiao said calmly, "What?"

"Nothing, Tea..." Sylvia curled her lips. "Old man[1]."

"What kind of term is that? Are your eyes not working properly?" Han Xiao looked at her with confusion.

The celebration performance continued. Han Xiao was not a New Phylen citizen, so he was not very interested in the ceremonies, but the performance was indeed exciting. When it came to the last and most anticipated performance, the performer was indeed Chen Xing.

All eyes were on Chen Xing. On the enormous stage, where he stood was the only place that had light; everywhere else was dark. Yet, just by standing there, he made people feel he had occupied the entire stage. The whole place was silent.

The first note flew out from under Chen Xing's veil—ethereal, elegant, and pure—like the voice from heaven. Her voice seemed to have created a wave of time, bringing the audience back to the ancient times, looking up at the first dawn between darkness and night, watching the first star glowing in a dim yet firm light.

Before the performance, the whole audience had turned off their translators, not allowing them to stand in the way of enjoying such a pure voice. Even though they could not understand what the lyrics meant, the immensity of the voice captured every one of their hearts. The audience felt like countless images flashed past before their eyes, the origin and the end of a star, and the endless cycle of life.

Along with his singing, the light on the stage started to expand. When he reached his highest note, the light also spread over the entire stage.

The audiences felt a shiver from the depths of their soul that flew into their mind.

"What a beautiful voice..." Sylvia was completely immersed in the song.

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

A voice that included such strong Psychic power was indeed very influential.

"The money spent on organizing such a huge performance is enough to buy so many spaceships. What a waste..."

Han Xiao shook his head. Art was definitely not suitable for him.

The song had come to an end. Whether it was the audience at the scene or the audience watching from a screen, they were all engrossed in it. Chen Xing lowered his head slightly and left the stage. The overwhelming applause only came after he left.

Han Xiao stood up, stretched his neck, and looked at the assistant. "Bring me to see him."

...

In the private room, Han Xiao and Sylvia were waiting on the guest seats.

The door opened with a squeak, and Chen Xing, who had just finished his performance, walked in with an apologetic smile. "Sorry for the long wait. I hope you are satisfied with my performance earlier."

"Your voice is a little bit better than mine." Han Xiao nodded.

Sylvia's eyes widened; she was shocked by how shameless he was.

Chen Xing smiled and took off the veil, uncovering his exquisite face. From a human aesthetic point of view, this was a very beautiful face. Coincidentally, the human aesthetic was the most common in the universe.

The most beautiful female that Han Xiao had seen was Aroshia, and just in terms of looks, she was only a little more beautiful than Chen Xing. However, this was a man... exciting indeed, but he did not have such an interest.

"I know you're very curious about why I invited you," Chen Xing said.

"Hmm, I am very curious," Han Xiao said with a poker face.

No! You're not curious! Sylvia screamed in her mind.

"The reason is, I have a hobby as a collector, and I like to collect some special items. You seem to have something that I want."

As he was saying, Chen Xing took out a statue. Other than it having a different form, its material and size were exactly the same as what Han Xiao had.

Seeing the statue, Han Xiao took out the [Mysterious Statue] that he had brought along and said with a surprised tone, "Wow, what a coincidence!"

Bullsh*t coincidence! Sylvia's expression was twisted from trying extremely hard to keep the annoyance in.

"Your friend does not seem to be feeling well. Does she need to visit the washroom?" Chen Xing asked with concern. "Should I call a doctor for her?"

"No need, thanks." Han Xiao gave Sylvia a stare.

Chen Xing shrugged and continued. "This is a set of collectibles. There were originally four of them. Two of them are here, and two others are lost in unknown places. When one of them is a certain distance from another, its location can be sensed."

He leaned back against the back of the chair in a very gentle way that did not look masculine at all. "I have just heard that you're a galactic mercenary, so I want to ask you to find the last to statues for me. I will pay a reward for it. How about 100,000 Enas?"

"On—One hundred..." Sylvia could hardly breathe. That's way too generous!

Han Xiao was not surprised, however; it was very normal for a celebrity to be wealthy.

Furthermore, one of the reasons that this mission was popular in the previous life was that the difficulty of the mission did not fit its reward.

"Sure, any requests?" Han Xiao gave a faint smile.

"Request..." Chen Xing tapped his lips and said, "The sooner, the better, of course."

_____________________

You have triggered C Ranked mission [Statues Search].

Mission Introduction: A singer named Chen Xing is collecting a special set of statues. He hopes that you can find the other statues.

Mission Requirements: Find the other two [Mysterious Statue].

Remarks: When you have two statues, if there is another statue within a certain distance, you will notice.

Reward: Basic reward of 100,000 Enas and 1,100,000 Experience.

After the mission is completed, grading will be given based on the time taken to complete it. The shorter it takes, the higher the rating. A bonus reward will be given.

_____________________

Got the mission. Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

This was the mission that he wanted to trigger; it was one of the most suitable missions for him to get a high rating after he searched through his memories.

Finding an item was not difficult but very time consuming—the process was complicated, yet time was a factor in the rating given.

However, to Han Xiao, it was not difficult at all. Thanks to the players in his previous life, he knew the location of the last two statues, so he could skip the search process and obtain them directly. Getting a high rating was not a problem at all.

Since he did not want to look for Grade A Supers to kill, he had to get random reward chances through high rating missions so that he could obtain Mission Completion Cards.

The reward of the mission itself was not important; the chances for random rewards was the key.

[1] The first word of the term "old man" and "teacher" is the same in mandarin. What the writer was trying to express here is that Sylvia was about to call Han Xiao "Teacher" but changed. Back

Chapter 446: City of Runes

"Take this statue and find the others as soon as possible," Chen Xing said.

Han Xiao sized the new statue up. Its shape was a faceless human looking up with a huge eye on its chest, which was strange as well. After he held it in his hands, the item introduction on the interface was [Mysterious Statue] as well but with an additional remark.

_____________________

These statues that you have discovered seem to be a part of a set. Gather all the statues and maybe something unusual will happen.

_____________________

Han Xiao held onto the two statues and asked, "For the sake of 100,000 Enas, I accept the hire. Where do I find you once it's completed?"

"My schedule is very full. Anyway, it's impossible for you to find all of them in a short time. I will give my assistant's communication number to you later. Just inform him once you complete it." Chen Xing gave a gorgeous smile.

Although he knew the location of the statues, Han Xiao did not choose to come after collecting all three statues—it would make him seem very suspicious. After all, Chen Xing felt that meeting Han Xiao was just because of luck.

Chen Xing was looking for the statues himself, but he had never found any leads. With two statues, the area of detection for the other statues would be much larger. If not because he was very sensitive to the frequency of the statues, he would not have been able to find Han Xiao among the crowd.

He had never expected to find another statue during this performance.

Although he was smiling calmly, Han Xiao knew full well how excited this guy was.

Chen Xing said that he was a collector, which, of course, was nonsense. Han Xiao knew what his goal was.

This singer was a Psychic that used his voice to spread his powers. Although he looked gentle and weak, if Chen Xing wanted to, he could scream in an extremely high and destructive voice anytime he wanted. He was at least Grade B. It was because he put his Psychic powers into his voice that made his voice sound so impactful. These four statues had a special effect for Chen Xing—they could enhance his Psychic powers.

The four statues had originally been a set of totems for receiving prayers from believers night and day. They came from the Arcane Church.

Unlike the practical Crimson Empire and the Federation of Light that believed in freedom, the Arcane Church was a very religious and mysterious civilization.

In the knowledge of most planet and Star System sized civilizations, religions and beliefs were just a comforting or guiding tool for the mind that could at most guide the believers to have a certain attitude toward things in life. Some civilizations even saw religions as the cancer of society.

However, there were countless paths of evolution in the universe. Most religions believed in a fictional god, but some believed in real gods. Luckily for the Arcane Church, they were the latter. They had begun as savages just like the others, but unlike the other civilizations that progressed through technology or magic awakening, their ancestors discovered a way to communicate with real gods. When the gods that they believed in could really 'respond' to the believers and when the religions could make technology and society advance, their social structure naturally turned out to be different from most of the technology or magic focused civilizations.

What was a god? In magic terms, they were supposedly beings with enormous magic power. From a technological perspective, gods were superior beings from a higher dimension that could not be detected by ordinary beings. The projections from higher dimensions were all strange and weird. Thus, those that did not look unique enough were basically all false gods.

In both cases, the relationship between believers and gods were usually beneficial for both sides. However, the more developed a civilization was, the more careful their attitude toward the gods was, not giving it a definition easily.

The Arcane Church had its own explanation for the existence of gods, and they had an unbelievable technology that could turn what the believers believed in into a real being! For example, for a religion that believed in a fictional god, the Arcane Church had methods to turn it into a real god. Of course, their reasoning for it was 'All gods have existed since the start of time, waiting for offerings, and we just build bridges for the lost believers.' Anyway, it was very Superstitious, and the Great Mechanic Han was not supportive of it.

Therefore, other than the Spirit Emperor, which the Arcane Church believed in, they gathered countless believers from other religions. It was a sacred land shared by all religions in Galaxy. Those four statues were the religious totems of a religion where its gods were materialized. It had gathered prayers from its believers for a very long time.

Most of this information came from the various articles that Han Xiao had read. All three Universal Civilizations had unbelievable abilities. Of course, he was not concerned with such a large matter. His primary target was completing the mission.

...

After the celebration ended, Han Xiao bade farewell to Chen Xing and went back to the rented spaceship.

"What did you get?" Herlous was very curious.

"I got a 100,000 Enas job."

"Yo, that's quite a lot," Herlous said with a surprised tone. "Save a bit more money, and it will be enough to buy a spaceship."

"There's no need for that at the moment. The fuel, maintenance, and repairs are all costly."

Han Xiao waved his hands. He had to at least wait until his own technology was enough to repair spaceships before he bought one. Only then would he be able to save on the cost of it. In his previous life, the players only all had a spaceship in the very late versions. Before that, only large guilds were wealthy enough to have spaceships.

Intercepting spaceships of gray organizations and selling them to the spaceship manufacturers at cost price was a way to earn money as well. He could work with the large mercenary groups if there was an opportunity. However, in that case, he would not profit much, since the people with spaceships were the main combat power in a space battle... unless he was the one piloting.

After setting the destination, the spaceship took off.

As Han Xiao knew the location of the statues, he did not have to waste any time. One of the statues was buried under the ground on some desolate planet; he just had to retrieve it. The usual method of getting it was through intel and detailed search of the entire planet, but he skipped those difficult steps.

There were no twists and turns on the trip. Han Xiao landed on the planet, headed straight to the location, and dug out the third Mysterious Statue. Other than the time spent on locating the exact spot, he did not waste a single second. According to the players' experience, he had saved at least twenty days.

However, the last statue had an owner.

For this mission, they passed through many areas, returned to the Taralam Star Cluster, and entered the East River Star System, Star Zone 4.

"Planet Secret Blue. There is a civilization on the planet. Due to unknown reasons, the galactic civilization that found this planet did not contact the local civilization, nor did they expose their existence. This means that Planet Secret Blue does not know that they once had a guest from outer space, and they also don't know what the universe is like. Hence, they are complete natives.

"However, the geographical... astronomical location of this planet is special. It's located on the path of the objects spat out by a wormhole cluster. Therefore, a lot of space trash has been landing on their planet."

Han Xiao opened up the star map and introduced their destination to the others.

"The objects from outer space allowed them to derive technology beyond their level, but due to the difference in technological level, the knowledge that they gained from it was limited.

"At the same time, this trash made them certain about the existence of other civilizations in the universe, but that's all they know.

"What's worth mentioning is that this space trash from different civilizations showed Planet Secret Blue different systems. Hence, since the early stages of development, they have been researching on magic, technology, runes, crystals, and so on. Focusing on too many things at once might not be a good thing for a developing civilization. In conclusion, their technology standard has yet to reach the level that allows them to carry out interstellar travel."

Han Xiao tapped the screen.

"The last statue is one such 'space trash' that landed on this planet. It was seen as a product of a new technology by a certain local organization. That organization has since kept it under tight security."

"Boss, what are you planning to do?" one of the Volgas asked.

"Land directly and make the request. If they don't accept, we will beat them up until they do."

Han Xiao's tone was very decisive.

Herlous was stunned. "Is that a good way to do it? How about we communicate with them and give them some information about the universe in exchange for the statue?"

Han Xiao shook his head.

In his previous life, the players had thought this way as well.

Due to the difference in technology, Planet Secret Blue was divided into various organizations that fought each other. After choosing to negotiate, the organization that had the statue took themselves highly and made over the top requests. First, they asked for a ton of information about the universe, which the players agreed to. Then they asked for many advanced knowledges and technology, which the players agreed to. In the end, they even made the outrageous request of making the 'outer space guests' conquer other local organizations for them.

The players finally could not take it anymore. After beating them up, they finally gave up the statue. This proved that the prior negotiations were completely meaningless.

Facing people with such a mindset, if they did not show how big their fists were, they would think too highly of themselves.

Of course, if they could really satisfy that organization's requests, they would get the statue in the end too and even trigger more missions. However, to Han Xiao, violence was obviously the most convenient method.

Therefore, Han Xiao did not want to waste time and chose to directly airdrop and make the request.

...

Located in the Northwest of Planet Secret Blue, the City of Runes was a city based upon, as its name implied, rune technology. It was located in the middle of a forest. Its buildings had engravings of runes that shone in blue and white lights. The theme of the buildings was mostly tall, thin, light, and triangular. There were tall, square towers standing a certain distance from each other engraved with energy-absorbing runes. Those towers were the energy cores of the city. There was no wall at the edge of the city, and the buildings gradually became shorter the further they were from the center, extending all the way into the forest.

Many years ago, some space trash had landed there, and on it were the secrets of the rune technology. The pioneers had derived some technology from it and slowly built that city. It was now one of the largest forces on Planet Secret Blue.

It was late at night.

In the forest more than forty miles away from the City of Runes, dozens of people constructed a temporary camp. The bonfire rune emitted a stable red light, giving out warmth. The people sat around it. They were wearing leather clothes and armor engraved in runes. The border of the camp was covered in green beast repelling runes, stopping the beasts and insects crawling in the night from getting close.

"Captain, how much can these goods sell for on the black market in the City of Runes?" A young man rubbed his hands together in anticipation.

The captain was a short and skinny man that looked somewhat like a mouse. He chuckled and said, "Someone is secretly purchasing space trash in the City of Runes. These goods we gathered would at least make us 8,000 Feces."

This was a smuggler group that sold space trash. Every once in a while, the trash from wormholes would land at different locations on the planet. Such trash had research value, and every organization was collecting them. However, they would definitely miss some of it. Hence, the space trash black market was born to purchase these objects from outer space. The smugglers were groups of people that searched for space trash and sold them on the black market.

At this time, they suddenly heard the sound of something breaking the sound barrier. The sound got louder and louder, cutting through the silence of the night like a sharp knife. They stood up and looked over hastily. A burning meteor appeared in the night sky and was heading toward them.

The smugglers were way too familiar with this sound. Surprise appeared on their faces.

"Space trash!"

The burning meteor approached very quickly and dashed right above their heads, stirring up a strong wind, shaking the forest, and rustling the leaves. Then, the meteor landed nearby, crushing some trees and making a loud noise.

Boom!

The ground trembled, and they staggered, almost falling.

Fire and smoke rose from the crash site.

"We got lucky!" The captain was overjoyed. "The landing site of this space trash is near us. We can take it away before the search team of the City of Runes arrives!"

The group of smugglers acted very quickly and arrived at the scene. Before them was a pit covered in thick smoke. In the middle of it was an egg-shaped metal object about 2.5 meters tall.

"What is this?" The smugglers sized it up curiously.

"Don't stand there, quickly move it away." The captain hurried.

Just as they were about the approach, a loud bang came from the forest, and a small pit appeared on the floor before the smuggler captain.

"Everyone, do not come closer!"

A deep voice came from the other side of the forest. Another group of people appeared in the forest. They were wearing metal armor, equipped with grenades and rifles. One of them was wearing infrared sniper goggles, and the muzzle of the sniper in his hands was still smoking. The sound earlier had indeed been the sound of a sniper shot.

"Troops of Iron Fire Castle!" The face of the group of smugglers changed.

The Iron Fire Castle was one of the large organizations on Planet Secret Blue. They had the technology of metal, gunpowder, and machinery. Their mechanical battle vehicles were the most dreaded on the battlefield.

They were not the only ones. With more rustling in the forest, more teams were approaching. This new 'space trash' was like a vortex that attracted all the teams in the forest.

Those teams had very different expressions. What they all had was alert and hostility toward each other.

The other organizations would always have operation teams in the territories of other organizations to snatch any space trash that landed near their territory, preventing opposing organizations from getting new opportunities.

If they could not snatch it away, they would... destroy it!

Chapter 447: Even We Will Have the Day When We Are Seen as Aliens

Iron Fire Castle, Arcane Institution, Crystal Mountain, Purple Sea Islands, Card Summit...

Five teams from different organizations surrounded the airdrop cabin and confronted each other. The smugglers at the side saw this and immediately backed off into the forest, observing the situation in fear.

Every time space trash fell, it would become a treasure that the various organizations wanted to get their hands on no matter what. This one had landed near the City of Runes, so the teams present knew that time was scarce. They started fighting immediately without saying anything.

Tuk tuk tuk!

The Iron Fire Castle warriors started to fire first, and bullets rained down from their rifles onto the other teams. The dark forest was lit up by the gunshots.

Gunpowder and machinery were technologies unique to the Iron Fire Castle, so most people dodged and avoided the bullets.

That was, except for the Card Summit warriors.

These people were wearing a strange device on their arms that looked like bronze plate armor. Its shape was similar to a disk, and at the side of it were many card slots. This was the core technology of the Card Summit warriors—Battle Card Disk. These people took out a shining card from the middle of the disk and placed it into the card slot. Then, something happened.

Hum!

A light, blue energy shield gathered before the disk, and bullets hit the shield and caused ripples. The shield stopped all the attacks.

Clearly, this was the product of another technology. The outer space object acquired by the Card Summit had the technology to store, transmit, and use energy through cards.

Boom boom boom!

At the same time, the warriors from the other organizations moved as well. It turned into a scrimmage of colorful energy and continuous growls.

Grenades blasted through arcane shields, sharp claws pierced metal muzzles, and sparks splashed all over the place.

Materialized spears from cards penetrated enhanced bodies, spilling boiling blood.

Radiation beams from crystals shattered Battle Card Disks, broken cards exploded into pieces, and the energy turned into an impact wave and splashed the black soil on the ground.

These were all elite warriors from their organizations. Different battle tactics clashed against each other.

No matter who got close to the 'space trash' in the middle, they would face attacks from everyone else immediately. They restrained each other, and the situation was in a stalemate.

Wu!

Suddenly, the sound of a horn came from afar. Their faces changed.

"That's the warrior horn of the City of Runes. Their search team is going to arrive soon."

Iron Fire Castle's sniper adjusted his scope and saw a huge group of creatures approaching rapidly.

"There's not enough time. What we are not able to acquire can't be acquired by the City of Runes. Ready the explosives and destroy it!" the Iron Fire Castle captain yelled. His subordinates took out all sorts of grenades and bombs and threw them toward the airdrop cabin.

The other organizations did the same and attacked the airdrop cabin, thinking the same thing.

Boom!

The sound of an explosion trembled the night, and the firelight mixed with the black smoke covered the airdrop cabin up.

"Continue!"

Space trash that could land on planets were usually very tough. Even so, they wanted to destroy it as much as they could so the enemy organizations would not be able to research it.

Whoosh!

Just as these people were preparing for the second round of focus fire, a loud, clear sound of pressurized air expanding was heard. The hatch slowly slid open. They saw the outline of a person in the fog. Then, an unfamiliar voice appeared in their language.

"Are you guys done?"

Wafting away the fog, Han Xiao walked out in large steps. He landed with his body and did not activate the Void Dragon mechanical suit. This awful airdrop cabin had trembled so badly that it had given him a headache. Furthermore, the system had frozen after the clash, so he could not even open the hatch. It was a shame of the airdrop industry.

He had needed quite some time to restart the system, and he had heard all the clanking sound from the battle outside.

Although the various organizations in Planet Secret Blue had so-called 'Supernatural' weapons, their technology standard was very low in his eyes. It had very limited power, so even if he did not wear a mechanical suit, it would be very hard for them to break through his defenses.

Han Xiao did not care about the heated battle outside, but these people wanted to destroy the airdrop cabin, which was unacceptable. He had to pay compensation if rented properties were damaged!

The moment Han Xiao appeared, the whole scene froze.

It was deadly silent.

These warriors gazed at Han Xiao like they were frozen, and shocked expressions were fixed on their faces. Even the smugglers who watched from the side opened their mouth widely in disbelief.

"A—alien!"

Past space trash had all been dead objects.

This was the first alive creature!

An alien from the boundless universe!

Horror, shock, greed, and countless emotions flashed past these warriors' face.

Everyone's breath became heavier, and the same thought appeared in their minds.

"Have to get the alien! He's too valuable!"

At this time, rapid footsteps appeared from the forest. A large group of City of Runes guards finally arrived at the scene. There were two hundred of them wearing their standard guard armor, one hundred melee guards and one hundred bow guards. The surface of their weapons and armor had engravings of runes that enhanced their attack, defense, and physical capabilities.

The warriors of Iron Fire Castle and other organizations' face changed. "It's the elite guerrilla group of City of Runes. We took too long!"

"Lay down your weapons!" the captain of the City of Runes team yelled loudly. He looked at the airdrop cabin, then looked at Han Xiao. With a little bit of thinking, he came to the same shocking conclusion as everyone else. He decisively ordered, "Surround them and evict the enemies. This is the territory of City of Runes; no one can snatch what is ours!"

The warriors of the other organizations quickly backed off with grave faces. There were too few of them.

According to tradition, they had to destroy whatever they could not obtain. However, an alien was too valuable, so many people could not make a decision. Should they really kill the alien? There were no prior examples to this. Maybe they should not do it...

The Iron Fire Castle captain's eyes were menacing, and murderous intent rose in his heart. He clenched his teeth and ordered, "Never mind all of that, our duty is to execute orders. Since we can't get that alien, we can't let the City of Runes get him. Fire!"

The sniper aimed his gun at Han Xiao's forehead and quickly pulled the trigger.

"Sh*t!" The captain of the City of Runes guards' face changed dramatically.

Bang!

The sound of a gunshot echoed.

They hurriedly looked at the alien.

Han Xiao turned his head around. There was a white mark on his forehead still emitting a faint smoke, but the bullet had not even penetrated his skin.

On Planet Aquamarine, even Grade C Supers could face firearms with no problem, not to mention Grade B. Although he was a Mechanic, his health and resistance even exceeded Pugilists, so such low firearms had no chance of penetrating his defenses.

Shock and terror appeared on everyone else's faces.

They only then realized that this person in front of them was not a dead object for them to grab if they wanted to but a mysterious guest from outer space.

His threat level was unknown!

"Zero damage." Han Xiao touched his forehead and raised his eyebrows. He could not even be bothered to wear his mechanical suit. With a stream of Mechanical Force, dozens of Black Panther mechanical beasts appeared and pounced at the people.

Everyone was his attack target, whether they were the warriors from the various organizations or the City of Runes guards.

The situation completely changed in an instant.

The mechanical beasts culled the people fiercely. They tried to fight back in a panic, but their weapons only left sparks on the mechanical beasts' armor. It was a completely one-sided battle; the mechanical beasts demolished everyone.

Whoosh!

A few sharp blade tails pierced into the sniper's chest, and blood gushed out from his mouth. Before he could scream, the mechanical beasts around him pulled their tail and tore him to pieces.

The pungent smell of blood spread in the air.

"These are all machines!" the Iron Fire Castle captain screamed in disbelief. The technology that the alien was using had the same root as their technology. The strength of the mechanical beasts astounded their soul.

The battle lasted less than ten minutes before everyone else fell onto the ground. The floor was covered in blood, and the forest was filled with screams of agony. Other than the Iron Fire Castle warriors, Han Xiao did not kill anyone else. After all, he needed someone to spread the word.

The smugglers in the forest dodged a bullet. They were horrified, and their legs were shivering; many of them could not even remain standing.

The alien defeated two to three hundred elite warriors in the blink of an eye, how terrifying!

The chaotic situation was suppressed—these local warriors were all defeated.

The mechanical beasts returned to Han Xiao, folded into compressed orbs, and rolled into Han Xiao's pockets automatically. This incomprehensible scene shocked the people once again.

Han Xiao looked around and coldly said, "Let me introduce myself. I'm a mercenary from space, coming to your planet to look for a wooden statue. According to my senses, that statue is in that city not far away. If you're willing to hand it over, I can give you some information about the universe in exchange. If you reject, I will take it myself. Time is limited, so I hope to hear your response before tomorrow morning."

Through the translator, his words became Planet Secret Blue's language. The people were shocked. Seeing that Han Xiao had no intention of slaughtering them, they had no choice but to suppress their confused thoughts, stand up carefully, and back off, stumbling with panic.

The warriors from different organizations left in their own groups and did not fight again. They were in a hurry to report the situation; that was the most important matter at the moment.

The smugglers also ran away, and Han Xiao did not bother with them.

The political structure of this planet is very underdeveloped. One technology creates a city, and a city is equal to a regime. My appearance to them is huge news. As they don't have any contact with the galaxy, there is no systematic Super knowledge here, only the individual power systems or incompletely information. The individual strength level is very weak. The strongest is only Grade C, and there are not even as many of them as there are on Planet Aquamarine.

With his Grade B strength, it was more than enough to crush this entire planet. Although Grade B was rather common in the universe and not too difficult to kill, it was almost invincible on lower level planets. The only advantage that Planet Secret Blue had on him was numbers.

Han Xiao smiled—Mechanics were most unafraid of being outnumbered.

However, Han Xiao did not ignore the possibility of some organizations on Planet Secret Blue having some powerful weapons.

"After hearing about me, the best result will, of course, be the City of Runes giving up the statue. However, that's unlikely." Han Xiao shook his head. He knew what kind of attitude these people had—proud and arrogant. They would most likely not compromise.

After waiting for an entire day, he would most likely not face smiles the following morning but a siege from their army.

However, this was exactly Han Xiao's plan. He planned to give one night to the City of Runes to gather an army so that he could destroy their confidence once and for all, saving a lot of time. Enemies being overconfident was his favorite thing to see.

Herlous and the others were still on the spaceship; him landing alone would make it easier to terrorize the enemies.

Although he had three statues and could locate the last statue, so sneaking in and stealing it seemed to be more convenient, Han Xiao did not want to go through so much trouble.

After all, he would still end up facing them alone.

Finally, this time, he did not have to use so much of his brain and could solve the problem with his fists.

If I remember correctly, winning against a siege of tens of thousands of people will trigger an achievement ability called [One Against the World], Han Xiao suddenly recalled.

He looked at the mess around him, walked up to the top of the airdrop cabin, closed his eyes, and started to wait.

...

That night, the intel of an alien landing quickly spread into the organizations of the alive warriors.

This was the first alien that had landed there!

Alive!

The City of Runes was astonished!

The whole of Planet Secret Blue trembled!

This was definitely going to be a sleepless night.

Chapter 448: The Siege

Han Xiao's arrival stirred up a storm.

Lord of Runes was the ruler of City of Runes. He had gone to sleep early but was awakened by this news. As soon as he heard, he quickly put on his formal clothes and hosted an emergency meeting.

The high officials in the city hurried to the hall in the central tower. They were all awakened from their sleep, and some were even wiping the sleep from their eyes.

Outside the balcony of the tower was the night sky. The moonlight passed through the stone railings and left a shadow on the floor.

The hall was illuminated by runes. Lord of Runes was an old and wrinkled man, but he was wearing a luxurious, elegant robe and holding a staff. The expression on his face was strange.

"Everyone knows the situation. An alien who calls himself a mercenary has landed and is looking for an outer space object in our hands. According to the intel, he used some kind of mechanical beasts and defeated two hundred Rune Guards with ease. He's now in the forest outside waiting for our response. What do you guys think of this?"

"Aliens have a lot of information about the universe. He's saying that he's willing to exchange for the statue with some information. I think we can consider it..." an official said. His position was similar to the King's Hand. "However, the object that the alien wants is definitely valuable. From his perspective, maybe he is making use of the fact that we don't understand its value and wants to exchange it for some simple information. I feel that we can't give in easily; it's best to check the statue first."

"You're right." The Lord of Runes nodded.

Very soon, a guard brought the statue over from the inventory. It had landed on the planet many years ago and had existed since the last Lord of Runes. As they could not figure out the statue's secrets, and most of the researchers had mental issues after being in contact with it for too long, it had been sealed in the inventory and listed as an unsolvable outer space object.

Due to the alien's request, they took the statue out once again.

This object was definitely not ordinary. The Lord of Runes was not very willing to give it up this easily, despite not being able to uncover its secrets. This was a treasure that the alien crossed unimaginable distances to retrieve after all.

"The alien gave us till tomorrow. We only have one night to consider." The Lord of Runes squinted.

"If we can capture the alien, not only will we be able to analyze the body of a space race, but we can obtain all of his knowledge. This is an opportunity to rise above all the other organizations." This man was the general of the army. He was wearing heavy armor and his tone was very aggressive. "He's just one man."

"He might have friends. Plus, he could land on our planet, which means he's not easy to deal with. I don't think we should fight with him," someone else said.

The officials were divided into two sides. One side felt it was better to accept the alien's request; the other side was very greedy and wanted to capture the alien to garner all the benefits. The latter side had more supporters. As they had seen a lot of objects from outer space, they were not completely ignorant of the outer world; therefore, they did not have a lot of respect but more curiosity.

The technology involved in these outer space objects was too advanced for Planet Secret Blue to figure out, so they could only learn the tip of the iceberg. However, ignorance often caused arrogance. Furthermore, the entire Planet Secret Blue did not have any idea of the strength level of the galactic warriors. Han Xiao coming alone gave them meaningless courage.

The supporters of conflict suggested tactics against the alien.

"We have one night, which is more than enough to gather about ten thousand guards and quietly surround that area. We can use the forbidden Runes; these most elite warriors will be able to endure it. Combined with the large rune weapons, it is more than enough to defeat the alien. He definitely will not expect us to attack him."

The Lord of Runes' eyes flickered as he swayed between peace and greed. In the end, he made the decision—reject the alien's request. If they could capture the alien, all the benefits would belong to them.

He looked around the officials and said, "Gather the troops and bring out our strongest weapons. This is a once in a thousand years opportunity. Being too careful will only waste it. We have to capture the alien no matter what."

The first beam of sunlight appeared in the sky, penetrating the forest, and landed on Han Xiao, who was sitting still like a rock.

Han Xiao's eyelashes moved, and he opened his eyes. The refreshing, cooling morning fog landed on his skin and left a tint of wetness, making Han Xiao feel slightly energized after not sleeping for the night.

"It's almost daytime. The enemies should arrive soon."

A few droplets of water landed on his face. He looked up at the sky and raised his eyebrows. "Looks like it's going to rain."

Rain poured very soon, pitter-pattering on the leaves.

Han Xiao stood up and looked around the forest. The swaying trees gave out a strange atmosphere. In the dark forest, he sensed a faint, murderous intent mixed with the dampness.

Suddenly, a pressure landed on his body and slowed his movements. Han Xiao realized that he had to use more strength to remain at his usual speed, which was the effect of some kind of gravity rune.

"Just as I expected, they chose war."

Han Xiao nodded in his mind. The organizations on that planets were all like calves that would not learn their lesson before receiving a heavy beating. People with no idea of the situation would dream of controlling and gaining every benefit before them.

Fear made people cautious. Normal civilizations would make contact with the aliens carefully, but that did not mean all natives would. There were some that were humble and some that were greedy. Some savage native civilizations would even think that the aliens were demons and choose to fight them with their entire nations, which had happened countless times before.

The greedier they were, the more they liked to play with fire.

The enormous Rune Guard army appeared from the forest in all directions. One thousand rune bows were aimed at him, and one thousand melee guards were slowly approaching. These two thousand troops were just the frontlines; the majority of the troops were still deeply hidden in the forest. The City of Runes had sent out seventy percent of all their troops.

"Alien, you should be able to understand our language. I'm the commander of the City of Runes Guard Army, Backzas. You're surrounded. We will not harm you, provided you don't resist meaninglessly and follow us."

The expressionless commander in gorgeous rune armor stood in the middle of the army and spoke in a cold tone. He was the general that had strongly suggested to fight the previous night. The whole night, he had been gathering the army and approaching the forest quietly. The encirclement had formed, and even the founder of the War Runes would not have a chance—that was the strongest person in the history of the City of Runes.

The soldiers looked at the alien with curiosity. He did not seem very terrifying.

"Apparently, I have no choice but to take a trip to your city personally, such an unwise choice." Han Xiao was regretful on the surface but delighted in his heart.

Hearing this, the rune warriors became nervous. However, when they looked at the countless comrades around them, they felt confident again.

Backzas' face became stiff.

Is the battle starting?

After gathering suggestions the previous night, they had designed many tactics for the possible methods that the alien might have. They were very prepared. Backzas recalled these tactics and felt assured.

The forest terrain was a little bit disadvantageous for Han Xiao. He looked around and faced at the City of Runes' direction.

I shall... head there directly!

Chapter 449: One Against the World!

Clank!

Dragging a trail of electric sparks, the compressed orbs quickly rolled out on the ground in a hundred-meter radius. With the sound of mechanical gears moving, artilleries appeared instantly and started firing at the army in all directions.

Countless troops fell in an instant!

"Hide!" Backzas yelled. He hid behind a tree, thinking that it could block the bullets.

However, the next moment, a few high-caliber Blazing Armor Penetrating Bullets blasted this tree into bits and shattered Backzas' armor. He spat out blood from his mouth and screamed in agony before falling to the ground. Clenching his teeth, he growled, "Fire!"

Pow!

A thousand glowing rune arrows were shot at a single target.

Facing the countless arrows, Han Xiao slightly raised his finger. Twelve Sonic Spheres flew out and surround him, emitting sonic waves that turned into impact waves, deflecting all the arrows onto the ground.

Han Xiao took a step forward and headed toward the City of Runes. The first group of troops was buried by the infinite bullets and cannons.

There were both Gunpowder Artilleries and Electromagnetic Artilleries. The bullets used by the Gunpowder Artilleries were all special bullets such as Incendiary Bullets, Penetrating Bullets, grenades, gas bombs, and so on. There were also bullets enchanted by the Volga brothers such as Frozen Bullets, Oil Bullets, and others that caused all sorts of debuffs.

Boom boom boom!

The trees fell under the crossfire, opening up a path covered in the remains of the trees that were still burning.

The light rain was devoured by the flames and turned into a fog, making the field of sight unclear. The troops could only see the shadow of a person slowly walking forward in the mist.

The direction of the fallen trees showed Han Xiao's location.

The large army finally arrived, and tens of thousands of Rune Guards charged forward under command. However, the area with a five hundred-meter radius of Han Xiao was almost a death zone, and anyone that got close would have their armor shattered and their body penetrated by bullets, no matter how many there were. No one could remain standing in that area.

Heavily injured soldiers filled up the path behind Han Xiao. Their wails were almost louder than the sound of cannons firing.

Han Xiao was not bloodthirsty. The level difference between him and these normal soldiers was too huge. They each only gave him one experience point anyway, so Han Xiao was too lazy to kill them all. For those who got hit in their vital spots, they were just unlucky. Although killing was not a hobby of his, Han Xiao did not feel pressurized by it at all.

Killing some people is normal. Back then when I infiltrated the Germinal Organization...

Never mind, a real mind does not mention his past glory days.

Finally, those soldiers hesitated and did not dare get too close. It was a completely meaningless sacrifice. They were afraid.

This time, three hundred special soldiers stepped out of the crowd. They were wearing black armor that had ten times more complicated rune engravings. All of their eyes were filled with veins like they were enduring enormous pain. They were the strongest warriors of the City of Runes—Black Armor Guards. Their rune armor was the highest level equipment; only trained ace warriors could use it, yet it would still cause irreversible damage to their body. Only one in fifty elite warriors would be selected as a Black Armor Guard. One Black Armor Guard could fight one hundred enemies.

Clank!

The Black Armor Guards charged into the rain of bullets. The highest-level armor finally stopped the bullets. The City of Runes army saw hope again.

Enduring the pain, the three hundred of them unsheathed their rune swords and charged toward Han Xiao fiercely.

Han Xiao's face was calm. He snapped his fingers, and tens of mechanical beasts stampeded forward and restrained these elite warriors. Then, Han Xiao switched the Electromagnetic Artilleries to manual control, multiplying their power. He focused on the Black Armor Guards and defeated them one after another with ease.

Han Xiao's combat style at the moment was almost invincible when facing a large number of enemies unless they were at the same grade as him. The most important thing was that they were cheap.

The ace warriors of City of Runes, the fighters that had high hopes of the army on their shoulders, were defeated without making any impact. Backzas' heart sank when he saw this.

The power of the alien was beyond their expectations!

A deep sense of regret appeared in their hearts, but it was more than too late. They would not know how much they overestimated themselves till they faced such a tragic defeat.

Backzas was held onto his pierced legs and yelled, "Activate the Rune Catapults!"

Four weapons that looked like huge cannons were dragged out and aimed at Han Xiao from afar. These were the trump card of the City of Runes. The design originated from an almost completely broken weapon from an advanced rune civilization. The City of Runes had yet to gain its full technology, and the replica that they had made only had a hundredth of its power, but it was more than enough to be their strongest weapon. The entire City of Runes only had ten of them, and they had taken out four to use as the trump card against the alien.

This was their final resort; they were worried that they might kill the alien due to how strong those weapons were, but they could not be bothered about that anymore. If they still had the mindset of wanting to capture the alien alive, Backzas could already see their ending of being completely defeated.

Hum!

The four catapults shot out enormous energy arrows with a high pitch sound, carrying their last hope.

"These things are not too bad."

Han Xiao pressed his hands together. Mechanical Force gushed out, and a colorful, bubble-like energy shield appeared, covering an area of three meters around him.

The energy arrows hit the bubble, but there were no explosions; they slid on the surface of the bubble and flew away, blasting ten-meter-wide pits on the ground hundreds of meters away.

[Skewed Energy Field Generator]. This was the equipment that Han Xiao had created using [Advanced Energy Theory]. It could skew energy attacks to a certain extent. He had purchased this knowledge during the nine months of doing hiring missions.

"These four cannons are a little bit threatening to me. One shot would probably cost me about 200 health." Han Xiao looked at these catapults. They were quite far away and exceeded the shooting range of his artilleries. Han Xiao nodded. A specially made set of compressed orbs flew out and turned into machinery parts midair.

These parts combined and connected with each other. Very soon, a medium-sized Electromagnetic Rail Cannon landed beside him. It was almost two men tall.

Han Xiao sat in the control seat, quickly locked onto the target, and started charging. The blinding electric currents gathered in the cannon's barrel.

Hum!

A blue electric beam crossed a thousand meters and penetrated three Rune Catapults instantly; everything in its path was melted.

This was the Giant War Cannon Style that Han Xiao rarely used. It was usually Cannon Master equipment specifically used to deal damage. This medium-sized Electromagnetic Rail Cannon was very powerful, and he spent quite some time to build it. It was used to deal single target damage, and every shot cost tens of Enas. It was equipment that he had specifically made to deal huge damage together with [Flaming Will]. In one hiring mission in the past, the local organizations had to fight against a space monster that had more than 50,000 health. Han Xiao had gotten lucky with [Flaming Will] and dealt five times the usual damage. At the same time, he had triggered True Damage from [Lethal Shot], dealing 14,885 damage in one shot. It was still his highest single damage record.

"What power is this?" Backzas' lips were pale, and his face was filled with horror.

The alien was outrageously powerful; the tactics that they had discussed the night before all became jokes.

This shot was the last straw that shattered their hopes. The City of Runes army finally collapsed; they threw away their armor and escaped in all directions. Some even sat frozen on the ground with a blank mind, even forgetting to run away.

You have defeated enemies outnumbering you more than 10,000 to 1 alone.

You have received [One Against the World] Achievement Ability.

[One Against the World]: When in battle, if you're alone, you will receive an 11% increase in all attributes.

"A rather good Achievement Ability." Han Xiao nodded. Some abilities could be obtained through hidden challenges—they were called Achievement Abilities. Most of them had quite good effects.

[One Against the World] was obviously an ability suited for lone wolves, and it was very useful to players. As long as they had this ability, they would receive free attribute boosts when hunting other players. The only problem was that the method of getting it was not so player-friendly. For the players to face 10,000 enemies alone, it was not as easy as it was for Han Xiao.

Seeing the defeated and escaping enemies, Han Xiao collected his weapons and continued walking toward the City of Runes.

He believed that this battle was more than enough for the City of Runes to realize the difference in their strength.

The Lord of Runes did not sleep that night; he was anxiously waiting for the battle report.

Only half an hour had passed after the decided time of starting the battle, and the battle report came from the frontlines. The Lord of Runes fell onto the ground and sat there in terror.

One man against an army of tens of thousands of soldiers.

The army was overwhelmingly defeated!

The target was completely unharmed!

The face of all the officials present changed dramatically. Horror had crept onto their faces.

Chapter 450: Golden but Poor!

The City of Runes was surrounded by forests. Looking down from the high places in the city, the white city was surrounded by a dense green. However, now, a conspicuous, empty path appeared in the forest.

Smoke rose in the rain, and the residents of the City of Runes could see it clearly from afar.

"What happened there?"

"The faint sound of explosions kept coming from that direction earlier. Could the Iron Fire Castle have launched an attack?"

"I woke up to arrange the goods before sunrise, and do you know what I saw? Groups of Rune Guards walking into the forest in that exact direction."

Seeing the smoke from far away, the City of Runes' residents wondered what had happened. The intel regarding an alien appearing had yet to spread.

"It's him... it must be him..." In the crowd, a short and skinny man was terrified. The people around him noticed his reaction and guessed that this person might know something, so they asked him about it.

"That's an alien! He landed outside the city last night. He speaks our language and made a request to the Lord of Runes..." This person was the head of smugglers from the previous night. He poured out everything that he had seen. More and more people gathered around him to listen, and they could not believe it.

"A battle definitely broke out there. This means that the Lord of Runes did not accept the alien's request." The head of smugglers gulped. The crowd exchanged looks and saw panic in each other's eyes.

This time, a commotion broke out in the distance. A Rune Guard ran back with all his might, his face still covered in the cannon ashes. He kept looking back with terror like there was some kind of monster behind him. Then, more and more defeated soldiers ran back after him.

This scene gave the residents a very bad feeling. A middle-aged man realized that his brother who served in the army was running back as well. He hastily caught him and asked him what had happened.

"The people above rejected the alien's request. They wanted to capture the alien... The army of tens of thousands of soldiers lost to the enemy who was alone. Thousands of us died, but we couldn't even touch him. It's terrifying. Everyone is escaping. You guys should too! He's coming to the city!" Fear was still lingering in this guard. He quickly explained the situation and ran away frantically.

The people were shocked, panicked, and outraged. They almost wanted to beat up the Lord of Runes—why did he not accept the alien's request? Why did he have to mess with the alien and bring danger to the entire city?

This time, a group of soldiers walked out from the direction of the central tower. They pushed away the residents and cleared a path. The Lord of Runes rushed to the edge of the city together with a group of officials, and the guard behind them was holding a strange sculpture.

The alien was going to enter the city very soon, so there was no time to escape. The Lord of Runes had no choice but to take the statue and ask for mercy. According to the intel from the frontlines, the alien did not chase the running army and was not hurt. Maybe the alien did not like killing. What he was doing was a total bet. His greed toward the alien had completely vanished, and he only hoped that the alien would leave after taking the statue and forgive them.

Seeing this, some residents followed behind. Along the way, more and more people joined in and formed a wave behind the Lord of Runes, wanting to see what happened with their own eyes.

Thousands of people came to the village at the edge of the city. They looked in the direction of the forest anxiously.

The Lord of Runes kept wiping off his sweat, apprehensive.

Ta, ta, ta!

The footsteps on leaves and soil came from the forest and gradually got closer. As the distance between them shortened, the residents and the Lord of Runes felt more and more uneasy. Not long after, Han Xiao finally walked out of the forest and came to the edge of the City of Runes.

As soon as he appeared, countless eyes focused on him with curiosity, fear, worry, and other emotions.

Seeing the large crowd and the group of people who clearly were government officials, Han Xiao's eyebrows twitched. His lips curled up as he could guess what their plan was. They had realized that they had messed with someone that they should not have messed with, and now they were offering the statue in exchange for forgiveness and mercy.

But isn't it too late to yield?

The Lord of Runes took the statue from the hands of the guard, walked forward hastily, observed Han Xiao cautiously, and said with a shivering voice, "Thi—this should be what you are looking for..."

Not knowing what the alien was thinking, the Lord of Runes did not dare say anything else. Although he was a ruler, he had absolutely no confidence in front of someone that could easily destroy an army of tens of thousands of soldiers.

Although Planet Secret Blue did not have a proper Super system, there were some that had discovered the path of Supers. The War Rune Church was the gathering ground of these people in the City of Runes and had a high position. However, even their founder could only barely face one thousand Rune Guards, and it had taken him a very long time to defeat them. The efficiency of killing was completely on a different level from the alien before them.

After the battle report came, the Lord of Runes had wanted to request the warriors of the War Rune Church to stop the alien but had immediately been rejected. The War Rune Church knew that there was nothing that they could do, so they did not even give the Lord of Runes a chance to speak... despite them receiving huge funds from him every year.

Han Xiao touched the statue. The information on the interface was correct, so this was indeed the last lost statue.

When he reached out to take the statue, the Lord of Runes' body shivered visibly. His eyes met with Han Xiao's eyes, and he lowered his head in horror.

Glancing through the nervous crowd, Han Xiao said calmly, "Don't worry, we don't kill innocents."

Hearing Han Xiao's words, they breathed a sigh of relief.

"By the way, who's your ruler?"

The residents pointed at the Lord of Runes simultaneously. Before the Lord of Runes could relax, his face turned stiff, and he gave a very forced smile.

"You're the one that sent the troops to attack me?" Han Xiao asked. "Why didn't you accept my request?"

The Lord of Runes shivered and did not dare to respond.

"According to the fair-trade rule of the mercenaries, you have attacked me. If you want to settle it, you have to pay compensation." Han Xiao narrowed his eyes. "What do you want to pay in exchange for your life?"

The Lord of Runes was covered in cold sweat. He was both furious and anguished. This was the first time that he had been threatened—who would dare speak to him that way normally?

Plus, you killed and injured so many of our men, yet you're the one asking for compensation?

"We have a lot of outer space objects..." The Lord of Runes clenched his teeth in his mind. He had no choice but to endure it and ask his subordinate to make a list of their inventory to give to Han Xiao.

Han Xiao scanned through roughly and was a little disappointed. The local currency of Planet Secret Blue was completely meaningless to him, and the only things that were acceptable were the outer space objects. However, the inventory of the City of Runes was really filled with trash. Most of it was trash. A small portion were products from rune civilizations that were close to rubbish and had basically no value. After looking through the list from head to toe, he came to a conclusion—looking at the list was a complete waste of time as these people were extremely poor!

Han Xiao threw the list away and shook his head. "These things can't buy your life. Sorry, I will have to make you pay for your mistake."

The Lord of Runes' face changed drastically.

Chapter 451: Superstitions Cannot Save the World

Is he going to kill me‽

The Lord of Runes looked behind him. Not even one guard stepped forward, and the officials were hiding far away, not daring to show their faces.

The Lord of Runes panicked. As resolving himself, he clenched his teeth. Suddenly, he grabbed the statue, took a few steps back, and held it before him. He then took a rune sword from the guard, pointed its tip at the statue, and fiercely yelled, "Don't do anything, or I will destroy what you have been looking for!"

Han Xiao stood still and expressed that the Lord of Runes could do as he wished.

"Destroy it then. If you are actually able to, I will spare your life," Han Xiao said in a mocking tone.

This statue looked like it was made of wood, but it did not even break after falling from space. How could it possibly be destroyed by a sword? The Lord of Runes had lost his mind.

Bang!

A bloody hole appeared on Lord of Runes' forehead. This old man's eyes opened wide in hatred, then they turned lifeless as he collapsed.

The people of the City of Runes trembled. They felt a mixed feeling watching their ruler being killed right before their eyes, but they were not very angry. The sense of national belonging was not very strong in Planet Secret Blue as the residents often migrated. Besides, the Lord of Runes was not very liked by his people.

Han Xiao holstered his gun and picked up the statue. After some blood spilled on it, the already strangely shaped statue felt creepy.

"Let's go." Han Xiao looked up at the sky.

Just as the people were confused as to what he was doing, the buzzing sound of an engine came from the sky. A spaceship quickly passed through the atmosphere and came to the sky hundreds of meters above Han Xiao. It shot out a blue beam and shrouded Han Xiao.

Han Xiao's body rose as he was sucked into the spaceship before countless pairs of eyes.

On the ground, the people in the City of Runes were dazed.

"Is that the tool that the space people use to travel?"

"It looks like a piece of machinery. Could the Iron Fire Castle's technology be the most correct one?"

Hu!

While they were discussing, the spaceship turned around. Blue fire shot out from its tail thrusters, and it broke through the sound barrier in an instant, disappearing.

The alien left just like that, but the City of Runes and other organizations on Planet Secret Blue had yet to recover from its impact.

Knowing what had happened to the Lord of Runes, the other organizations were glad that the alien had landed near the City of Runes instead of near them, or they would have ended up the same way.

When receiving the information on the previous night, these people had still been holding urgent meetings on how to deal with the alien. Many of them wanted to snatch the alien away from City of Runes. In their eyes, the City of Runes would most likely capture the alien successfully. At this time, the ones that made the most aggressive suggestions and yelled the loudest last night were all covered in cold sweat.

Since Han Xiao arrived, only around ten hours had passed, but the huge impact that he had brought to Planet Secret Blue deeply changed this planet's perspective on the world. Their first contact with an alien was not peaceful, and there was no deep communication, but the influence that Han Xiao had on them was incalculable.

After all the organizations were shocked by Han Xiao's strength, they looked forward to having that power. The warriors that explored ways to train themselves saw Han Xiao as a goal. They researched his actions when he fought the army, hoping to find a method to become stronger.

As they saw how strong a galactic mercenary was, the various organizations on Planet Secret Blue woke up to a certain extent. They felt that their internal battle was useless. Maybe in the eyes of those people in space, they were like ants fighting each other. This fueled their will to maintain peace and stop the battles.

Because of this, this incident was recorded in the history of Planet Secret Blue. The philosophers analyzed the impact that the alien had on society from different perspectives.

At the same time, because they saw that the interstellar spaceship was a piece of machinery, the technology in Planet Secret Blue finally showed signs of uniting. Iron Fire Castle's machinery technology became the 'truth' that was agreed upon by all the organizations. They felt that this was the future direction that a civilization should take. Hence, they stopped research on other systems and focused on technology. Under the pressure from all the other organizations, Iron Fire Castle had no choice but to share all their knowledge.

Since then, most of the people on Planet Secret Blue became materialists. Their social structure changed without them noticing.

Although Han Xiao had been there for trouble, the influence that he had was very positive. Planet Secret Blue learned a lesson from their ignorance and wrong decisions, and they had a new understanding of how strong the people in space were, so they became more cautious. When they finally came into contact with a galactic civilization, the organizations on Planet Secret Blue were extremely glad that the first alien on their planet was a mercenary who gave them a chance. If they messed with a higher-level civilization when they were so arrogant, later... no, they would not even have had a 'later'.

Those were all changes that happened after the Great Mechanic Han left, which he was not concerned about.

After gathering all the statues, Han Xiao did not notify Chen Xing immediately but went to the nearest Star System civilization colonized planet.

His goal was to buy some special consumables, something that could be used on the statue.

A few days later, the spaceship returned to the Rain Star System. After the Union Day Celebration, Chen Xing stayed in the New Phylen Alliance for his tour. When he received the message from Han Xiao, he was shocked and surprised.

It's only been a few days, but the other two statues have already been found?

My god, what level of efficiency is this!

The item that he had spent years looking for had been found by this group of mercenaries in a few days. They were indeed the professionals!

The spaceship docked on a colonized planet of the New Phylen Alliance. Chen Xing was performing in a city there. With the passionate welcome of the assistant, Han Xiao and the others met with Chen Xing in the most expensive suite of a high-class hotel.

"Hahaha, Black Star, you've really surprised me. I never thought you would be able to find all the statues so quickly." Chen Xing was overjoyed, and his face was slightly red from his excitement.

This time, Han Xiao had brought everyone along. This was the first time that Herlous had met Chen Xing. "Being this pretty, is he a man or a woman?"

"I'm a man. It's natural beauty." Chen Xing heard Herlous' murmur and replied with a smile.

Han Xiao coughed and said, "I've brought the stuff. There will be more than enough time later for chitchat. I think it's better to carry out the holy deal first."

Chen Xing gave him a seductive look, chuckled, and said, "So impatient. Alright, I'm very satisfied with your efficiency. I'll pay double the reward to repay the surprise you've given me."

"Double? Wouldn't that be..." Sylvia counted with her fingers, and her mouth fell open. "Two—two hundred thousand!"

"Calm down, don't act like you've never seen money before." Han Xiao knocked her head. Celebrities were, of course, wealthy; it was nothing to be surprised about.

The four statues were placed on the table. Chen Xing checked them, made sure they were the right statues, and paid the money instantly.

[Statue Search] Completed

Grading mission...

Grading complete.

Mission Rating: Unbelievable

You have received [Unbelievable] level bonus reward: Bonus 120% experience (1,320,000), bonus 100,000 Enas, random reward x 1, special item x 1.

You have received [Character Summon Card - Chen Xing]

Character Summon Card—Chen Xing: [Flirtatious Smile]: +688 CHA. Duration: 15 seconds. Usages: 0/3

Seeing the effect of the Character Summon Card, Han Xiao was silent.

Other than the word 'ridiculous', he could not think of another word to describe it.

688 points of attribute boost, but in charm‽ Is this supposed to make the enemies lose too much blood from nosebleeds‽ If this boost was for Intelligence, I'd go beat up a Grade A right now!

Han Xiao's mouth twitched. He was speechless.

A flirtatious smile? Are you serious‽

The Charm attribute had always been a side attribute. It was mainly used to get discounts in deals or enhance illusion abilities, affinity with creatures, taming beasts, farm favorability, and so on. Almost no player would focus on increasing their character's Charm... other than some female players. Technically, no player would spend this many points on Charm. Han Xiao felt that this value would give him natural seductiveness, and anyone that looked at him had to be above a certain level of resistance to not be affected.

Why did it have to be charm! I already have enough of it!

Other than the extra reward, he received 2,430,000 experience and 200,000 Enas. The monetary reward was really high—celebrities were generous indeed. His savings finally exceeded one million and reached more than 1.1 million.

He had gotten a very high completion rating for the mission but did not receive any legendary points nor a Medal of Honor since the difficulty of the mission itself was only C. He already had one Medal of Honor, [Germinal Organization Slayer], which he had received after destroying the Germinal Organization. Its effect was a three percent boost in all attributes. Gathering three Medals of Honor would turn them into a special Medal of Achievement which gave a twelve percent boost in all attributes.

However, the random reward from the [Unbelievable] mission rating was the key.

Han Xiao's eyes became firm. He pulled Herlous aside and touched him here and there.

"What are you doing?" Herlous felt a disgusting shiver and jumped away hastily.

"Getting some of your luck." Han Xiao rubbed his hands. He knew how good his luck was. Old Herlous was at least a main character and had the lucky aura, so he was willing to believe in superstitions in such times.

The Great Mechanic Han took a deep breath. With a solemn and serious expression, he slowly clicked on the 'confirm' button.

Randomizing...

Randomizing complete.

You received the Random Reward Type: [Talent]

"Damn it!"

Chapter 452: Sudden Attack!

Only if the reward type was [Item] would there be a chance to obtain the Mission Completion Card.

Are you a fake main character Old Herlous?

Han Xiao turned around and looked at Aroshia. He felt that touching her was more dependable.

Aroshia looked at him with a poker face, and they looked at each other for three seconds.

Han Xiao shook his head, rubbed his temples, comforted himself, and thought, This is just the first time. It's normal to meet a small obstacle. It's normal... normal...

Han Xiao knew that the chances of getting a Mission Completion Card on the first try were very low. Although abilities were not what he needed most at the moment, it could have been worse.

Sigh, things would be much easier if the players were here. I could just give out a mission to have them give me Mission Completion Cards, and I wouldn't have to hope to get lucky.

Han Xiao shook his head and looked at the interface.

_____________________

Please select 1 from the 3 talents below.

[Flame Affinity]: +16% Fire Resistance, +10% damage of fire element abilities

[Advanced Mental Toughness]: +35% Psychological Resistance, decrease Psychological Resistance needed to be immune to mental controlling debuffs, -30% duration of these debuffs.

[Cell Engine]: +21% Energy recovery speed, +330 energy

_____________________

With just one look, Han Xiao had already made a decision. [Flame Affinity] was suitable for the Mage class and had a very limited effect on him. [Cell Engine] was not bad, but it was not as practical as [Advanced Mental Toughness]. Anything that had the 'Advanced' prefix was usually half decent. Furthermore, the Psychic class could attack through the armor of the Mechanic class, so this talent could largely enhance his Psychological Resistance.

Plus, he would be able to use it on the spot.

After some pondering, Han Xiao suddenly realized that something was wrong.

Wait a minute, why am I becoming tankier?

Is there really no way for me not to be a tank! I want to deal damage, damn it!

Although he did not get a Mission Completion Card, he did garner quite a number of benefits on this trip—two talents, one Character Summon Card that felt kind of useless, more than two million experience, and 200,000 Enas.

Chen Xing was staring at him with a smile, expressing his intention of sending these guests off graciously. He suppressed his emotions and could not wait to do his stuff after the mercenaries left.

Han Xiao reached out his hand and said, "Since the mission is completed, we shall get going."

"Sure. If there is a chance in the future, I will work with you again."

Chen Xing smiled politely and grabbed Han Xiao's hand.

Suddenly, without any warning, Han Xiao's hand locked onto his hand tightly. Han Xiao abruptly pulled Chen Xing to his side before he could react.

In an instant, the Void Dragon mechanical suit covered his body. Han Xiao leaned back slightly, then heavily headbutted Chen Xing's face with his armored forehead.

Bang!

Being suddenly attacked, Chen Xing felt the world was spinning.

Han Xiao activated all the enhancing modules of Void Dragon. With the Electromagnetic Pulse Controller stimulating his body, he entered the [Excited] state. Together with the attribute boost from Void Dragon's combat form, his Strength increased by more than one hundred points. One headbutt was not enough, so he headbutted Chen Xing again, stunning him for a short period.

Using the short opportunity, Han Xiao grabbed Chen Xing's head with his hands and released [Void Jet Spray]!

Boom!

The shockwave turned the luxurious hotel suite into a total mess like it had been visited by a tornado.

"What are you doing‽"

Herlous, Sylvia, and the Volga brothers were all shocked!

A mercenary is attacking the employer!

It was still so peaceful moments ago, why did he suddenly attack‽

"You..." Chen Xing's resistance was not low. He finally regained focus after taking two charges of Void Jet Sprays. His eyes turned pure white, and the surging Psychic power pushed everyone away.

He clutched his head full of pain, stared at Han Xiao with hate, and bit his lips. He was shocked and enraged.

He did not understand why Han Xiao suddenly attacked him, but that did not stop him from feeling threatened.

"Argh!" Chen Xing opened his mouth. Psychic power flew into his voice, and the sharp high note pierced into the others' brains like a spear, causing a strong pain.

They felt like the world was spinning, and their organs were distorted like they were going to vomit. Sylvia was the weakest. She grabbed tightly onto her brain like it was going to explode the next second.

Han Xiao felt painful too like a blade was stirring in his brain. The [Advanced Mental Toughness] that he had just acquired instantly showed its effect. He had planned to attack long before he chose this talent. It largely reduced Psychic damages and debuffs, which was very useful against Psychics.

After all, he knew everything about Chen Xing.

Han Xiao endured the pain and pounced forward. His elbow slashed onto Chen Xing's psychic shield like a tomahawk, making a loud crash of the sound barrier breaking, then it landed on Chen Xing's pretty face.

Pa!

Blood splashed out from Chen Xing's nose and mouth. He held his bleeding nose and backed off in a panic. His eyes were filled with rage and shock.

"Herlous, go outside the door and stop the guards. Volga brothers, protect Sylvia and don't get too close to us."

Han Xiao spoke very quickly. At the same time, his fist covered in armor punched and broke Chen Xing's shield time after time, forcing him to back off without a choice, not able to use psychic attacks. He was moving closer to a dead end.

"What is going on‽" Herlous was still lost. He clenched his teeth and decided to trust that Han Xiao had a reason to do this.

Boom boom boom!

Herlous rushed out the room door, swung his Battleship Slicing Blade, and stopped the guards outside.

"Piss! Off!" Chen Xing screamed like a woman, and blood flew out from his eyes. He used some kind of secret technique to stimulate his mind and go beyond his psychic power limit. The windows and walls of the room exploded and shattered, and dust suffused with the air. Han Xiao was pushed aside as well.

With the opportunity to catch his breath, Chen Xing clenched his teeth and activated his psychic power. All the items in the room floated up into the air and fused into a wave, pushing Han Xiao back and not letting him get closer.

This time, Chen Xing's face was covered in blood. His luxurious and beautiful clothes were coated in dust and blood, and he was in a very bad state. He was still suffering from the concussion resulting from Han Xiao's headbutts, so he was unable to focus, and his psychic power was flowing slower than usual.

The next second, the four statues that had fallen to the ground were grabbed by Chen Xing with his psychic power. Like a thirsty man seeing water, he pressed the statues against his forehead.

A unique psychic rhythm appeared in the air. In a spectrum invisible to the human eye, the Psychic Current in the statues was flowing into Chen Xing's brain. His weakened Psychic powers recovered extremely quickly.

This was the statues' effect on Chen Xing. The Psychic Current in them was like a strong supplement to him that could enhance his psychic power. Items like this that received prayers over a long time could all be used by him to strengthen his powers. This was a method used by the Psychics, absorbing Psychic Currents to strengthen themselves. It was rare and had a very strong side effect, the user would usually be impacted by all the thoughts in the Psychic Current, which might even damage the user's mind.

Aroshia saw this and was about to stop Chen Xing but realized that Han Xiao was secretly giving her a hand sign, telling her not to do anything. Hence, Aroshia stopped and watched things unfold.

Originally, he needed to be very cautious when absorbing the Psychic Current from the statues or his mind would be influenced by the countless thoughts in it. However, Chen Xing could not be bothered about that now. God knew if this mercenary had become crazy. All Chen Xing knew was that if he did not save himself, his life might be in danger.

Whoosh!

After gulping down the Psychic Currents from the four statues, the statues fell onto the ground and lost their uniqueness, only left with their tough exteriors.

After absorbing the Psychic Currents, Chen Xing's eyes turned red. A horrifying Psychic power surrounded him, and even the air was distorted. His psychic power was so strong that it was visible. His head did not hurt anymore, and his back did not ache anymore; he recovered to his peak performance and even beyond.

"How dare you beat me up to this extent? I—I will turn you into my Silent Slave!"

Chen Xing wiped off the blood on his nose and lips. His tone was full of rage like a woman who realized that her beautiful face had been destroyed.

Strong Psychic powers gathered as Chen Xing prepared to launch his strongest attack.

This time, Han Xiao's eyes sparkled. Suddenly, he activated Hila's Character Summon Card, and a hologram of a redhead woman appeared behind him.

_____________________

[Whisper of the Dead]: Deals psychic damage three times to the enemy. Damage is based on the user's INT or MYS (can be indicated). Decreases all status of the target by 15%.

Duration: 3 hours

Usages: 2/8

_____________________

Dark red energy surged from Han Xiao's eyes and shot straight at Chen Xing.

Although he did not have the ability to enhance Psychic attacks, his Intelligence was very high. The three consecutive attacks were quite powerful.

Hum!

The world before Chen Xing's eyes was spinning. The heavy hit landed on his mind and caused him to lose control of his Psychic powers. The Psychic power that he had gathered exploded before it was launched.

Blood poured out Chen Xing's nose and mouth, and his eyes turned blood red. This was not because he used some ability to break his limits or anything like that but because the veins in his eyes exploded.

Psychic's Psychological Resistance was supposed to be very high, yet Chen Xing's mind was like it was almost defenseless, causing him to be heavily hurt instantly.

Suddenly, his state became even worse than before he absorbed the energy from the statues. His mind became extremely slow, and his knees became weak. Chen Xing fell onto the ground and gasped for air. He grabbed a statue in disbelief.

"You... did you do something to these‽"

Chapter 453: The Real Owner

Han Xiao's lips curled up. Before notifying Chen Xing, he had purchased a type of specially made mind poison on another planet and coated it on the statues. As long as anyone's Psychic powers came into contact with the poison, they would be damaged and suffer decreased Psychological Resistance. It was effective for Psychic type Espers, Mages, and Psychics.

Not only was Chen Xing already injured by Han Xiao, but he also absorbed all the energy from the statues, which made his mind weak, and now he was poisoned too. With all these factors, his resistance was largely decreased. Hence, his mind directly fell apart.

Chen Xing was Grade B, but Psychics were normally like paper, so Han Xiao did not dare to use Flaming Will. He was afraid that if he got lucky, or maybe unlucky, he would kill Chen Xing right away.

Blood poured out from Chen Xing's nose and mouth to the floor, Chen Xing had lost the ability to resist. He looked at Han Xiao with a death stare, his face was filled with loath.

For an instant, Chen Xing's expression seemed to become very calm, but that was so brief that it felt like an illusion.

"Why are you doing this?" Chen Xing clenched his teeth. "Did you accept a request to assassinate me?"

Han Xiao answered Chen Xing by grabbing onto his hair and slamming it heavily onto the floor, knocking him unconscious.

Explaining is a job for the villains. We are just!

"Old Herlous, come back here and let's retreat!"

"Thanks to you, I might be quite busy at the moment..." Herlous' annoyed voice came from outside the door. He had blocked several waves of guards outside, so the fight outside the door was getting intense.

Han Xiao grabbed Chen Xing's clothes and threw him to the Volga brothers, then he aimed his hands at the hotel wall and launched a maximum output Void Jet Spray.

Boom!

The gray shockwave blasted through the wall. Bricks and rebars showered onto the ground, and the air became filled with the pungent smell of dust. A huge hole appeared on the outside wall of the hotel. The ground was hundreds of meters below, and about a hundred meters below them was the nonstop traffic of hovering cars.

Han Xiao caught an opportunity and jumped down, smashing through a hovering car's roof and landing on the seat. The driver was horrified, but before he could speak, Han Xiao knocked him out and threw him onto the backseat.

Han Xiao quickly sat on the driving seat and held onto the steering wheel. He immediately felt a sense of familiarity. The next moment, the car flew upward and deviated from the midair traffic track, stopping outside the hole in the hotel's wall.

"All of you, come in!" Han Xiao said as the door opened.

The people squeezed in. Before Herlous could enter, the blaring alarm became even louder. Han Xiao looked in the rearview mirror and saw a convoy of hovering police cars coming from behind.

This was a high-class hotel, so there were a large number of police patrols nearby. The commotion had already raised alarms, and the hotel had informed them of the situation.

Han Xiao did not dare to continue waiting. He controlled the car to drive away and yelled, "Jump! Quickly!"

Herlous slashed sideways with the back of his sword and swept all the guards away, then he hastily turned around and sprinted to the hole on the wall. With a step that cracked the floor, he crossed almost a hundred meters in the air like a leap of faith and fell right into the car from the hole that Han Xiao smashed through earlier.

"Close, that was close..."

Herlous had yet to recover from the intense fight earlier. Suddenly, he felt he was sitting on something very soft. He looked down, and it turned out that he was sitting on a stranger's face. He asked in a surprised tone, "Who's this?"

"A driver that kindly gave us his car... Hey! Don't sit on his face, be appreciative."

Seeing that everyone was here, Han Xiao sped up immediately and charged forward like an unruly rhinoceros.

Not only were there police hovering cars behind chasing them, but there were more in front as well. However, as they were in the air, forward and backward were not the only two directions, so there was no way that they could stop him from escaping.

The turbulence made the people in the car feel like they were sitting inside a sardine tin that was being violently shaken. Herlous wanted to question Han Xiao about why he was doing this, but he had no choice but to put that thought away for the time being—he was afraid he might throw up if he opened his mouth.

Aroshia turned into her energy form and instantly felt better.

Sylvia, who had fainted from the Psychic wave earlier, slowly woke up. The world before her eyes was spinning wildly, making her think that she had a concussion. In less than thirty seconds after she woke up, she felt nauseous and vomited, fainting once again.

"Stop your car immediately, or we will open fire!" An announcement was made from the speakers on one of the police hovering cars.

Han Xiao grabbed the steering wheel. His car crashed directly and accurately into that police car's tail. The police car spun rapidly in the air like a gyroscope, and waves of shouting came out of the speakers.

Han Xiao felt zero pressure when facing such an amateur force. He downloaded the map of the entire city from the mechanical suit database, and the artificial intelligence assistant quickly planned a route and showed it on the analysis screen.

After more than ten minutes, he quickly got rid of all the pursuers. The tattered hovering car stopped at the gap between two buildings.

...

Bleurgh!

Herlous held onto the car window and vomited for a while before he finally felt better. He breathed heavily, stared at Han Xiao, and said with a fiery tone, "My dear captain, do you now have the time to explain what is going on to us laborers?"

He was very frustrated. How did a normal reward collection process turn into them being chased by the police all over the city? Furthermore, they had kidnapped a galactic celebrity.

If it was a woman, it would be fine, but it's a man! What are you trying to do, captain!

Han Xiao changed his position and looked at the backseat. He pointed at Chen Xing's head covered in dry blood and said, "My target is this guy. He's not as simple as he looks."

"... Thanks for your reminder. I didn't know a Grade B Psychic is not simple!" Herlous clenched his teeth.

With worry written all over his face, the youngest Volga said, "He's a huge celebrity. We will definitely be wanted by the local police, and we might even be reported to the New Phylen Alliance's direct police department. This will damage our mercenary name. Furthermore, the Rain Star System is New Phylen Alliance's territory. What should we do?"

"Don't worry." Han Xiao looked at Chen Xing and said, "That guy will speak for us, and as long as he does, we'll be fine."

"Are you going to threaten him? I don't think that will work." Herlous expressed his doubts.

"Threaten? No, there's no need for that." Han Xiao smiled. "He will choose to help us."

As he was speaking, he pulled Chen Xing out of the pile of people and threw him into the passenger's seat. After some pondering, he took out some tissue and wiped the blood off Chen Xing's face.

Chen Xing's face was covered in bruises and swollen parts. His delicate looks during his performance were nowhere to be found.

"I used too much strength earlier. Sigh, he was quite a handsome boy. What a pity..."

Han Xiao sighed sympathetically.

Pa pa pa!

Since his face was already in that state, Han Xiao gave him a series of slaps as a wake-up service.

Chen Xing's eyelashes shook, and he slowly opened his eyes. His pupils gradually focused, and he sat up straight.

His temperament changed completely. If he was more like an alluring woman earlier, he was now completely like a masculine man. He turned to look at Han Xiao and smiled calmly; there was no sign of him being furious like earlier.

"Hello, I have been looking at you since just now. Although you might have attacked me to kidnap me, I would still like to thank you for giving me the chance to come out and breathe some fresh air."

Completely unlike his earlier feminine tone, his voice was gentle and deep. It was almost like he was a different person.

"Yo—you..." Herlous was bewildered.

'Chen Xing' nodded and smiled gently.

"Nice to meet you, my name is Adrian Kelvinsin Feidin. You can call me Feidin. You don't have to be surprised—I'm the real owner of this body. The Chen Xing that you met is... how do I put it... I would say she is a not-so-friendly guest."

Chapter 454: Helping Hand

Schizophrenia? Paranoia? Faking? The people were perplexed. What is wrong with this guy?

"Mind Possession," Han Xiao said with a low voice.

A tint of surprise flashed through Feidin's eyes as he heard this. He did not expect Han Xiao to know the truth.

"I didn't expect you to realize." Then it occurred to Feidin—it turned out that Han Xiao had suddenly attacked him because he had discovered Chen Xing's secret.

As he understood why Han Xiao attacked him, he became skeptical. Why did this mercenary called Black Star help him? Mercenaries were not ones who would kindly help others without asking for anything in return—he definitely had a motive.

"So, it's Mind Possession..." The youngest Volga understood and immediately started explaining it to the others. He was a Psychic, too, so he knew what Mind Possession was.

Just like how a Pugilist trained their body, a Psychic trained their mind and soul. The strong ones could detach their soul and consciousness from their body and possess the mind of another, giving them a second life.

Usually, they would only use this spell when their body was heavily damaged and they had no choice, as the detaching process would cause irrecoverable damage to their soul. Furthermore, the success rate was only 0.3%, and failure would cause their soul to shatter, killing them on the spot.

Most people were not willing to abandon their original body and change into someone else's body unless they were left with no choice. Chen Xing was a perfect example for this. She was a woman, so why would she ever want to change her body into a man? They did not even have mutual hardware!

It was impossible for Psychics to possess someone whose mind was stronger than their own. As soon as a Psychic successfully possesses someone's mind, they would gain control of that body, and the original owner's body would be trapped in a cell. The original owner could feel what the body was feeling but would not be able to control the body, like a spectator.

Chen Xing was heavily injured, and her mind was very weak, so she had to rest. Hence, Feidin took over his body, and Chen Xing became a spectator.

Han Xiao had attacked because he wanted to meet Feidin, and injuring Chen Xing's mind was the most direct method to do that. It just so happened that he had Hila's Character Summon Card, which could attack one's mind, so there was no need to beat Feidin's body up to the brink of death... although his injury was still not light.

The youngest Volga briefly explained the principle of Mind Possession, and the others finally understood what it was.

No wonder Chen Xing was so feminine—it turns out she was a woman from the start.

"When did you get possessed?" Herlous said curiously.

"You mean, when was the last time I controlled this body?" Feidin shrugged. "4 years, 9 months, 14 days, 8 hours, and 23 minutes, oh, now it's 24 minutes."

"About five years ago..." Sylvia had woken up. She had heard their conversation and was puzzled. "Isn't that when Chen Xing made his debut?"

"Yes... my home is in a remote Star System in the Shattered Star Ring. I didn't like the completely modified main planet, so I migrated to a remote half-colonized planet. That planet is a gathering ground for the poor, also an abandoned planet in the others' eyes. However, I felt that place was more full of life than the city surrounded by iron and steel. I lived in the wild, making a living through farming land and hunting. Everything was peaceful. One day, a spaceship fell onto the land of my house, and inside was a heavily injured, unconscious woman. She was Chen Xing. I saved her and treated her wounds, but her injuries were too heavy. Before she died, she took away my body and continued living with it, then she became a celebrity. That's the gist of what happened."

Feidin spoke very calmly as if he did not have much hatred or anger on how his body had been taken away. He had long adapted throughout the five years, so there was no more resent and anger like when it first happened.

Han Xiao nodded. Despite the fact that Chen Xing had been crushed by him without being able to fight back, it was because her power had been heavily damaged when she extracted her soul from her body. Her strength had once been extremely close to Grade A. Because she changed a body, she became tremendously weaker and almost dropped to Grade C. That was why she was collecting things like these statues—it was to recover her powers.

Chen Xing was not a main character, but Feidin was!

Furthermore, his luck was stronger than Herlous, who was just a local main character. His Luck Glow was high-class!

Having someone so strong staying in one's mind was a standard main character storyline. However, for others, it was an old man, whereas for Feidin, it was a young woman.

If not for Chen Xing, Feidin would never have maximized his potential with his old man personality and would have been an ordinary person forever. Although Chen Xing took away his body, she also brought him on an unknown path. If that did not happen, Chen Xing would never have discovered how much potential he had. Furthermore, he would only face this difficult situation temporarily. Although Han Xiao did not know the exact time, he knew that Feidin would become stronger than Chen Xing in the future and retake his body.

Feidin's personal growth storyline was [The Legend of a Singer]!

How strong was a main character with High-Class Luck Glow? When Feidin was at his peak, he was as strong as Hila. His voice could reach one's soul directly without air to spread it.

He could use his holy voice to cleanse those souls filled with anger and hatred, making everything peaceful and filled with joy.

His one song solved a galactic war that had been about to break out!

That was what Feidin was known for!

Furthermore, Feidin did not keep all his secrets to himself. He publicly passed his Psychic knowledge on to others. The Psychic class players could learn the way to use Psychic powers through songs from him, which was one of the combat styles for Psychics. Feidin was like a high-class Psychic mentor.

When Han Xiao thought of this mission, he had already made a complete plan. If he could get the Mission Completion Card, he would not mess with Chen Xing for the time being and go for Promotion first. However, if he did not get the Mission Completion Card, he would then trigger this storyline. The players who did the [Statue Search] mission, of course, did not know Chen Xing's secrets. Many players only regretfully found out that this character had a storyline later.

Although Han Xiao did not know what the result would be if he triggered this storyline at this time, he decided to give it a try as he was not completely ignorant. He somewhat knew about Feidin's personality and could guess how things went. He could not say that he was a hundred percent certain, but there were definitely some benefits that he could get from it.

"I can help you to control your body and evict the guest in your mind, or your body will be hers again when she recovers," Han Xiao said.

Feidin was not moved. "What do you want? I believe this help does not come free."

"Chen Xing is very wealthy, you and her share your body, so you definitely know her account and password. I want her savings," Han Xiao said.

Chen Xing was indeed wealthy, but this was not the Great Mechanic Han's main goal. However, he could not directly say that he was interested in Feidin's potential, or he would not be able to gain his trust. Targeting his money was more convincing and would make Feidin lower his guard to a certain extent.

After all, the body belonged to Feidin—he would rather have Chen Xing control it than risk it entirely.

Feidin was instantly convinced; mercenaries wanting money was more normal than anything. Furthermore, this could not be considered a kidnapping but helping someone who was possessed, so they did not break the mercenary contract.

Feidin thought that it was a good idea. Although Chen Xing was the one who had made this money, she was using his body, so he did not feel any guilt about spending it.

"Sounds good... but if you want the money right away, I'm afraid I won't be able to do that." Feidin pointed at his head and smiled bitterly. "She just threatened me, saying that if I touch her savings, she will die together with me. Therefore, before her problem is dealt with, I won't be able to afford the reward."

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled. When he made this request, he had already guessed how Chen Xing would react to it, and this result was exactly what he wanted. He was secretly delighted. He nodded and said, "Then you have to be following me all the time—only then will I be able to suppress Chen Xing for you. Until we find a way to completely deal with her."

Feidin paused and said, "I hope that her life is not harmed. She possessed my body because she did not have a choice, and she did not use my body recklessly. In these five years, although she blocked my voice because she felt I was too annoying, I looked through all her memories, and she really is a pitiful person."

Usually, when someone's body was taken away, the owner of the body would most likely want the one who took that body to turn into ash. However, as a main character, Feidin's personality was obviously unique. He still thought of Chen Xing even in this situation, which surprised everyone else.

"Sure."

Han Xiao nodded. He looked very confident on the outside, but actually, even he did not know how to deal with Mind Possession. No player had triggered this storyline before, so he could only figure it out himself. However, this did not stop him from agreeing first.

"Since we have come to an agreement, we will need you to deal with the current situation. As long as you help to speak, our wanted status will be canceled."

"No problem." Feidin smiled gently. He looked at his full of bruises face in the mirror and said, "But the wounds on my face need to be treated first, or it will not be convincing at all."

Chapter 455: Hidden Mission, Choice.

"This morning, the famous singer Chen Xing was attacked in the Colton Star Cluster, Rain Star System, New Phylen Number Eight Colonized Planet. His whereabouts are currently unknown. According to information from witnesses, the kidnapper is the Black Star Mercenary Group, a mercenary group with a good name in Colton Star Cluster and the field team of Floating Dragon Island. The details are still unknown. We are currently closely communicating with the local police department and Chen Xing's assistant team..."

The hole outside on the hotel wall was surrounded by hovering cars. Other than the police team that was sealing off the scene, there was also a huge group of reporters. Some were local New Phylen Alliance reporters, and some were galactic reporters. They quickly arrived at the scene after the incident happened like sharks chasing after the smell of blood, fighting to report first-hand news.

If it was just a normal kidnapping, those reporters would not be very interested. But this time was different—it was a famous person who got kidnapped, a celebrity singer. Furthermore, it happened in the middle of the city, and the kidnapper was a known mercenary group. These reporters were very sensitive to hot news material, and they immediately realized what was unusual about it. Other than reporting the incident, they also started creating rumors.

Assassination hire?

A crime of passion?

Property dispute?

Anyway, the titles were all created for the sake of attracting attention. Chen Xing had many fans in various places in Shattered Star Ring, and these fans were all shocked. The news spread like a hurricane.

The local police were extremely overwrought. A galactic celebrity being attacked in their territory was not a small thing. If they did not deal with it properly, the negative influence would be severe. Furthermore, Chen Xing was a guest performer for the Union Day Celebration. If something happened to him, the New Phylen Alliance would be the one losing face. The central police department had already focused their attention on this incident, which made the local sheriff tremendously pressured.

Just as the incident was unfolding, without anyone expecting it, Chen Xing returned himself, and together with him were the kidnappers, the Black Star Mercenary Group. This surprised both the police and the media.

As soon as Feidin returned, he was surrounded by countless people and reporters asking him questions. The police divided the crowd and protected him. On the other side, the hovering car of Han Xiao and the others were also surrounded by layers of police cars.

After convincing Feidin, Han Xiao had let the oldest Volga brother to cure the wounds on Feidin's face with his water element spells, which turned out to be very effective. Although Feidin still looked quite exhausted, he returned to a handsome young man again. Unlike the feminine and alluring feeling that Chen Xing gave off, when Feidin controlled his body, he gave off a very gentle and tender vibe.

Feidin calmly dealt with the media with the script that he had already prepared. Back when he was trapped, he had been watching Chen Xing's every move, so he had no problem with doing the same.

If it was five years ago, Feidin would not have known so many things. The memories and experiences that Chen Xing had gained when using his body were all things that Feidin had never gone through—they all became his experiences.

The police and reporters had their doubts on the excuses Feidin had thought of, but since he had explained it himself, there was nothing more that they could do. The local sheriff filed a report and left, and the reporters also left with disappointment.

The manager of the hotel found Han Xiao and requested that he pay for the damages on the wall. It was a very reasonable request, so Han Xiao did not reject and paid for it. After the hotel people left, he woke up the driver of the hovering car and paid him 20 Enas to repair his car, which was more than enough.

After these things were dealt with, it was finally peaceful. Just as Han Xiao was about to walk to Feidin, Chen Xing's manager stood in front of Feidin and yelled, "This place doesn't welcome mercenaries. Please leave now!"

Chen Xing did not belong to any entertainment group; she had built a logistics team herself that was made up mostly of females. The manager was a purple-skinned young Dunan girl with rather large eyes. She had completely fallen for Chen Xing and worked for him willingly. She was staring at Han Xiao with rage in her eyes.

Feidin dry coughed and said, "I have something to announce. First, cancel all the following tours and clear out my schedule."

"O—okay." The manager could not bother about Han Xiao and quickly noted it down. When she turned around and saw Feidin was looking at her, she immediately blushed and almost panicked out of shyness. She quickly lowered her head and did not dare to look Feidin in the eye. She did not even know where to place her hands.

Seeing this, Han Xiao curled his lips and thought, He really is an attractiveness focused main character. With such a high Charm attribute, he probably has a default Seduction Spell...

"Relax." Feidin smiled gently like the spring wind. "Second, I'm going to stop my performing career temporarily and leave here with these mercenaries."

"Okay... what‽" The manager was about the agree subconsciously, but she suddenly realized what he had said, and her face changed dramatically. She was completely dumbfounded. She turned to look at Han Xiao with incomparable rage and hatred.

"Sorry, you guys might have to look for another job." Feidin waved his hand and patted the manager's head. The manager, who had been like a furious lion just a second ago, instantly quieted down and started crying.

On the side, his other female assistants all cried as well. They looked at Han Xiao with eyes filled with hostility like he was their romantic rival who had snatched their love away. But when they looked at Feidin, their expression became sorrowful again, and they ran toward Feidin for hugs. This scene looked like a group of people who had just lost their lover, yet none of them blamed their 'ex-boyfriend' and forgave him instead. It was very peaceful.

Han Xiao's mouth twitched.

If handsome people could stand on a few boats at the same time, Feidin had the potential to stand on hundreds of boats at the same time.

Being extremely attractive really allows people to do anything they want.

I have nothing to say.

After Feidin disbanded the group and told everyone to pack up their things and leave, he ignored Chen Xing's screams in his head, walked over to Han Xiao, and shrugged. "I'm free now, how do you plan to help me?"

Just as Han Xiao was about to speak, the interface notified him that he had received a new mission.

You have triggered the hidden mission [Choice].

Mission Introduction: You discovered that Chen Xing is actually a Mind Possession lifeform. You met with the original owner of the body, Feidin. He decided to completely deal with Chen Xing, who is in his mind, and your choice is extremely crucial.

Mission Completion Requirement I: Evict or kill Feidin's consciousness and let Chen Xing control the body.

Mission Completion Requirement II: Evict or kill Chen Xing's consciousness and let Feidin control the body.

Mission Completion Requirement III: Help Chen Xing and Feidin come to an agreement and have them take turns to control the body.

Mission Completion Requirement IV: Unknown.

Remarks: As long as one requirement is met, the mission can be considered as complete. Different results give different rewards.

"I can help Chen Xing?" Han Xiao was surprised. As he knew about Feidin's future, he did not think about this possibility.

This meant that the fate of a main character, Feidin, was in his hands. If he helped Chen Xing, he would not have a future.

Interesting.

Han Xiao squinted and read through the mission requirements carefully again. The fourth requirement was unknown, and in his experience, this kind of hidden requirement usually gave the greatest reward. In that case, other than helping one party or helping them come to an agreement, what result could be better?

No player in his previous life had done this mission before, so Han Xiao could only judge from his experience of doing countless missions over the years. The first two choices were simple and straightforward; the third requirement, however, needed more time to have the two of them communicate with each other. All he could do at the moment was let Feidin continue control his body and create an environment for two of them to communicate peacefully. If Chen Xing regained control of Feidin's body, she would definitely mess things up.

Furthermore, the mission could be completed based on his choice of when to complete it—this meant that the fourth requirement would need more time.

Although he had only just seen the mission, Han Xiao already knew what the keyword was—time! Time was the difficult part. The longer it took, the more chances Chen Xing would have to gain control of the body. This was an unstable factor.

Furthermore, the only reason that Feidin's consciousness had lasted for so long was that Chen Xing had held back—she could have wiped Feidin's consciousness out long ago. Maybe it was because Feidin had saved her before, so she felt guilty. However, if Chen Xing was really forced into a corner, she might kill Feidin when she recovered. Hence, the reward for the first requirement should be very small. No matter who controlled the body, the problem would be considered solved, so the mission would be completed.

After some pondering, Han Xiao said to Feidin, "If you don't want to hurt Chen Xing, I will not use any destructive methods. I have a few ways to suppress Chen Xing. There is a Psychic in my team. Despite him not being very strong, not being too strong allows him to weaken Chen Xing consistently without hurting her too much, so she would not be able to recover. If you want to deal with the problem completely without hurting her, the only way is for you to come to an agreement with her. The most I can do is not let her control your body. However, this way, you won't be able to leave us, or Chen Xing might take over again anytime."

What Han Xiao said was for Chen Xing as well, to prevent her from doing anything extreme.

"... Alright, I will try."

Feidin nodded and smiled—he was quite optimistic. "Letting me control the body is enough. I happened to learn the ways to train my Psychic powers from her memories. If my mind becomes strong enough, she won't be able to do anything anymore."

Han Xiao had a flash of insight after hearing what Feidin said.

He had a rough idea of what the fourth mission requirement was.

If that's really the case, it indeed does require a lot of time...

Chapter 456: Power of the Main Character Aura

Han Xiao had a rough idea as to what the fourth requirement was. Extracting again was impossible given the 0.3% success rate; neither Feidin nor Chen Xing would be willing to take the risk. Therefore, the only path left would be for them to reconcile. The extent of 'reconciliation' for the fourth requirement would definitely be more perfect than the third requirement, so it would require more time. Of course, Han Xiao preferred the fourth requirement with the greatest reward, but even if not for the reward, letting Feidin walk the same path as the previous life was beneficial for Han Xiao.

Since Feidin had decided to stay with the mercenary group, his position was not a member but an employer who needed help. However, this guy was potential stock. If his problem was dealt with, Han Xiao would at least be able to get more than half of Chen Xing's savings. According to Feidin, with the money that Chen Xing had made throughout the five years of her career, they were a multimillionaire.

Of course, Han Xiao had more hopes to make Feidin an officer of the mercenary group. In that case, he would get all the benefits!

However, this was not easy to achieve. With Feidin's personality, he would not become a mercenary. He was only following the mercenary group to solve his problem.

Although I have him in my team temporarily, he is not considered as a member. He is just a customer, so he definitely will not help in combat, Han Xiao thought. Hmm... In order to make him join us, it will take some time. I shall first see how [Choice] goes, then plan from there.

They had to take care of Feidin since he was following them around, or he might face danger. The youngest Volga brother was suitable for this job, since his combat abilities were not strong anyway, so he might as well do something else.

The mission [Choice] needed time and had to develop naturally, so Han Xiao was not hoping to complete it any time soon.

Feidin handled his matters with ease and became a completely free person. Han Xiao was not planning to stay for long. He brought everyone to the dock and arrived at the parking spot of their spaceship.

The spaceship let down a ladder, Han Xiao and the others climbed up. Han Xiao turned around and saw Feidin still on the ground sizing up the spaceship with complexity in his eyes.

"Stop standing there," Han Xiao said, "let's go."

"... Fine."

Feidin took a long, deep breath. This was the first time that he had controlled his body after five years, and he missed that feeling. Chen Xing stopped talking in his head and focused on recovering, waiting for an opportunity.

As long as he stepped onto the spaceship in front of him, he would go on an unknown journey once again. The difference was, this time, he was not a spectator. As someone who disliked the advanced technology, Feidin felt like it was like a dream. Five years earlier, he had never thought that he would become a celebrity singer known throughout the galaxy, or that a woman would be living in his body, making him fight for the control of his body with her, or that he would ever end up following a group of mercenaries and even try to train his Psychic powers.

Feidin sighed. He had once thought that he would spend his entire life as an ordinary person. Living his life in the wilds, having a pet as a companion, hunting while he is young, put down his hunting bow to farm his land once he got older before he got killed by a beast, maybe falling asleep near the fire one day and never waking up again. But that fallen spaceship shattered his life plan like a hammer, suddenly and without any warning.

"Although this life now is not what I wanted," Feidin murmured, "it seems quite interesting."

Just as he was about to step onto the ladder, a commotion came from far away. A large group of people flooded toward them, shouting Chen Xing's name. He looked over and realized that they were reporters.

After thinking for a while, it occurred to Han Xiao.

"Right, Chen Xing's assistant group has disbanded. Someone must've contacted the reporters."

As he expected, the reporters smelled a hot topic from the fact that 'Chen Xing' gave up his singing career and left with the group of mercenaries who were suspected to have kidnapped him earlier. They immediately turned around and came back like maniacs.

"Chen Xing, what are the reasons behind you doing this?"

"Were you threatened?"

"Tell us, don't be worried about someone hurting you. We will protect you."

These reporters surrounded Feidin and almost wanted to take him away. Feidin struggled to squeeze out of the crowd and waved. "This is my own decision. I have something else to do..."

As he spoke, he hastily rushed up the ladder. Han Xiao moved aside and let him in.

The reporters were not going to let Chen Xing go this easily. They squeezed up the ladder one after another, wanting to push Han Xiao away and rush into the spaceship no matter what.

Boom!

A ring of energy erupted!

All the reporters on the ladder were blown away and rolled down. They barely stood up enduring the pain but did not dare go forward anymore. Only then did they remember that it was a dangerous mercenary who was standing before them.

Han Xiao closed the hatch with an expressionless face.

The spaceship took off and left that colonized planet.

...

Outside the window was the dark universe in which the spaceship slowly traversed. In the hall, Feidin was sitting in the middle of everyone. The youngest Volga brother pressed onto the back of Feidin's brain, and rings of formless Psychic waves spread out from his forehead. After a while, he took his hands away.

"I found Chen Xing. She's very weak and could not resist my invasion. I have set four layers of walls and trapped her inside, at the same time hypnotizing her consciousness and slowing her thinking speed, which equals to reducing her recovery speed. In the next fifteen days, she won't be able to do anything."

Feidin nodded. "She's scolding me, so it seems to have been quite effective."

He turned and smiled at the youngest Volga brother, releasing his attractiveness without holding back. "Thank you for your help."

"Er, yo—you're welcome." The youngest Volga brother's face blushed for some reason.

Han Xiao sat in the middle of the sofa. On his left was Aroshia and on his right was Sylvia. He said with a deep voice, "Exterior forces are not stable no matter what. Only you becoming stronger is the right path."

"I know." Feidin shrugged. He looked at an object on the table. A slight wave of Psychic power reached out, and that object slowly levitated and floated in the air. "Actually, I awakened Psychic powers on the way here."

Plop!

Sylvia fell onto the ground.

She hurriedly climbed up, and her face was covered in shock. "S—So quick?"

Feidin smiled and said, "There are full sets of Psychic training methods in Chen Xing's memories, and I could feel it when she trained her Psychic powers. It's easy to do the same. Apparently, I am rather talented. She used three days to awaken her powers back then, whereas I only used a few hours. By the way, when she is curing herself, I can take some Psychic power from her more or less. She and I use the same body, so there's no power rejection."

Chen Xing's memories were an enormous treasure, and all of that was now shared with Feidin. It was like Feidin had already walked that path once so now he would not make any mistakes. Furthermore, he was very talented. Only Feidin himself did not know how fast his growth was.

Han Xiao's mouth twitched. Feidin surely lived up to his high-class main character aura.

Sylvia had no tears left to cry.

For me to become a Super, not only did I have to memorize tons of books every day, but I still had to be electrified. Why are you so lucky‽

Herlous snorted and did not really like Feidin. He turned around and asked Han Xiao, "Where are we going now?"

Han Xiao pondered and said, "Let me think about it..."

Han Xiao did not get a Mission Completion Card this time, but he was not going to give up. This was only the first try—maybe he would get it on the next try. Compared with taking the risk and fighting a Grade A Super, although taking his chance with the random reward required luck, it was steadier.

Promotion is the most important target currently. Level 100 is the gateway to Race Evolution; the enhancement will be huge. Strength is the most important thing—everything else has to be put aside. The version update is in more than one year's time, so there is quite some time left. I have to find another familiar mission to get a random reward chance. Luckily, my list of missions is very long. I refuse to believe that I will not get the Mission Completion Card even after so many chances.

After some contemplation, he chose the nearest mission. Just as he was about to change the route on the autopilot system, Aroshia, who was silent most of the time, spoke. Her tone was hesitant, and she spoke more than usual.

"The past few days, I've felt a restriction on becoming stronger. It seems to be the Grade B limit you spoke of. I have a feeling that as long as I surpass it, my power will be much stronger. However, this limit is not as strong as you said. I should be able to break it any time...

"Also, I have been dreaming. I saw many blurry images in my dream that felt familiar, but I can't recall the most of it after waking up... Do you think these are the memories I've lost?"

Han Xiao was surprised, and his eyes narrowed.

Chapter 457: The Second Grade B Officer

This news was a little too sudden. Even the Great Mechanic Han could not react to it instantly. He thought about it and realized that Aroshia had been at Grade C+ for quite some time. With her growth speed, it was indeed about time for her to enter Grade B.

In Aroshia's A ranked chain mission [Reboot], the requirement of the first round was to reach Aroshia and help her reach Grade B. The rewards were very rich—5,200,000 experience and one chance of a random reward. Han Xiao just happened to be in need of random reward chances, so this was an unexpected, pleasant surprise.

Aroshia was very special. She said that she had recently dreamed of many familiar images and that those might be the memories she lost. Every time Aroshia died, her memories would reboot, and she would forget everything before that. After so long, it was unknown how many memories she had lost.

"When you step through the doors of Grade B, there might be a special change," Han Xiao said.

Due to this sudden situation, Han Xiao changed his destination and made the spaceship stop at the nearest small planet.

Aroshia was not a player. Plus, she was an Esper that had no certain pattern. Her class advancement might release a powerful force. For the sake of being cautious, he did not let her advance her class in the spaceship.

...

Stepping onto the ground, Aroshia closed her eyes. Her body slowly levitated up, and beams of bright light shot out from her body, causing an energy tide in a range of a few hundred meters.

Whoosh!

Violent winds stirred up stone and sand, and the energy wave kept expanding like a ripple.

Around the spaceship, Han Xiao and the others watched Aroshia go through class advancement from afar. Their hair was dancing in the wind as sand and dust blew on their faces.

"It's quite a huge scene..." Herlous raised his hand to block the beams of light.

"She's very special. She was around Grade C as soon as she awakened, and there's an enormous amount of energy hidden in her body. Breaking through Grade B is a piece of cake for her." Han Xiao nodded.

Herlous' face twitched. "Am I the only one who feels that breaking through grades is not easy?"

The oldest Volga patted his shoulders and said meaningfully, "Be satisfied with what you have."

Like the expanding sea, the light energy quickly filled up the space within a few hundred meters. That area became a sea of light. It was as if Aroshia's powers far exceeded before.

Ohm!

Suddenly, the light stopped expanding and rapidly retracted to the center many times faster than before. A countless number of light beams rushed into the middle point, making a loud noise like the howling wind. The light converged into a tornado, and the center of it got brighter and brighter. However, when it reached its maximum brightness, it looked like it suddenly got darker.

All the energy was infused into a point. That point suddenly enlarged and exploded into light dust, turning into a human figure of light without a face. It was covered in ripples of energy waves and golden electric currents.

Then, under the effect of Aroshia's Esper power, the energy followed a certain unknown principle and turned into matter. Aroshia's body appeared again as she slowly landed on the ground.

Han Xiao took out the energy level detector and aimed it at Aroshia. The energy that she was emitting now had exceeded the lowest Grade B energy level standard.

First round of [Reboot] completed.

You have received 5,200,000 Experience.

+5 Risda Favorability.

You have received Random Reward x 1.

This Risda definitely has an unusual relationship with Aroshia, but who is he?

Holding back his joy, Han Xiao temporarily left the random reward in the interface, walked to Aroshia, and asked, "How are you feeling?"

Aroshia checked herself and said, "I can control more energy now."

"Other than that?"

"I saw more familiar images, way too many... my head is hurting a little." Aroshia frowned.

Han Xiao looked down, reached out his hands, and rubbed her temples, easing her pain. "What else are you feeling?"

"I don't know. Some places that flashed past in my memories seem to be summoning me. I have a feeling that if I go to these places, I should be able to recall some things..." Aroshia moved her fingers in the air and drew out the images of different locations in her memories with light energy.

Han Xiao raised his brows. Initially, Aroshia was not curious about the memories that she had lost at all, but after she entered Grade B, she seemed to have awakened a more human side of her. She had new desires, and her emotions were richer.

Could it be that as Aroshia became stronger, her secrets would be gradually exposed?

At this time, a new notification popped up on the interface.

[Reboot]

Second Round: According to Aroshia's descriptions, head to the various locations in her memories and help her look for the pieces of her memories.

Current Progress: 0/?

Reward: 10,300,000 Experience, +10 Risda Favorability

Failure Condition: Aroshia's death

The second round is to help her find parts of her memories? Han Xiao's eyes sparkled. Being this special, Aroshia's origin was definitely extraordinary. If she found her memories, he was not certain whether it would be a good or bad thing.

He felt that Aroshia was good the way that she was. If she recovered her memories, her personality would definitely change. This current state between them would most likely not be able to carry on.

Han Xiao was a little hesitant.

Maybe keeping things as they were and not doing this mission was the best choice.

No matter what, Aroshia was a very decent friend, and she was now the second Grade B officer in the mercenary group. If she continued to grow, she would be of more use.

With three Grade B Supers, including Han Xiao himself, the rating of the mercenary group in the alliance would increase, and he would have another strong comrade.

However, this should be Aroshia's personal storyline. Even if he did not do it, she might remember more memories as time went on. By then, she might choose to leave nonetheless. When thinking this way, Han Xiao thought that he might as well do the mission and see how things went.

This second round of the mission was like treasure hunting. Aroshia could only briefly describe the images, and they still had to find the actual locations of those images. It would be like looking for a needle in a haystack. Furthermore, there were multiple locations. Although there was no information regarding this mission in his previous life, Han Xiao remembered quite a number of places, so he would not be completely clueless

This mission is definitely impossible to complete in a short period of time. Sigh, I shall look for it slowly then. Promotion is the most important matter right now.

Han Xiao patted Aroshia's back and told her to get back to the spaceship with the others. The spaceship then took off and left the planet.

There was still a random reward chance in the interface. Han Xiao rubbed his hands together, took a deep breath, and activated it.

Randomizing...

Randomizing complete.

Your Random Reward Type is: [Item]

Han Xiao's eyes immediately brightened; he was excited.

There is a chance!

He subconsciously held his breath in trepidation.

Time felt like it was stretched out, and everything became slower. The three choices appeared one after another.

Please select one from the three items below

Small Potential Potion: Grants 1 bonus Potential Point

Mechanic Blueprint: 1 random Mechanic blueprint.

Blank Character Summon Card: Choose a character and randomly generate that character's Character Summon Card. Can only be used once.

Han Xiao's eyes widened in shock.

Wow, they were all complete trash!

I finally got the [Item] type, and this is what you give me‽

Han Xiao almost wanted to smash the table.

He had caught a glimmer of hope, and the next second, it was extinguished. The highs and lows of life were too exciting!

I want the Mission Completion Card!

Chapter 458: Attention from a Distant Star Field

After panicking for a while, Han Xiao finally calmed down. He clenched his teeth and smiled.

It's not a big deal. I didn't get it this time, but I will try it the next time and even the next time after that!

It was just like card games, where normal people had to rack their brains to win but lucky ones just had to use whatever card they got in order to win.

I'm not panicking at all!

Han Xiao drank a cup of water to calm down and looked at the interface again. The three items were still there waiting for him to choose.

None of the three items were rare, so Han Xiao could only choose the best out of them.

Although Potential Points were important, the Small Potential Potion only gave one point, which was negligible. Han Xiao would only have considered it if it was a medium or large one. One random Mechanic blueprint looked good, but it was actually complete garbage. There were way too many Mechanic blueprints, so the chance of getting a good blueprint was way too low. Even if he did get a very rare blueprint, it would most likely be a piece of equipment that could only be built at very high levels. If his level was not high enough, it would be completely useless. Furthermore, Han Xiao did not need any random blueprints. He remembered the knowledge combination for most blueprints, so he could make them himself.

After contemplating, he felt that only the Blank Character Summon Card was worthwhile. If he chose to generate Ames' Character Summon Card, who knew what effect it would have?

Although he had the Super-Gene Extractor, it was obviously impossible for him to use it on Ames; he did not want to die yet.

Its lower limit was not too low, and its upper limit was over the top, so it was quite a good choice.

You have received [Blank Character Summon Card] x 1

Han Xiao nodded. The next time I see the Dragon Emperor, I shall use this. If I can generate some overpowered effect, I might be able to use it to fight a Grade A Super directly, so that will be an option.

No matter how strong a Character Summon Card was, it was considered the user's ability, which met the requirement of the Promotion mission. He did not get the Mission Completion Card this time, but he got another possible method to complete it. Han Xiao took it as a backup choice, but of course, it was based on the fact that he would generate one of the extremely strong abilities from Ames. Something that would demolish a Grade A Super would be best.

For the time being, Han Xiao still preferred to continue trying the random rewards. Although the results at the moment were not satisfactory, he did not think that the plan was a bad idea. He would not give up because of the obstacles so far.

He set the next destination, and the spaceship started its autopilot and headed in that direction. This rented spaceship was focused on speed, so it was suitable to travel to many places.

His choice this time was a simple and straightforward BOSS mission. It did not have rich rewards, but this kind of time-saving mission was exactly what Han Xiao needed.

Furthermore, Aroshia was now Grade B, so fighting a BOSS around the same level would definitely be much easier.

At the same time, in a Star Field extremely distant from Shattered Star Ring, a black spaceship in stealth mode was quietly hovering in space. The exterior of this spaceship was very smooth, reflecting the scenery of the space like a black mirror. It looked like a fan from above and a diamond shape from the front.

It was a Stealth Level Scout Ship, usually known as the Black Light Prowler. As a product of the Federation of Light, it was extremely expensive—top-notch in stealth, detection, speed, and many specifications. Its technology far exceeded most civilizations. On the spaceship black market in various Star Fields, the spaceships from the three Universal Civilizations were the most popular. A second-hand Black Light Prowler could be sold for tens of millions of Enas. It was among the top scout ships.

In other words, this was like an extremely luxurious, high-class sports car.

One nanosecond earlier, a special wave had traveled through countless light-years in the quantum realm and arrived there in an instant. In the cockpit of the spaceship, a finger-sized, oval-shaped accessory was hanging at the top of the cockpit. This transparent accessory received this special wave and emitted a golden glow.

"Hmm?"

A sound appeared in the empty cockpit.

Countless streams of light appeared out of nowhere and gathered into a human-shaped cluster of light. It reached out its hand and touched the accessory that was flickering with weak light.

"Your energy level finally recovered to the level that's locatable by the detector... So, you were thrown to the Shattered Star Ring by the wormhole... I will look for you very soon. Wait for me."

In the blink of an eye, this Black Light Prowler turned into a stream of light and disappeared. It only needed microseconds to warm up before jumping. It was so swift that it was almost impossible to catch.

After Feidin left with the Black Star Mercenary Group, the impact that it made on the entertainment industry stirred up quite a controversy.

The news that 'Chen Xing' had given up his singing career when it was soaring shocked many. Although the reporters and the media did not get any information from Feidin, they started making guesses. Stories with headlines like 'The Real Reason...' spread very quickly, stunning the Chen Xing fans and sparking heated discussions.

However, the entertainment news and the mercenary industry were two different worlds, so Han Xiao did not care. He only paid a little attention when this actually made him more famous.

After completing Chen Xing's mission, he did not waste time and went on to the next location to trigger one of the missions.

In a remote Star System in Colton Star Cluster, the Godoran Civilization had set up research space stations to scout unpopulated planets, researching different planets, life forms, and environments. There were many Observers like Kerlodd in such space stations.

In 075 Godora Research Space Station, upon receiving permit, the spaceship entered the railroad of the space station and parked at the internal dock.

Alighting from the spaceship, Han Xiao and the others looked around. This space station was built to have a very typical Godoran theme.

A few Godora Observers waited at the dock, and one of them asked, "Black Star Mercenary Group, may I know why you are here?"

"Just happened to pass by, and my spaceship needs to refuel, so I'm here to rest for some time. We will pay the corresponding fees, or we can do some missions," Han Xiao said. "Do you have anything here that needs to be dealt with?"

The leader hesitated and shook his head. "There is no extra work here. Since your spaceship needs to be repaired, you can use our shipyard."

Mercenaries were semi-neutral and slightly leaned toward the lawful side. They had an access permit by default and could park in many strongholds of Galactic Civilizations. They have reported their arrival before entering the space station, and as the Black Star Mercenary Group had a good name and had fought against DarkStar some time ago, the space station allowed Han Xiao and his friends to park.

If their negative reputation was too high or even were wanted, not only would they not be able to enter many places, they would also be chased by the police once their location was exposed.

After talking for a while, the Godoran Observer led the way and guided them out of the dock into the space station lounge. According to the management regulations, as soon as their spaceship was refueled, they would have to leave.

Of course, Han Xiao did not go there just to refuel. This Research Space Station had a mission that he wanted to trigger. It was easy to get a high rating and simple to do.

The mission's setting was that a research ship had gone missing and lost contact in a nearby desolate planet. The space station sent another team to look for them, but that team lost contact as well. Hence, the space station reported the situation to the Godoran Directorate General of Intelligence and Investigation and waited for them to send more Observers to investigate the situation. As this was an internal job, the Godoran Observer did not talk about it earlier. They did not want to request help from mercenaries.

However, the players could trigger this mission through the internal personnel in the space station. This was not a hidden mission, so the players just had to pay close attention to the clues, and they would be able to find that person.

That person was Han Xiao's target.

Chapter 459: Low Attribute Does Not Mean That I Am Not Handsome

The space station was not huge. Its exterior was dark gold and gray colored, and its overall design followed the traditional Godora theme—light and twisted.

Unlike other civilizations that focused on accuracy and simplicity, the interior of the space station was rather complicated. One might even get lost without looking at the map on the devices along the corridors. Han Xiao and the others were outsiders, so the restricted areas were not open to them. They could only move around the dock, lounge, and guest hall.

The space station chief was the one who came to welcome them. Despite the Great Mechanic Han not being good at differentiating one Godoran from another, he could tell that this station chief was a very serious person. Standard Observer compressed orbs hung from his Godoran-style hair knot, and his movements and clothes were neat and tidy, classic military style.

Godora Observers came from many backgrounds—some were selected from the military, some were recruited from the society or the security forces then trained, and some took exams to become one. This station chief had clearly once been a military officer; he did things strictly according to the rules and regulations.

The spaceship was sent into the shipyard for repairs and refueling. Han Xiao and the others were resting in the hall. Han Xiao did not tell his friends about the goal of this trip, so the others thought this was just the usual refueling and resting process. Herlous and the three Volga brothers were playing a casual card game at the side. It was a strategic battle style card game—these cards were all renowned individuals and civilizations across the galaxies. Different Star Fields had their own set of cards. For example, in the Shattered Star Ring card set, there were the four Beyond Grade A bosses including Ames.

The battle could be carried out between two or more people. The players would play as a Star Field, pick out a certain number of cards from that Star Field as their card combination, then start the battle. These cards were also classified into different functions—civilization card, strong individual card, exploration card, organization card, ability card, history card, mercenary card, fortune card, treasure card, spaceship card, monster card, and so on. It was very popular across the universe. It was like poker for galactic residents. Other than the standard playing method of acting as a Star Field, there were also many other ways to play it.

In Han Xiao's previous life, quite a number of casual players liked to play this game. They could even find out about the organizations and the force structure of different Star Fields. This card game was made by a galactic commercial organization, and they would update the cards every once in a while, adding new famous people as cards or placing the deceased ones into the 'abandoned card set'. This could almost be considered as the fame leaderboard of the various areas.

Recently, Herlous and the others had become addicted to this card game. This was because in the last update, a few new cards had been added to the Shattered Star Ring card set and the Black Star Mercenary Group was one of them, acting as a new mercenary card.

Mercenary cards were neutral troops, available to recruit any time by spending money, entering the table directly from the card set. It could be used for many purposes including fast attacks and turning around the situation. In the Shattered Star Ring card set, most of the mercenary cards were large mercenary groups consisting of tens of thousands of people such as Sky Ring and Blades. The Black Star Mercenary Group was a new special card. As the Black Star Mercenary Group's size was small and not very strong, the producers gave the card the lowest attribute among the mercenary cards, but it had a special effect.

Since the Black Star Mercenary Group card had the identity of Floating Dragon Field Team, it could be infused with the organization card 'Floating Dragon Island'. If certain requirements were met, the player would be able to draw [Dragon Emperor] Ames directly from the card set.

Han Xiao did not even have to guess where the idea for this card came from—the top news last year about him summoning Ames and Ames destroying the DarkStar mothership with one hit.

In his previous life, the Great Mechanic Han had rarely played this card game as his luck was too bad, but he knew how popular this card game was. He did not expect to now have become a member of the card set, and it was a very pleasant surprise to him. When the players entered space, this would become another way for him to increase his fame.

Since they had been added in as a new card, they could more or less be considered famous. Herlous and the others were having a blast playing it. Of course, they would definitely put something on the line when they played cards.

Beside these gamblers, Sylvia was holding onto a book and memorizing it, immersing herself in the abyss of education. Not far away, Aroshia was resting with her eyes closed. Ever since she entered Grade B, different images had flashed through her mind regularly, causing her to frequently lose her focus. Feidin was sitting in the corner, training his Psychic powers.

The station chief had told them about the rules and regulation in a very serious tone before leaving the hall. Another slightly chubby Godoran with a friendly smile had stayed to take care of them. He had introduced himself as the deputy station chief.

Unlike the station chief, the deputy station chief was very good at chatting and kept a consistent smile on his face. The clue for the mission was with him. Han Xiao vaguely mentioned the topic, and the deputy station chief exposed the clue in a casual chatting tone.

"One of our research spaceships lost contact in a nearby planet. The search team that we sent ended up the same. We saw signs of a spaceship crashing and exploding, so the station chief reported the situation to the superiors. The Directorate General of Intelligence and Investigation planned this mission into their schedule, assuming no one survived... but there's a possibility that those people are still alive waiting for us to send people over. We might have already missed the rescue timing... Sigh, Nereja's wife is in the research team—he has been very anxious recently..."

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled as he asked, "Where can I find this Nereja?"

Deputy station chief shook his head. "This matter has been given to the superiors. According to the rules and regulations, we are not allowed to privately request help from mercenaries."

"I just want to have a talk with him."

"Alright then, he should be at the porthole corridor."

Han Xiao stood up and took his leave, heading toward the location that the deputy station chief told him. Nereja was the person that would trigger the mission.

The deputy station chief looked at Han Xiao's back, and a strange emotion flashed in his eyes.

Han Xiao came to the porthole corridor, and from far away, he could already see a Godoran Observer staring out the window in a daze with a worried expression. Han Xiao quickly walked up to him and asked, "Are you Nereja?"

"You're the mercenaries parked here?" Nereja turned his head to Han Xiao. He was a little on edge.

"Yes. I heard two of your research ships lost contact on a planet. My intuition tells me that there is a job here that needs help."

"This is an internal matter of us Godorans; there is no need for an outsider's help." Nereja frowned. His expression was noticeably irritated when mentioning this matter, and this emotion was clearly not toward Han Xiao, whom he had just met for the first time.

"I heard your wife is in the team. I'm sure you're worried. Maybe she's still alive. For just a small reward, I can help you to find the targets," Han Xiao said.

Hesitation flashed past Nereja's face. He became silent. Han Xiao thought that he would agree, but to Han Xiao's surprise, he shook his head and said, "This is none of your business."

Then, he continued staring outside the window and dazing.

Han Xiao froze. According to the steps in his memories, as long as he mentioned this clue, Nereja's mission would be triggered.

Could it be that I missed something?

He tried convincing Nereja again, but no matter what, Nereja was unwilling to request help from mercenaries. Han Xiao was out of ideas. He pondered hard, and suddenly, he had a flash of inspiration.

Could it actually be because of that?

Han Xiao went back to the hall and dragged Feidin along. On the way, he explained the situation to Feidin, who was still confused. After seeing Nereja, Feidin adjusted his collar and approached him with a gentle smile. Only a few sentences in, Nereja's eyes were filled with tears, and he turned around to look at Han Xiao.

"He's right, I can't let myself regret because of hesitation. Mercenaries, I want to request you to find my wife. This is an act against the regulations, so please don't tell the others."

A notification popped up on Han Xiao's interface immediately.

_____________________

You have triggered mission [Interstellar Beast]

Mission Introduction: You accepted Nereja's request and are planning to head to a desolate planet to look for the research team that has lost contact.

Mission Requirements: Head toward the target planet and investigate the reasons for them losing contact. Search for the missing research team.

Remarks: Your investigation results affect the final rating of the mission.

Basic Reward: 1,358 Enas (In gray), 85,000 experience, Kenorn Diamond Ring (Purple equipment)

_____________________

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes, his feelings indescribable.

It really is because my Charm has yet to reach the standard of triggering the mission...

Chapter 460: Interstellar Beast (1)

The Great Mechanic Han had evolved his race once; his genes were optimized, so his looks were naturally good. Even he was sometimes shocked by how handsome he was when he looked in the mirror. However, Charm was more like affinity—it influenced the default Favorability and hidden options when communicating with others. The effect of some abilities also depended on Charm, such as the summoning abilities and beast controlling abilities.

When affinity was insufficient, others might refuse to communicate further.

The player that triggered this mission in the previous life definitely had enough Charm, so they did not meet any obstacles. According to Han Xiao's rich experience, if the missions could not be triggered even after following the process that he remembered, it would most likely be because a certain hidden prerequisite was not achieved. In those cases, Charm not being high enough was a common one.

However, Han Xiao was definitely not going to put points into his Charm attribute as he was not short of missions. Plus, what on earth was the use of affinity? Being strong was much more useful!

Feidin lived up to his role as an attractiveness focused main character; he convinced Nereja straight away. This mission was not difficult—they just had to investigate the target planet. The mission could be completed even if they only investigated the remains of the spaceships. However, getting a high rating as not that easy. They had to find the majority of the truth about why the research teams had lost contact and find the missing Observers. The mission was called [Interstellar Beast], which was a clue for the players.

Of course, finding Nereja's wife was one way to increase the rating, dead or alive.

In the mission reward, the monetary reward was grayed out, which meant that it was locked, and no matter how high the rating was, there would not be any extra monetary reward. Nereja only had so much money.

I triggered this mission many years before the players did before, so the process should be somewhat different. There are many uncertain factors in this, but the key point should be the same...

When the previous players accepted the mission, the background was different. At that time, the Godora superiors had already sent more than one research teams in, but they had all gone missing. However, they did send back some new intel before going missing, stating that the planet was shrouded in a strange magnetic field that could disrupt most common communications, hence causing all the research teams that landed on that planet to lose contact with the outside world. The crash marks of the spaceships could only be seen by the observation equipment in the space station, which meant that there was definitely something else that had happened to the research team between the time of them losing contact and landing.

Due to it being a natural cause, this did not attract a lot of attention from the Directorate General of Intelligence and Investigation. They were responsible for the investigations of an entire Star System, so there were countless missions for them to do every day, and only the extremely important matters would be passed by the smart system to real people to handle. The smart system ranked the missions according to how important they were, so this mission was placed into a regular mission. After another research team completely lost contact once again, it assumed that all the Observers were dead and stopped investigating that planet. They then told the astronomical observatory to research the environment of this planet first before making further decisions.

Hence, the investigation was put aside for the time being. When the players arrived, only then did this problem get solved—no one was more suitable in exploring unknown dangers than the undying players.

The deputy station chief beside Han Xiao at this time had already become the station chief in his previous life, but he was still the one who gave the mission clue.

Now, these clues had yet to be exposed. Luckily, Han Xiao remembered them, or they would meet dangers if they went there without any information. Han Xiao guessed that if he brought these clues back, it should be calculated into the mission rating.

Nereja took out his communicator, sent over many files, and solemnly said, "Here are the coordinates of that planet and the location of the spaceship's crash site. My wife's name is Lenny. This is her photo, please find her."

"Got it."

Han Xiao nodded and pulled Feidin back to the hall.

As the spaceship had completed its refueling, the station chief appeared again to express his intentions of sending them away. Han Xiao had gotten the mission that he wanted, so he did not stay any longer. He boarded the ship with the others and told them about this operation.

"You actually accepted a private hire? This is Godora's internal matter, and we are sticking our nose in it without their permission—won't Godora have a problem with that?" Herlous was hesitant.

"It's not like that planet belongs to Godora. Nobody said we can't go there."

Han Xiao shrugged and entered the planet's coordinates. It was shown as an unnamed planet. This planet had not yet been fully investigated, so there was no official name for it in the database. This was one of the differences as compared to the situation in his previous life as well.

In the enormous universe, there were still quite a few undiscovered planets. These resource planets with serial numbers were all recorded into the database after field investigations. The planet this time was clearly an unexplored mysterious planet.

In the dark universe, the spaceship tail was producing a dark blue light as the spaceship headed toward the destination. As the spaceship's speed reached its maximum, it turned into a stream of light and entered the jump state, disappearing among the fabulous river of stars.

A few days later, outside the porthole was a small, gray planet. There was no vegetation and no Fixed Stars nearby; it was desolate. No sun could be seen on the planet, and the surface temperature was extremely chilly. There were some markings of volcanoes, so it should not be as cold as absolute zero.

Clearly, the environment of the planet was not suitable for most life forms to survive.

"Wear the protection suit properly. Once your skin is exposed to the air, your body will be damaged."

As Han Xiao was speaking, he activated his Void Dragon mechanical suit, adjusted the inner temperature, and maintained it at a stable level. This slight energy cost was not even worth mentioning for the Mini Portable Nuclear Reactor. Although the suit was powered by nuclear energy, the radiation was blocked by the reactor's special shell. Of course, even if he was exposed to it, Han Xiao would definitely not be damaged with his current Endurance. It would at most give him a negligible damage reduction debuff.

As Herlous was putting on Amphiptere, which Han Xiao lent him, he sighed and said, "If only the Commander Class armor that my brother gave me was still here."

Han Xiao extended his hand with an expressionless face and said, "Give it back if you're not wearing it."

"Come on, don't be so petty." Herlous cracked a joke and hastily put the mechanical suit on.

Aroshia did not need the mechanical suit to protect her. As long as she turned into her energy form, she would be able to ignore the harsh environments.

For this mission, Han Xiao had only brought Herlous and Aroshia along—the rest had all stayed in the spaceship. They were not strong enough, so bringing them along would only burden Han Xiao.

As the magnetic field of the planet could block communications, Han Xiao parked the spaceship outside the atmosphere and set a time to pick them up. The three of them used the mini aircraft to land on the planet.

The spaceship entered the edge of the atmosphere. The cabin under it opened, and a mini aircraft flew out. This was the 'Dragon Butterfly' scout aircraft, a model used by the Floating Dragon Guards. Han Xiao had learned this blueprint long ago.

After the aircraft took off, the spaceship instantly rose higher and left the atmosphere.

Inside the aircraft, Han Xiao sat at the pilot seat and operated the control planet with ease and familiarity. The other two sat in the passenger seats behind him.

"Let's go, the research team's crash site is below."

The magnetic field affected radars too, but Han Xiao adjusted the location when they were on the spaceship. Their destination was right below.

With a tug of the gear lever, the anti-gravity pipes under the aircraft illuminated slightly as they landed quickly.

It was dark around them, and it was very difficult to see. Such planets that did not have light from a Fixed Star existed in many parts of the universe. Han Xiao switched on the aircraft's light perception, and their vision became clearer. They could now see the nearby environment.

"About 6,000 meters to reaching the ground," Herlous said.

"Hold on, there might be some turbulence." As Han Xiao spoke, he suddenly turned off the engine and the anti-gravity levitation device.

Hu!

The aircraft instantly descended forcefully.

Shocked, Herlous said, "What are you doing?"

Before Han Xiao had chance to reply, the aircraft suddenly trembled. Electric sparks erupted from the internal circuits, and at least three-quarters of the buttons on the control panel became unresponsive.

A warning appeared on the radiation detector, and a shadow that looked like a sandstorm swept toward them as seen from the screen.

"At 2,000 to 6,000 meters altitude on this planet, there is a radiation storm that can incapacitate most of the devices in a spaceship. That's how these research spaceships crashed. However, there are still about 2,000 meters for them to buffer before crashing onto the ground, so their shield would be able to prevent them from shattering into pieces when the smash into the ground," Han Xiao explained. "High-class spaceships can make it through, but Godora's research spaceships obviously would not have too many high-end devices equipped."

"What should we do then?" Herlous was stunned. "Aren't we trapped on this planet in that case? Plus, our spaceship won't be able to pick us up."

"Don't worry. Every once in a while, the radiation storm will weaken—we will be able to leave then." Han Xiao was not worried at all; he remembered the mission process. Furthermore, when it was completed, this mission was turned into a dungeon, and the Dungeon Crystal could be earned through doing daily missions in that space station. Countless players had come to this planet before, so he was extremely familiar with it.

The gravity of the planet was quite strong, the aircraft was falling at a very fast speed. They passed through the radiation storm very soon and saw the mountains and craters on the ground, rapidly closing in. At this height, with the strength of the aircraft shield, it would definitely successfully shatter into pieces.

Of course, the three of them would not die from the fall, but the aircraft was a resource, and Han Xiao did not want to give it up easily. As he pressed a button, gliders popped up from the two sides of the aircraft. He switched the aircraft to nerves controlling method and connected the gliders to the nerve signal of his arm. It was as swift and smooth as controlling his own arms.

With the engine still off, the aircraft slowly turned from falling into gliding, quickly approaching the ground.

Boom!

Finally, the aircraft landed on the ground in a slanted angle, stirring up a huge amount of sand and dust. The shield generator was still working and flickering. The shield and the incapacitated thrust engine were not in the same system and had different fundamentals. Although the shield had been affected by the radiation storm, it had already recovered to a certain extent.

Turbulence still lasted in the aircraft for quite some time before quietening down. Aroshia rubbed her butt. Since she did not turn into energy form, her butt was hurting from the turbulence.

Han Xiao stood up and pulled down the manual handle on the hatch. The hatch popped open, and extreme coldness blew onto their faces. The temperature inside the mechanical suit lowered largely in an instant before slowly recovering to the normal temperature.

"The air temperature is about minus a hundred degrees. It is... actually higher than expected. Looks like there are bodies of water on this planet.

Han Xiao stretched his arms and legs, breathing in the oxygen from the mechanical suit. He was not planning to run around in this kind of place without wearing a mechanical suit.

Aroshia almost froze from the coldness and hurriedly turned into energy form. After entering Grade B, she had become much more skilled in using her powers. When she turned into energy form, she still maintained her human figure, including all of her facial features. Other than her body being made up of bright energy, everything else remained unchanged.

"The landing location deviated a little from the target without a radar." Herlous looked around. "Looks like we can only slowly search for the remains of the research ships."

Han Xiao squatted and touched the ground. Under the rough and black dust were hard rocks—the density of the planet surface was rather high. He then looked up and searched for certain markings on the sky.

Very soon, through the vision zoom of the mechanical suit, he saw the light from the spaceship outside the atmosphere. He pointed in that direction and said, "There is no need to search. The target is right there."

Chapter 461: [Interstellar Beast] (2)

The weather was freezing. On the empty gray planet surface, craters could be seen everywhere. The spaceship outside the atmosphere was acting as a guide, so Han Xiao, Herlous, and Aroshia walked in that direction. Although the gravity of this planet was quite high, it had minimal impact on Grade B Supers. After a while, a spaceship wreckage appeared before them.

This was a Godora research ship. Its light gold shell was covered in black dust, its body was twisted by the crash, and behind it was a fissure that stretched hundreds of meters with pieces of the spaceship here and there. Clearly, the spaceship had skidded for a distance after crashing.

Herlous looked at his tactical screen and said, "It's dead silent, and there are no thermal signs. I think we should go there to take a look."

"Thanks for making a suggestion that no one thought of." Han Xiao rolled his eyes.

Herlous shrugged. "You're really being more and more gentle in your words. I keep having a feeling that you're targeting me."

"I'm only well-mannered toward strangers."

"I'm flattered." Herlous changed the topic. "This mechanical suit of yours has quite a number of functions."

"What, the armor your brother left you does not have these functions?"

"Ha. My brother knows me too well. He knows that I don't like these fancy functions; the armor that he tailor-made for me has maximized combat functions. To know how strong the enemy is, I just have to fight him. What's there to analyze? Speaking of which, these people on my home planet took my armor and have been researching it for a year. I even gave my brother's notes to them, so they should have gotten some results by now. How about we find a chance to return there and get my armor?"

"You actually made a genuine suggestion," Han Xiao said with a surprised tone. "How shocking."

Herlous was speechless. I really want to draw my sword, but I have to maintain a smile.

As they casually chatted, the three of them arrived at the wreckage. This was a medium-sized research ship. It was divided into many cabins and was more than ten meters high. As they got closer, more details appeared before their eyes. There was a huge hole on the side of its body, but the hatch was still closed. Han Xiao peeked into the cabin; it was completely dark. Apparently, the system was basically incapacitated.

"Let's go in and see if there are any survivors or corpses," Han Xiao said. Although he remembered how the mission would go, since he came at a different time, he did not know if there would be any slight changes.

He explored inside the cabin, and no one was in it. Han Xiao switched to the tracing interface and discovered some panicking footsteps. After extracting the newest markings, he realized that these people did not leave the spaceship. There were also markings of someone being dragged along the floor in some rooms.

"Hmm, it's obvious that the shield did not fully protect them, and some people fainted. However, none of their footsteps left the spaceship. It seems like everyone disappeared into thin air. The hatch is closed, which means that that hole was made by something else. It looks like there are some special life forms on this planet, and these things are the reason for the ship crew's disappearance."

Han Xiao spoke fluently. He walked around the scene and briefly investigated. The situation was not much different from the mission in his previous life, which instantly lessened his worries. Ever since his Intelligence attribute became higher, he realized that his memory had become stronger as well. Some of the blurry memories started becoming clearer.

The mission rating depended on the investigation results. Hence, although Han Xiao knew where the final Boss was, he was not in a hurry to go there. He moved to the control room of the spaceship, found the central computer, and manually rebooted the spaceship system.

Hum!

The spaceship shook, and all the rooms inside lit up.

"Reboot complete. Initiating self-diagnostics... Damage rate 72%. Most devices are incapacitated. Fuel leak detected, 3% energy remaining. Activating Advanced Power Saving Mode..."

Han Xiao pressed a few buttons. "Turn on ship recordings."

"Insufficient energy. Request rejected."

"Switch to manual mode."

"Please confirm Observer ID."

Han Xiao thought about it before taking out his communicator and searching for a while in the notes. Then, he entered Kerlodd's ID.

"Connecting headquarters database... connection failed. Signal disrupted by an unknown source. Connecting local database... successfully connected. Authorizing access... authorization failed. This ID is not in the crew list of this ship."

"Godora's operation system is so damn terrible."

Han Xiao's mouth twitched. He dismantled the central computer shell and pulled out the smart chip directly, taking the chip back to the space station would have the same result.

He dismantled all sorts of core parts of the spaceship—all of them would increase his mission rating if he took them back. Then, the three of them walked out of the cabin. There was nothing valuable left inside.

Herlous hesitated and said, "If the crews were captured by some life form, doesn't that mean that said life form can fly? Since there are no signs of any creatures walking outside here. How do we find it then?"

Han Xiao touched the edge of the hole—there was a layer of ice on it. "The other parts of the spaceship did not freeze; only this part has frozen markings, meaning that the water vapor was brought by that creature. With such a low temperature here, if there is a water body, it should be a geothermal hot spring that might be underground. This creature most likely used it as its nest..."

Herlous' eyes sparkled. "So, these Observers might still be alive!"

"I don't know." Han Xiao gave a perfunctory reply. "There's another spaceship wreckage nearby. Let's go there to take a look."

Soon after, they found the wreckage of the second research ship. Identical to the previous one, there was no one inside. However, the markings were different. There were messy footsteps outside the spaceship and even signs of a battle. The second batch of Observers on this ship were stronger than the previous ones, so they still had the strength to resist after crashing. However, their ending was clear—they had all been defeated.

"There are more ice markings one the ground but no frozen blood, so no one should have died. There aren't many battle markings, so these Observers were clearly demolished."

After looking through the clues, Han Xiao dismantled all the core parts of this spaceship as well and said, "Let's go. I roughly know where that creature is."

Following the path in his memories, Han Xiao advanced quickly without stopping. Usually, only by collecting more clues nearby would they be able to discover the nest of the Boss. However, the mission rating would not be high this way. In his previous life, there were more spaceship wreckages at that period in time, meaning that there were more clues. The clues they had now were many times fewer, which was not very beneficial. Han Xiao, however, did not have to go through so much trouble—he headed to the location in his memory directly.

Very soon, they found a hidden nest at the bottom of a crater. There were signs of burrowing, and the entrance was about four to five meters wide, rather spacious. The path was slanted downward. The three of them slid along the tunnel and finally stepped on solid ground.

Around them was the dark underground. The temperature there was much higher than that of the surface. There was only one way forward—it was a dead end behind them.

Han Xiao activated night vision, walked forward for a while, and came across a fork in the road. Without hesitation, Han Xiao took the left path. The temperature gradually increased. Herlous took off his helmet, sensed the surroundings, and said, "This temperature is quite comfortable."

"We're almost there. Get ready for battle," Han Xiao said.

The three of them arrived at the end of the tunnel. Before them was an underground lake. The water was boiling with bubbles rising to the surface, causing the area above the lake to be filled with a thick mist. This lake was like a hot spring, meaning that there should be a geothermal area below it that caused the hot spring to form.

This time, an exclamation came from the hot spring.

"Who are you?" A naked Godoran appeared in the hot spring, looking at them with surprise. Water rolled down her curvy body.

Herlous first looked down, then up, then repeated the process a few times before he realized. "You're Lenny?"

"You know me?" The female Godoran was surprised. She was indeed Nereja's wife.

"We're mercenaries. We accepted your husband's request and came to save you. Where are the others?" Herlous asked.

"That's amazing. Finally, someone came to save us. The others are..."

Joy appeared on Lenny's face, but suddenly, her expression changed, and she anxiously said, "Don't stand there. It's coming out!"

Just as she finished her sentence, a small whirlpool formed in the middle of the hot spring lake. Something large was rising to the surface. A tsunami-like wave expanded from the middle and splashed onto Han Xiao and the others.

Boom!

A strange creature jumped out of the lake and levitated midair before turning toward the three people on the shore.

"What... is this?" Herlous' eyes opened wide.

"An Interstellar Beast, a space creature born between stars," Han Xiao quickly explained. "It can fly in space with its body and increase its speed through the gravitational force of planets to reach the speed of spaceships. Although it cannot jump like a spaceship and usually has to fly alone for thousands of years, its lifespan is almost infinite. They can keep molting and renew their cells—they're very rare. Mages can summon Interstellar Beasts through an ancient ceremony. The spell is unidirectional and ignores physical distance. However, they summon Interstellar Beast mostly to hunt and kill them. After all, an Interstellar Beast's body is a very rare material."

The Interstellar Beast before them looked very strange. It had a slender, violet body that was tens of meters long. It had no scales or hair and was very smooth. Its skin had a translucent texture, emitting a dim light under its skin. It had no limbs—its front and tail were narrow while the middle of it was wide, looking like a fin. There was only a long tentacle on its head and nothing else. At the end of the tentacle was a clear crystal. It looked similar to marine life forms.

The Interstellar Beast spun in midair like a fish swimming swiftly in water. Its tentacle vibrated, and Han Xiao suddenly felt an invisible force trying to pull him to the Interstellar Beast. His body started levitating uncontrollably.

"Ha!"

Herlous acted first. He slashed his Battleship Slicing Blade, sending out a beam of blade shaped light, directly hitting the Interstellar Beast's body. However, it shattered in an explosion, and the Interstellar Beast was unhurt; it did not even move an inch.

"Don't hope to hurt an interstellar creature that can travel through the universe with its body this easily." Han Xiao pulled out an electromagnetic firearm and fired. The bullet bounced off the Interstellar Beast's body, and a damage number "1" appeared.

The Interstellar Beast's attributes appeared on the interface.

_____________________

[Interstellar Beast]

Level: ?

Class: [Space Creature—Interstellar Beast] (END to HP conversion rate: 1:500)

Attributes: ? STR, ? DEX, 500 END, ? INT, ?MYS, 153 CHA, ? LUK.

Energy: 0

Energy Rank: ?

Health: 249,986

Status: Normal

Talents: Unknown

Abilities: Unknown

_____________________

Han Xiao nodded in his mind. He had known the Interstellar Beast's attributes since the start. As a Space Creature, its health was outrageous. Without a doubt, it was a true Boss. Furthermore, its Physical Resistance and Magic Resistance were very high, so attacking its body would deal close to no damage. The players in his previous life had been wiped out once before finding a way to defeat it.

The weak spot of the Interstellar Beast was its tentacle crystal. It almost had no resistance, so basically, every hit on it would deal True Damage.

Every time the damage accumulated to 50,000, the Interstellar Beast's entire body's resistance would decrease by twenty percent, which would allow attacks on its body to deal some damage. The Interstellar Beast's attacks were controlling objects with its mind, similar to Psychic. It was good at disabling enemies and could redirect the ballistics aimed at its vital spot. The good thing was that its damage was not very high. The only way to defeat it was to take it slow.

However, to Han Xiao, as long as the enemy's damage was limited, it would not be a threat.

Chapter 462: Pet (1)

The enormous body obstructed all of Han Xiao's vision. Compared to its size, Han Xiao was tiny. It was like the difference between a sparrow and an elephant.

The invisible Psychic power surrounding Han Xiao's body did not express any intention to attack. It seemed like the Interstellar Beast just wanted to pull Han Xiao to him and observe him out of curiosity. The attack earlier was no different from a scratch to the Interstellar Beast.

As Han Xiao levitated in midair, two rows of thrust pipes emerged on the back of his mechanical suit. A strong air stream gushed out, and the force allowed him to escape from the Psychic power. His electromagnetic scythe expanded in the blink of an eye as he slashed the Interstellar Beast's tentacle.

Clunk!

The blade of the scythe struck the crystal violently, and blinding electric sparks exploded. The Interstellar Beast's tentacle quickly retracted, and its body tensed as its vital spot was hit.

This slash dealt close to a thousand points of damage. Compared to its tough body, its tentacle had close to no resistance.

Suddenly, the light on the Interstellar Beast's tentacle became dozens of times brighter like a flashbang exploding out of nowhere. The almost blinding light filled the entire underground cave. Han Xiao and Herlous' vision was covered in white. Before they could adjust, a tremendous force hit onto their body, pushed them away and into the cave wall.

Boom!

The impact wave caused by its Psychic power echoed in the cave. The lake and the cave started to tremble, and countless rocks splashed into the underground hot spring.

"Look, it's angry." Han Xiao stretched his neck and chuckled.

A pipe flickering with blue light appeared on his wrist armor plate, which then shot out compressed orbs one after another that quickly turned into artilleries.

Boom boom boom!

A violent, wild storm of metal erupted in the cave!

Countless bullets hit the Interstellar Beast's body. Its tentacle emitted Psychic energy that formed a shield, changing the direction of the bullets continuously.

Herlous jumped up and landed on the Interstellar Beast's body. Close range battles were his specialty. He swung the Battleship Slicing Blade and slashed down on the Interstellar Beast's back. Although it was no different from a massage to the Interstellar Beast, at least he was spirited. He slashed toward the tentacle on the Interstellar Beast's head.

The Interstellar Beast's movements were very swift as it turned and rotated in the air rapidly. Herlous wanted to hold on, but the skin of the Interstellar Beast was exceptionally smooth, so there was no leverage, not even a single hair.

In comparison, Aroshia made a bigger impact. After she turned into energy form, the Psychic powers could not control her body but only disrupt her energy frequency, which was almost useless. She flew to the Interstellar Beast's head with ease and gently held onto its tentacle.

The next moment, highly concentrated energy exploded in her palms.

Boom!

The explosions were continuous, the Interstellar Beast twitching in pain all the while. With its vital spot being used like a boxer used a sandbag, the agony would be indescribable. Han Xiao could almost feel the pain just by looking at it. If the Interstellar Beast had an organ to generate a voice, he was certain that it would be screaming with all its might.

After Aroshia entered Grade B, the strength of her Esper power skyrocketed. She took on the role as the main damage dealer and made a tremendous impact.

The three of them surrounded the Interstellar Beast. Psychic energy was exploding, bullets were raining down, and slashes were landing continuously. It was intense and heated.

Swoosh!

Although this was just an underground lake, the impact of the battle was like a hurricane that stirred up the lake.

Lenny and a few other naked Godorans hastily climbed out of the hot spring, leaned against the cave wall, and nervously watched the battle. They could not interfere with a battle involving Grade B Supers.

The Interstellar Beast's health went down slowly but surely. Even though it protected its vital spot as much as it could, there were times when Han Xiao and the others' attacks penetrated its defenses. The Interstellar Beast's Psychic powers were only limited to pushing and controlling objects—it dealt very limited damage to Han Xiao. All in all, it was a worry-free fight.

Not long after, the Interstellar Beast's health dropped by 50,000. Its resistance decreased by a large portion, and the damage dealt by the three of them increased.

Although Space Creatures had very thick skin, the Interstellar Beasts were not adept at battle. It could only be ranked as Grade B, and even that was because of his outrageously high health that ranked among the top even in the countless Bosses. If the players did not have sufficient damage, they would be defeated due to exhaustion. After all, their energy and stamina were limited.

The three of them could deal more than enough damage, but after fighting intensively for so long, their energy and stamina was reducing as time passed by.

Bang!

The battle lasted a long, long time. When the Interstellar Beast only had five percent of its health left, it could not continue levitating and fell into the hot spring, making a huge wave.

Han Xiao gave Herlous a signal, and the two of them dived into the lake. After looking for quite some time, they finally found the near-death Interstellar Beast at the bottom of the lake. Han Xiao grabbed this monster, turned his mechanical suit to maximum power output, and slowly dragged it onto the shore.

Its gigantic body was covered in wounds with violet slime flowing out of them. Its tentacle crystal was filled with cracks and emitting very dim light. The Interstellar Beast was squirming weakly. Han Xiao made sure that the thing did not have any more energy to battle before exhaling deeply and swinging his arms to loosen his sore muscles.

Although he was protected by the mechanical suit, it was still painful being smashed and thrown around by the Interstellar Beast.

Herlous took off his helmet, his hair damp from his sweat. He held his knees and panted. "This guy is way too resistant. I'm exhausted..."

Aroshia's body was much dimmer; she had spent more than eighty percent of her energy.

Han Xiao looked at the interface. He still had a lot of health, but his energy and stamina were almost empty. He collected all the artilleries and counted—twenty-something artilleries had been squashed by the Interstellar Beast's Psychic power.

"You guys defeated it!"

Lenny and the others walked over with stunned expressions.

Han Xiao turned around and looked at them. He frowned and said, "Where are your clothes? Also, you guys should not be the only missing Observers. Where are the others?"

"This monster took off our clothes—it probably thinks they're our weapon. We were usually suppressed under the lake by this monster. Maybe he took us as trophies," Lenny said.

"Take your clothes, let's talk when you have them on."

Han Xiao glanced at her indifferently.

Compared to women, Han Xiao was more interested in robots. He was a real man!

He turned around and saw that Herlous could not take his eyes off Lenny. He patted him and said with a displeased tone, "Don't stare at her—that's the employer's wife. I don't want to be refused the reward in the end."

Herlous scratched his head. Before he could speak in his defense, Lenny laughed alluringly.

She was in a very good mood after being rescued. She blinked and said with a smile, "It's okay, us Godorans are very open-minded. You guys saved my life, so maybe..."

"Stop, I'm not interested in golden skins."

Han Xiao shivered in his mind.

Damn, this wild‽

Brother Nereja, you are so green[1]**!

[1] "Wearing a green hat" is a slightly offensive and mocking term often used in Mandarin to describe someone whose partner cheated on them. For example, "he is wearing a green hat" means his wife cheated on him. Back

Chapter 463: Pet (2)

Lenny shrugged, and they went below the water, quickly picked up a large pile of Observer standard equipment, and put them on.

"Where are your other friends?" Han Xiao coughed drily.

"Many of them died. This monster robbed our equipment, so if we went too far from the hot spring, we would very likely freeze to death. Some people were dragged underwater by this monster for too long and drowned. Other than us, there is another group of people that's alive at the other end of the cave tunnel. There's another hot spring there.

Han Xiao nodded. There was a fork when he came, and the other side led to the hot spring where the other Observers were. If they had gone to the other side first, they would have gotten intel about Interstellar Beast in advance, but he did not have to do that.

"Why did this Interstellar Beast capture you people?" Herlous asked curiously. "It seems like it's deliberately trapping you here."

Anger appeared on Lenny's face as she said, "This monster appeared after we crashed. It brought us here, let us move freely in the hot spring, and would sometimes drag us into the water and throw us around like it was playing. It kept us as pets!"

On a life form level perspective, the Space Creatures were superior life forms to humans. Making humans their pets was the same as humans taming beasts as pets. It was almost a law of nature.

However, when humans that were used to turning other species into pets became pets themselves, it felt like their superiority was being stepped on. These Godorans felt enraged and ashamed.

Han Xiao raised his eyebrows and did not comment. Whoever had power could do whatever they wanted with the weak. Outside the areas with civilizations, this law of the jungle was the only truth. He straightforwardly said, "Alright, you're already rescued. When the radiation storm in the sky is weaker, we will be able to leave. Old Herlous, go to the hot spring on the other side and bring the other Observers here."

Bringing those Observers back could drastically increase the mission rating. After making the arrangements, Han Xiao turned to look at Interstellar Beast that lay on the ground.

The only problem left was how to deal with this beast.

"This is the first Interstellar Beast discovered by Godora, so it will be very important research material. If you can bring it back to the space station, we will pay you a very high reward." Lenny was wearing her Observer combat suit and had tied up her hair; she looked neat and confident.

Han Xiao squinted and pondered.

Give it to Godora? No, that would not be worth it at all. Interstellar Beasts were extremely rare and filled with treasures. The important parts of Interstellar Beast could be made into Gene Potions that could increase one's attributes. There was even a chance of getting a talent from the potion. Plus, it would increase the choices during Race Evolution. Furthermore, killing it would trigger a Legendary Milestone.

Most importantly, the powder created by crushing an Interstellar Beast's crystal could be made into a special potion. It had no effect on the players but was extremely rare. It could even be used as a currency to purchase any resources from NPCs.

Such potions only had one effect—to grant part of the Interstellar Beast's metabolism adjusting ability. Simply put, this thing could extend one's life span!

Han Xiao had worried about such an issue since the beginning. It would not be a problem in the earlier versions of Galaxy, but the time skips between versions would become longer and longer. Hundreds of years would pass between versions. The life span of Supers was many times that of ordinary people, but in the history of tens of thousands of years, it was still just a very small part.

There were few ways to increase one's life span. Installing mechanic prosthetics was one of them, but it had very visible side effects. On the other hand, the Interstellar Beast potion had close to no side effects.

This is very important, so it cannot be wasted.

Han Xiao's eyes became firm. He grabbed tightly onto the Interstellar Beast's crystal, and a wave of emotions were transmitted from the crystal to his mind.

It was begging.

The Interstellar Beast was begging him for mercy.

Han Xiao ignored it completely, and Void Jet Spray exploded in his palm.

Boom!

The crystal, already covered in cracks, shattered into pieces and fell into Han Xiao's hands. The violet light under the Interstellar Beast's skin faded. Life escaped from this Space Creature.

This crystal was Interstellar Beast's life core, and it was also the most important material.

_____________________

You have killed a Space Creature.

[Legendary Hunter] Milestone activated.

Current Progress: 1/5 (Kill 5 special creatures)

_____________________

This was a Legendary Milestone. Upon completion, corresponding Legendary Points would be granted. The special creatures stated here were all sorts of rare and special creatures including Space Creatures that had Boss level attributes. Also, Bosses in dungeons were not counted.

Luckily, there were many monsters in Galaxy. Even by the latest version that Han Xiao had played in his previous life, despite the game being played by countless players for many years, there were still cases of players killing a special creature occasionally. After all, there would always be new creatures being born in the universe. Of course, the competition to kill them was very intense.

Some special Legendary Points could open a certain corresponding storyline. [Legendary Hunter] was one of them—it was similar to a title.

Han Xiao stowed the crystal, pulled out his scythe, and sliced the Interstellar Beast's carcass. He quickly collected the important parts. An Interstellar Beast's carcass would not rot easily and could be kept for a very long time.

Very soon, this Interstellar Beast was only left with an incomplete carcass.

"Sigh..." Lenny's face was filled with regret, but she did not have a problem with it. This beast was Han Xiao's trophy to start with, so he was free to do whatever he wanted with it.

This time, Herlous finally brought the other Observers over.

The Godorans were all surprised. Moments ago, they had still been trapped in the hot spring and singing, but the next moment, they had suddenly been rescued by mercenaries. It felt like a dream.

Seeing the Interstellar Beast's carcass, the new group of Observers sized Han Xiao up with shock. They had suffered quite a lot from this monster, and they knew how strong the Interstellar Beast was.

"Everyone's here, let's go," Han Xiao said.

...

Han Xiao tested the radiation strength with a device as they returned to the surface. After waiting a few days, the short window in the radiation storm finally arrived. They hastily boarded the aircraft and went straight up into the sky.

The aircraft had a capacity for about ten people, but there were more than ten Observers. It was crowded in the cabin.

They passed by the storm area successfully, and the spaceship went to pick them up.

All the Observers that escaped from death hugged each other passionately, overjoyed.

Han Xiao had his mind on the mission, so he did not waste any time. He set the return route and headed back immediately.

A few days later, the spaceship returned to the space station. This time, when they requested to enter, they conveyed the fact that they had rescued the lost Observers. Everyone in the space station was shocked.

The space station immediately opened up its port. Unlike the cold treatment last time, the attitude of the space station's people completely changed, and they welcomed them enthusiastically.

The spaceship docked at the port. As soon as the cabin opened, Han Xiao saw that almost everyone in the space station had gathered at the port. The station chief stood at the front. Surprise and contentment were on this serious army officer's face.

Beside him, the deputy station chief was smiling as usual. However, for some reason, his smile was a little stiff, and there was a faint sense of irritation in his eyes.

Chapter 464: If Godora Was More Conservative, DarkStar Would Never Have Been Created.

"Darling!"

Nereja squeezed himself out of the crowd and opened his arms with excitement on his face.

A smile appeared on Lenny's face as she saw her husband. She dashed into his arms, then kissed his forehead, and they started kissing passionately. She hung on Nereja's neck like a koala. Their position was so fiery that it looked like they were going to do it on the spot. Han Xiao's eyes hurt from watching it, and the image of back then when he captured Kerlodd and stripped him naked appeared in his mind. Muscular, wide shoulders, small member. No wonder there were so many hybrids in Godora...

The other surviving Observers jumped down from the spaceship and hugged their friends.

When Han Xiao got off the spaceship, the space station chief approached and said with a surprised tone, "Black Star, this is..."

Obviously, the station chief did not know that Nereja had hired mercenaries privately. Hiring mercenaries for internal matters without permission was against the regulation in Godora, and the punishment would be given depending on how serious the situation was. It would also be added to their permanent record and affect their future and promotions.

When Nereja gave the mission, he had requested Han Xiao not to leak this information. However, keeping it a secret might lead to missed opportunities and lowered rating, so Han Xiao did not listen to him and told Lenny and the other survivors about it. These Godoran Observers, of course, knew about the regulation. After discussing it privately on the spaceship, they decided to keep the identity of the employer a secret. After all, Nereja had taken the risk to hire the mercenaries to save them, so they were willing to cover it up.

The Observers around them heard the station chief's question and all looked over. The survived Observers looked at Han Xiao worriedly, Nereja swallowed his saliva nervously.

These people were worried that Han Xiao would tell the truth. As Black Star was not an official of Godora, maybe he did not know about their regulations.

Han Xiao smiled and said, "When I was here, I heard about the research ships. I'm a mercenary, so I won't give up any opportunity to make a fortune. Mr. Station Chief, my services are not free. Maybe you should pay a reasonable price for my labor."

Nereja heaved a sigh of relief, and the other Observers were thankful, too. They looked at Han Xiao discreetly with appreciation.

In order to protect the employer's identity, this mercenary is even putting up a show. That is some dedication to his profession.

The station chief was puzzled and a little troubled. "According to our regulations, we can't pay you any money. This was your own action; we did not hire you."

Han Xiao raised his eyebrows. "Are you saying that I worked for free? Is this how Godorans treat their friends?"

A shade of joy flashed through the deputy station chief's eyes. He coughed and said, "Station chief, he rescued the missing people after all. Although it's against the regulations, I feel that we should return the favor. We should thank him for saving the lives of these Observers. Godorans never treat our friends badly."

The station chief frowned and firmly shook his head. "Regulations are regulations. I appreciate your actions, but I really cannot pay you. This was your own action. If I paid you a reward, it would become a hire. That would be against the regulations."

The faces of the crowd around them changed in dissatisfaction, especially the surviving Observers including Lenny. Their eyes turned rather cold.

These mercenaries saved us, yet you don't even want to give a reward. Are our lives this cheap in your eyes?

Although they were unhappy, they did not say anything. The regulations were not to be disobeyed.

Han Xiao squinted and said in a deliberately indifferent tone, "Okay, I shall just say that I did a good deed. I want to park here for a day, will you maybe allow that?"

Seeing that he did not forcefully ask for a reward, the station chief felt relieved. He nodded and said, "Yes, we always welcome our friends."

Hearing this, the crowd around them stared at the station chief in discontent before looking at Han Xiao with even more appreciation.

The station chief turned around and left, and the crowd gradually split up as well. When they passed Han Xiao, they greeted him with a solemn gesture, expressing their appreciation.

In a corridor far away with only the deputy station chief and station chief, the deputy station chief took a few steps forward and walked beside the station chief. "You're too stubborn."

The space station shook his head and said with a very serious expression, "This is not being stubborn but principles. Since I was assigned to this place by the superiors, my job is to supervise all the work here and make sure that everyone does things following the regulations."

"Sigh, you're right." The deputy station chief purposely acted regretful. "Very few mercenaries would only negotiate a price after doing the job—their actions were not a coincidence. They probably accepted a secret hire from a space station employee long ago..."

The station chief suddenly stopped walking and said, "You're right... Those mercenaries deliberately lied earlier because they wanted to make more money. Humph, mercenaries indeed are a group of greedy people. Investigate it. I want to know who the one that hired the mercenaries was."

The deputy station chief hastily discouraged the station chief and said, "For things like this, knowing about it in our hearts is enough. Don't be so serious about it. No matter what, all the lost Observers returning is a good thing. If you act as if you don't know about this and don't look for who's responsible, the regulation violation will not exist. When you report to the superiors, you can write it into your own merits. This will be very beneficial for your future. They will think that you're very capable."

The station chief frowned and said in a righteous tone, "Merits? I won't hide the truth for something like this! Investigative who hired the Black Star Mercenary Group. A violation is a violation; no leniency is allowed."

...

Back at the hall, Nereja found Han Xiao. The two of them walked to the side, and he grabbed Han Xiao's hand with a face filled with gratitude.

"Thank you so much for your help. Lenny and I don't even know how to repay you."

Han Xiao pulled his hands back, shrugged, and said, "Of course you know how to repay me. We agreed on the reward."

"Yes, yes, yes, of course, I'm just too excited." Nereja took out his communicator and quickly made a transfer.

[Interstellar Beast] Completed!

Grading mission... grading complete.

Mission Rating: Excellent

You have received [Excellent] grade bonus reward: Bonus 50% experience (425,000), Random Reward x 1

Only Excellent... Han Xiao thought. The chance of getting a random reward from Excellent grade is only thirty percent. Luckily, I still got it.

+35 Nereja Favorability

+20 Lenny Favorability

This Favorability... Han Xiao's mouth twitched. Why do I feel like there's a green color to it?

Godorans really could not be messed with. No wonder they had so many hybrids...

Putting those thoughts behind, Han Xiao activated the Random Reward on his interface.

Randomizing...

Randomizing complete

Your Random Reward Type is: [Attribute Point]

"How great."

Han Xiao's tone was calm, and he was expressionless.

At this point, he was already very calm about it... or at least he seemed very calm.

"I'm not angry, not at all."

Han Xiao took a deep breath and looked at the three choices.

Please select one from the three reward below

DEX: 3 – 6

INT: 2 – 6

LUK: 1 – 8

Han Xiao glanced through and picked Intelligence without hesitation. The numbers behind it were the range of the random attributes given.

+5 INT

Not too bad. Although it's not very good, a permanent attribute point is acceptable. This is the first time I've gotten an attribute reward from the Random Reward. It's worth remembering.

Han Xiao comforted himself more than ten times in his mind and felt like he was feeling much better, although it might have been his imagination.

After Han Xiao got the money in his account, Nereja took out a white diamond ring from his pocket, looked at it for a while with reluctance in his eyes, and then solemnly placed it into Han Xiao's hand.

"I know I don't have much money, and these rewards are too little for you, but you still chose to help me. I'm very touched and thankful. This ring is called the Kenorn Diamond Ring. It's a magic treasure that I collected. I want you to know that not all Godorans are as petty as the station chief. Please accept my gift."

The inside of the diamond on the ring had a magic glow. Han Xiao held onto the ring and looked at the item description on the interface.

[Kenorn Diamond Ring]

Grade: Purple

Type: Magic Equipment—Ring

Equipment Effect: +9% Magic Resistance, +7% Magic Affinity, +11 INT, +23 MYS, +5 CHA

Equipment Requirement: Mage, above level 80.

Additional Ability: [Ring of Arcane]

Passive aura: Permanently increases the vitality of magic in a 15 meters diameter, +13% damage of all magic attacks.

Remarks: This ring is engraved with a very strong enchantment, and it has an enormous amount of magic power. The creator of this ring is clearly an arcane master.

Magic equipment, its attribute boost is not bad. The aura is perfect for dungeons. These guilds will definitely be willing to pay a huge sum for it. Sadly, this thing has limited use to me.

The oldest and second oldest Volga brothers were the only Mages in the mercenary group, and they had a high enough level, so it could only be given to them. Anyway, the players were not there for the time being, so there was no need to sell it.

After bidding Nereja farewell, Han Xiao returned to the hall and casually threw the ring to the Volga brothers. The three of them cheered with joy and went to the side to look at it closely, leaving Herlous there holding onto his cards and staring at the game that he was going to win money from.

"Now that everything's over, are we not leaving yet?" Feidin asked.

Han Xiao's eyes flickered. "There are more situations here, but I have already done what I should do. The situation will only become beneficial after a very long time. When that happens, it might be worth it to return here... Alright, pack up then, we will be leaving in a short while. Nothing will be happening here for now, so there is no need to continue staying here."

The others did not understand what he meant.

"You're the captain—you know what to do," Herlous said. "Where are we going next?"

Han Xiao thought of the Interstellar Beast materials in the spaceship and said, "We need to find someone to turn that carcass in the warehouse into potions first."

Although finding the Mission Completion Card was important, he was not in a hurry. Anyway, being in a hurry would not make him any luckier.

Doing missions could be postponed temporarily. To him, dealing with the Interstellar Beast's materials was the most important matter.

Chapter 465: Life Span Potion

In the vast universe, new species were being born every second. Finding out about the valuable parts of all kinds of flora and fauna, extracting them, and making them into potions was a very complicated, profound subject. This was especially true in Galaxy, where there were countless species; it required a lot of patience and skill.

There were also many different methods of extraction and making potions, such as chemical extractions from the technological side and witchcraft decoctions from the magic side.

The Pharmacist Association was the authorized organization in the universe. Just like the Spacetime Research Council, this was a platform for the Pharmacists to communicate with each other. It was also the simplest way for the galactic residents to hire Pharmacists. All they had to do was log into the Pharmacist Association website, and there would be Pharmacist Apprentices online who would inquire about the customers' needs. It felt like those online doctor inquiry websites in Han Xiao's previous life.

As the matters in the space station came to an end, Han Xiao immediately contacted the Pharmacist Association and found a dependable pharmaceutical organization that produced Interstellar Beast potions. This organization was located on a colonized planet of the Purple Crystal Civilization in the Colton Star Cluster.

Purple Crystal was one of the strongest civilizations in the Shattered Star Ring.

Godora was a Star System level civilization, and there were many Star System level civilizations in Colton Star Cluster—Godora from the Gavin Star System, New Phylen from the Rain Star System, Black Raven and Holy Stone from the Fawn Star System, and many more. Purple Crystal Civilization, however, was a Star Cluster level civilization. Its colonized planets spread across the various Star Clusters and Star Systems of the Shattered Star Ring.

Juberly Hub had stable stargates connected to the various Star Systems in Colton. Those Star System Civilizations in Colton were the ones that co-funded and invited Purple Crystal Civilization to build the stargates.

The level of Purple Crystal was too high, so Han Xiao did not want to have a deep connection with them for the time being. The risk would only be higher than the benefits. His goal for this trip was only to make the potion.

There were no twist and turns throughout the process. Perhaps the Shattered Star Ring was rather dangerous, but few galactic pirates or scavengers dared to mess around near the stronghold of Star Cluster Civilizations. The security weapons of Star Cluster Civilizations had very long attack ranges. If they discovered there were criminals causing problems near their colonized planet, they would not even need to send out spaceships to chase them. They just had to fire the weapons from their planet, and those criminals would become fireworks.

The pharmaceutical company that Han Xiao had chosen had a very good name and was very high class. It was a technology side pharmaceutical organization. After paying a certain fee, he waited a few days and successfully got the potions made from the Interstellar Beast's materials without any issue.

In the machinery modification room of the spaceship, a portable freezer was placed on the table. Han Xiao opened its cover, and under the thick, cold fog were two rows and a total of eight tube potions. Six of them were light purple, and two were deep blue. The former was gene potions made by the important organs of Interstellar Beast, and the latter were special potions made by its member... no, its life crystal.

Han Xiao's finger slid past the potions, and two translucent light blue information panels popped up around them. It was the item introduction.

[Interstellar Beast Potion (High Concentration 62%)]: A precious potion, made by extracting an Interstellar Beast's genes, that grants a permanent attribute increase after consuming.

Effective Usages: 0/3

Remark: Before drinking it, be warned that the genes of a Space Creature are not that easy to control. Of course, if being a distorted life form aligns with your aesthetic, please drink as much as you wish.

[Metabolism Adjusting Potion]: A rare potion, made from an Interstellar Beast's life core, that grants an extended life span after consuming with almost no side effects.

Remark: Life is never too long; no fortune or reputation even comes close to how important it is. Make a guess, how many would turn insane for this small potion?

The potion that could extend one's life span did not have a usage limit as it had no effect for the players. Han Xiao held the potion in his hands and contemplated.

Only eight potions were made from an entire Interstellar Beast. What a scary proportion. If I drink the life span potion, will the interface show that my life span is increased? The interface does not have this attribute after all.

Even as he was thinking, his movements did not slow down. He drank a tube of life span potion. It tasted spicy, entering his stomach like a burning blade stabbing down his throat. The pain only lasted for a few seconds before it turned into a gentle warmness that spread throughout his body.

Han Xiao was initially prepared to endure the pain, but to his surprise, it felt good. He closed his eyes in amusement. His mind sunk deep into his body, and his senses went beyond his five senses and felt the changes in his every cell.

Countless lives in the universe had a body, but very few could control it fully. The soul was the owner of the body but also like a slave that had to consume, sleep, excrete to ensure the body survives, unable to turn those functions off. Han Xiao, however, felt different. He felt as if he could control every single part of his body, not only the parts where there were nerves. He discovered that the cells were responding to his thoughts.

It felt like his body had turned into a complicated machine. Before, he could hardly control how this machine operated, but now, he could make the machine operate slower.

"Increase life span by controlling metabolism, just as the name suggests." Han Xiao looked at his hands. He could now control the metabolism speed of his body. He mumbled, "Not only can I now slow down my aging process, I can even speed it up, but speeding it up is irreversible. I wonder how much my life span has increased."

The life span of Supers far exceeded ordinary people. Since he had gotten the ability to control his metabolism, he did not know how long his life span was.

"It feels like I can live for a very long time."

He looked at the interface; there was a notification of him getting a new ability.

You have acquired ability [Self-Healing].

Self-Healing (No Level): When you are injured, you can spend energy to increase your health recovery speed. Maximum recovery speed 120/s.

The interface notification says it's a self-heal ability, but the life span potion gave me much more than what the interface stated. Looks like life span is a hidden effect. Or maybe it's because the interface only calculates the basic attributes.

The ability to self-heal was not bad; it gave him one more guarantee. However, he still had yet to use up Aurora's Character Summon Card, so he probably would not be using this ability any time soon.

There was one more life span potion left, so Han Xiao saved it in case he might need it in the future. He took out the other type of gene potion and injected three of them directly. He was already very familiar with gene potions. After the pain, he looked at the information on his interface. They gave him a total attribute increase of two Intelligence points, six Endurance points, and three Charm points.

Its effect is not as strong as the Void Dragon Pith. After all, the Void Dragons are more than a thousand times stronger than Interstellar Beasts. One is a dragon, while the other is a mayfly.

Han Xiao looked at his [Intermediate Strengthened Life] talent. After using the Void Dragon Pith last time, this talent had leveled up. After consuming the gene potions of another rare creature, this talent should theoretically have been enhanced again.

Despite that, nothing popped up on the interface, so Han Xiao was sure that the talent did not level up.

Looks like one type of gene potion is not enough, or maybe the Interstellar Beast's species level is not up to standard. More gene potions are needed to level it up from intermediate to advanced, but I can't use too many potions.

He walked to the mirror. His looks did not change; the Interstellar Beast potion did not cause a gene mutation. Previously, after he used the Dragon Pith, he had felt that he became even more handsome.

He saved the rest of the potions as well and safely stowed the box away. Han Xiao sat before the table, took out a mission list, and started contemplating.

There are still tens of missions on the list, and these are just suitable missions after basic filtering. I'm not short of Random Reward chances. The earlier I complete my Promotion, the sooner I can make preparations for the main storyline of Version 2.0...

Han Xiao rubbed his chin. This reminded him of how he used to run around everywhere just to get what he wanted. It felt nostalgic.

He thought through the schedule of doing these again and made sure they were correct.

Hope that there is still enough time before the version update ends after I complete my Promotion.

The sound of Herlous and others yelling came from outside the door, and the faint sound of Feidin singing came from another room. He was learning Chen Xing's techniques for training his Psychic power through singing. However, Feidin was not Chen Xing, so his high notes sounded like a pig about to be butchered.

Han Xiao shook his head and put in some earplugs. He pulled out a pile of sheets that he used to punish Sylvia with copying basic machinery theories and quickly started marking them.

Tsk, raising apprentices is just like farming crops; patience is very important.

Chapter 466: Two Months

Anur stood silently outside the thick, silver-alloy gate without saying a word. Behind him was a long, straight corridor with the only light source coming from a mini indicator light every ten meters on both sides of the wall. This gate was the end of the corridor, and looking back from there, there was only a line made by the two red rows of lights extending into the darkness. At the end of it, the two red lines almost connected with each other.

This scene reminded people about words such as 'secret' and 'forbidden land'.

He had been standing here for ten minutes.

Whoosh!

The gate slowly opened and broke the silence.

Light shone from inside, lighting up Anur's strict, wrinkly face.

A person walked out slowly from the room back facing the light. His front was dark, and his looks could not be seen. He stopped before Anur. The light behind the man stretched out his shadow, covering Anur and extending into a black line on the corridor.

"You can only contribute your power to DarkStar after having my approval, and now it's time, Ember."

A faint smile appeared on Anur's serious face. He reached out his palm and said, "Welcome to Calamity."

The person extended his arm and shook Anur's hand. As he looked up, his face became clearer. It was indeed Ember.

It was the day that Ember regained his freedom.

To him, being in solitary confinement was the same as training. There was no need to run around for missions and duties; he just had to do one thing every day—cultivate his potential. After training day after day, he had finally passed the threshold that had stopped countless Supers and entered Grade A. All his senses felt fresh; it was like he had been reborn.

He did not just become stronger; his level of life, world view, and mindset had changed as well. Problems that once felt difficult seemed easy, and enemies that he could not let go no longer mattered.

During his solitary confinement, Black Star, who could counter his Esper power, had always been on his mind. One of the reasons that he had worked this hard to reach Grade A was because he wanted to meet Han Xiao again and wash away his shame.

However, when he really reached the Calamity Grade, this thought suddenly faded. Ember did not bother about Han Xiao anymore. He realized that Anur was right; his level and a Grade B's level were different. It felt as ridiculous as being offended by a mosquito that had bitten him.

Ember did not look at Han Xiao as his opponent on par with him anymore. Even if this person could counter his Esper power to a certain extent, he was still confident that he could turn Han Xiao into dust within ten seconds.

The difference between Grade A and Grade B was a fissure that could not be crossed.

"Teacher, thank you for your guidance."

Ember's tone was respectful. Anur's experience and teachings had helped him conquer many problems, so he admired this mentor very much.

Anur nodded and wiped away his smile. "The situation is not looking good. Although we are in the dark, Godora has not given up hunting us down. As the next step of the plan is carried out, the war will be on an even larger scale. Our high-end combat powers are the main focus of Godora. Some of them left us. High-end combat powers like you and I are in shortage, so you don't have time to rest; there's a mission that needs you."

With an expressionless face, Ember said indifferently, "This is my destiny. Ever since I opened my eyes, I was already prepared to contribute my power to DarkStar."

"Okay, follow me." Anur turned around. "This is your first mission after entering Grade A. I will work together with you in case you can't control your power. We're going to Noriosse to kill a traitor..."

...

In the Garton Star System, a galactic pirate spaceship was traveling in space in stealth mode. A chase was happening on the spaceship.

"Stop running!"

Bang!

A light cannon shot on the ground where Sylvia had just dashed past, turning the floor bright red. A large group of galactic pirates were chasing behind with rage on their faces.

Sylvia sprinted with large steps. She was wearing a simple, black battle suit with machinery only covering her joints and important parts. Her body was glowing with a youthful vibrance. Her hair extended to her shoulders and danced in the wind. A machinery ring hung from her right ear, and a mini tactical analysis screen extended before her right eye.

She was not alone. She was pulling an arm of a young boy and escaping together with him. This boy was a pureblood Godoran about the same age as Sylvia, wearing prison garbs. Although he was half a head taller than Sylvia, he was panting heavily. He was an ordinary person.

"Wh—who are you? Why are you saving me?" the boy asked as he was panting.

Sylvia glanced at him and yelled softly, "I'm a mercenary; someone paid money to save you. Stop talking. Save the stamina and run faster."

The boy was stumbling as he was being dragged. The sound of lasers exploding was chasing tightly behind the two of them. Despite being in such a dangerous situation, this Godoran boy was staring at Sylvia's delicate, lively profile in a daze.

He was a hostage kidnapped by these galactic pirates. He had a wealthy family—his father was the CEO of a Godora financial group and was very rich—so he had been targeted by the galactic pirates who demanded a ransom. Other than him, those galactic pirates had also kidnapped other hostages and imprisoned them together. Ten minutes earlier, this soft-looking girl who had just been captured and taken aboard the ship as a hostage suddenly turned into a warrior, opening the prison and dragging him out.

As expected, the two of them were chased by these galactic pirates.

Ta, ta, ta!

Suddenly, three galactic pirates turned up from the corner in front of them. Just as they were about to fire at them, the captain of the galactic pirates yelled, "They're valuable hostages, don't kill them!"

The three galactic pirates' actions to pull their trigger paused for an instant. Sylvia quickly pulled out a short alloy stick from her tactical belt. Its exterior cracked open, and more parts extended from within, turning into a long, mechanical sword. The two sides of the blade were emitting yellow light—this was an energy weapon. Its body was engraved with enchantment runes to make it lighter.

Sylvia moved very quickly. She lowered her shoulder and bashed onto the galactic pirate's stomach. Her battle suit provided her with enough strength to make the muscular galactic pirate stagger. Before the galactic pirate could react, Sylvia pressed onto his gun, pointed at his friend beside him, and helped him pull the trigger.

Boom!

The light cannon penetrated the head of the person beside him.

This galactic pirate was furious. Just as he was about to kick Sylvia away, he suddenly felt a pain in his knees and lost strength in his legs. He kneeled down on the floor, looked down, and realized that his knees had been slashed open and were covered in blood. Before he could scream, Sylvia held the sword with both her hands and stabbed it into his eyes. The blade penetrated through and came out the back of his head.

Two months had passed. With the Great Mechanic Han's guidance, Sylvia had slowly realized her potential and was already Grade D. Wearing the machinery weapons that Han Xiao had built for her, she could now deal with galactic pirate groups that mostly consisted of ordinary people.

As the third galactic pirate saw this, he could not be bothered with the captain's orders and fired immediately. Sylvia hastily tilted her head before he fired and barely dodged the laser. She quickly pulled up the alloy sword from the dead galactic pirate, turned around, and sliced through the muzzle. She then recalled what Han Xiao had taught her regarding how to quickly shatter the enemies' combat ability, so she raised up her leg and kicked the third galactic pirate between his legs!

Bang!

The face of this galactic pirate turned purple as he kneeled down, grabbing his crotch. His forehead knocked onto the ground, and he curled up into a twitching shrimp.

The Godoran boy shivered and felt his member aching as well.

This battle ended very shortly, but the pursuers caught up somewhat because of it. Sylvia did not have the time to finish the kill; she grabbed the boy's arm again and started sprinting.

"Quickly, go!"

The galactic pirate group had many members. As the chase dragged on, the movement area of Sylvia gradually became smaller. Finally, she was stopped in a corner. Close to a hundred galactic pirates surrounded them and glanced at Sylvia with vicious intentions.

The boy was very afraid and held Sylvia's shoulder tightly. Sylvia, whose face was grave, stood in front of the boy and kept adjusting the direction that her sword was pointing in.

"You have nowhere to run, little girl." The captain of the galactic pirate group walked out of the crowd with a cold smile on his face. "I didn't expect one of our hostages to be a Super and even cause a commotion on my ship. Did you think saving this boy would be so easy? Where do you think you can run to on my ship?"

Sweat rolled down the side of Sylvia's head as she gripped the alloy sword tighter. Most of those galactic pirates were ordinary people, but there were quite a few Supers. The captain standing before her was indeed a Grade C Super, someone whom she did not stand a chance against.

"Tell me, who are you?"

"A mercenary," Sylvia said with a low voice, but she still sounded young and innocent.

When the galactic pirates heard that, they looked at each other and started laughing out loud.

"Hahahaha... This kid is a mercenary‽"

Anger appeared on Sylvia's face. "I just killed three of your members."

They laughed even louder.

The galactic pirate captain laughed ruthlessly, and his face turned ferocious. "Little girl, do you think you can be a mercenary by killing three ordinary people? You have no idea what strength is."

Sylvia bit her lips and acted tough. "I have friends; they won't forgive you."

"What kind of mercenary group would want a kid like you? The boy scouts? Ha, I will kill all of your friends that come," the galactic pirate captain sneered. "And for you... although you're a little too young, you're quite pretty. I guess a mercenary group won't be able to pay a high ransom, so you can use your body to pay for it..."

The eyes of all the galactic pirates sparkled as they laughed loudly. They sized Sylvia's face and body up pitilessly.

"Don't do this..." Sylvia immediately became nervous.

The boy's face changed dramatically. Suddenly, he found the courage from somewhere and stepped before Sylvia. Just as he was about to speak while shivering, the galactic pirates started loudly discussing.

"I want her leg. Its texture is the best!"

"Then I want her butt. I like fats!"

"Ears are crispy. It's best to cut them off and eat them raw."

Sylvia froze. She could not control the panic in her heart and yelled, "Hey, is this what you mean by paying with my body‽"

The galactic pirate heard that and was confused.

"Of course, we meant eating you, what else?"

Sylvia was puzzled, mumbling, "Why do I suddenly not really want to kill all of them?"

Beep beep beep!

This time, a sound came out of Sylvia's wrist. The people looked over, and Sylvia gave a proud smile, the earlier panic having completely disappeared. She had been stalling for time.

She waved her wrist and said in a playful tone, "This is a GPS."

Just as she finished her words...

Boom!

A thunderous noise exploded beside them, and the ship shook violently. The galactic pirates almost all fell onto the ground. They hastily looked in the direction where the loud noise had come from.

A hole had been blasted through the tunnel dozens of meters away, filling it with dust and fog.

A few people appeared in the fog and stepped onto this spaceship.

The foremost person walked out of the fog first. He was wearing a black windbreaker, his hands were behind his back, and his eyes were flickering with a deep light that looked like the starry sky. A natural pressure emanated from his body that sent shivers down the galactic pirates' spines.

This feeling became stronger as the man walked closer. He stared at the galactic pirate captain, and the galactic pirate captain's legs felt soft like he was being stared at by a monster that was about to devour him.

Actually, Han Xiao only looked at him casually. The pressure came from his far superior level.

"I heard you have a problem with my mercenary group?"

Chapter 467: Go Create Miracles, Young Teen

Clank clank clank!

With some simple, straightforward punches, Herlous beat up these galactic pirates easily. He tied them together and made a wailing human mountain.

It was a piece of cake for Herlous to defeat such weak galactic pirates; the main difficulty of rescuing the hostage had been locating the stealthy galactic pirate spaceship. Hence, Han Xiao had gotten Sylvia to disguise as a hostage to get captured while wearing a locator so that they could track this spaceship's location and board it. Han Xiao had borrowed one of the employer's battleships, which had breached the tail of the galactic pirate spaceship.

Also, this was the first time Sylvia took part in a mission. It was a test for her. The lessons that Han Xiao had planned for her filled up her schedule. After she awakened Super-Genes, other than learning knowledge, she had also gone through all sorts of battle technique training. Although Sylvia had only trained for two months, she had a lot of potential and had progressed very quickly. Furthermore, she was very talented in battle. She did not get nervous in battle but became calmer instead, which surprised even Sylvia herself. She did not know that she could stay so calm in the face of danger.

Of course, if Sylvia did not have potential, Han Xiao would not have spent his energy to train her.

"You guys let the hostages out," Han Xiao ordered the others. "I will go to set the course and make this ship head back toward where it came from. We can complete the mission there."

This time, Sylvia trotted toward Han Xiao and asked with an eager expression, "How did I do?"

Han Xiao rubbed his chin and said, "Acceptable, barely a pass. What, do you think there's anything worth complimenting?"

Sylvia curled her lips in disappointment. "Oh."

"Black Star, be more lenient to the youngsters," Herlous said and smiled at Sylvia. "You did quite well. When I was your age, I was not... wait, I was much stronger than you."

Sylvia ground her teeth. "You're really good at comforting people."

"Don't listen to them." Feidin smiled gently. "You progressed very quickly, and we all saw it."

"Shut up!" Sylvia became furious as soon as she heard Feidin speak. She stared at Feidin angrily. Every time she saw this guy, she felt that life was unfair. She had awakened earlier than him, but Feidin's growth speed was like a rocket that soared to Grade C smoothly with ease as he sang and meditated, unlike Sylvia, who lived in the abyss of studies.

Comparison was the thief of joy!

Feidin did not get mad; he gave a gentle smile and did not say any more.

He had followed Han Xiao on his missions for two months. In this period, Chen Xing had tried many times to take back control of his body, but she had been stopped by Feidin time after time. As Feidin's Psychic power rapidly became stronger, Chen Xing's threat gradually became smaller. Feidin's plan was to borrow Chen Xing's memory and make himself stronger; the time when he could completely suppress Chen Xing was probably the time that he would leave.

However, Feidin's personality was very tender; he did not like fighting and almost never got angry. He did not want what happened to him to happen to Chen Xing as he knew how terrible it felt. Therefore, Feidin communicated with Chen Xing many times in his mind, hoping that he could make her give up the meaningless resistance. Unfortunately, Chen Xing was very firm and absolutely unwilling to compromise. Feidin did not give up and still kept up the habit of communicating with Chen Xing every day.

The Godoran boy stared at Han Xiao and the others. When he thought that he had no way out, those mercenaries had come out of nowhere and defeated the galactic pirates. He only came to after a very long time. He looked at Sylvia's back, mustered the courage, and walked to her. "M—my name is Naru. Thank you for saving me. Are you the mercenaries hired by my father?"

The people paused the casual chat and looked at him. Naru panicked from Sylvia's glance. He did not even know where to put his hands.

"I—I want to know your names..."

Naru stuttered.

Han Xiao patted Sylvia's head, chucked, and said, "This kid likes you."

With the truth being exposed, Naru completely panicked. "I don't!"

Han Xiao raised his eyebrows and said, "Oh, looks like he dislikes you."

"N—no, I don't dislike..." Naru could not form a complete sentence.

Sylvia rolled her eyes at Han Xiao and extended her hand. "My name is Sylvia."

Naru hesitated, then cautiously grabbed Sylvia's fingertip. The moment their fingers touched, Naru's face became orange—this was Godoran's face color when they blushed, very scientific and logical.

Herlous sighed and said, "Being young is so great."

Han Xiao took out a cigarette-shaped candy from the snack bag in Aroshia's hands and put it into his mouth. He had been trying to quit smoking, so he could only eat snacks to kill the boredom. He tutted and pondered. "If I complain to the employer that his son flirted with my lovely apprentice, I should be able to blackmail him for some money."

"... You don't have to say it out loud the next time you're thinking of a plan like this." Sylvia turned around angrily.

All the hostages were rescued, and Han Xiao had set the course. Not long after, they returned to the planet where the employer was at. The guards and the families of the hostages were waiting at the dock. The rescued hostages quickly got off the spaceship and reunited with their families.

A police officer approached Han Xiao and expressed his gratitude to Han Xiao for dealing with the kidnappers. As the people involved were mostly people in financial groups, this was an important matter to them.

Han Xiao passed the captured galactic pirates and the spaceship to the police department as agreed; this way, the mission completion rate would be increased. After the officers walked away, Naru and a middle-aged man came to Han Xiao. The middle-aged man had an air of someone in a high place, but he was very friendly when facing Han Xiao. After he expressed his appreciation, he paid the reward.

This middle-aged man was Naru's father, the head of a Godoran financial group, so the promised reward were, of course, not little. At the same time, he was also the one that had issued the mission. After Han Xiao got the 85,000 Enas, the interface notified him that the mission had been completed.

All hostages were rescued, the galactic pirates were captured alive, and the spaceship was handed over. A perfect completion rate, so a Random Reward will certainly be given, Han Xiao thought. He looked at the interface and saw the notification of him getting a new chance to receive a [Random Reward]. He did not use it straight away and saved it in the interface. He had already saved four Random Reward chances.

In those two months, he had done more than ten missions. He had gotten a Random Reward chance from more than eighty percent of those missions. At the start, he had used them up as soon as he got them. He had gotten Attribute Points, experience, Potential Points, and others. Not only did he not get what he wanted, he also got a bunch of trash. Han Xiao had grown quite frustrated, so he had started saving them.

The single draw was not dependable; miracles would only occur in consecutive draws.

Han Xiao did not stay for long after submitting the mission. He took the others back to the ship. The thruster shot out fire, and the spaceship disappeared into the sky.

Naru looked up and stared in the direction that the spaceship had left. He shook his father's arm and said, "Dad, I want to ask something from you."

"What?"

"I... I want to hire this mercenary group as the private guard of our house," Naru said bravely. He could not forget about Sylvia.

"It's impossible."

Naru became nervous. "Then give them more money. Being our guard is at least safer than being mercenaries. As long as the pay is enough, they definitely will agree."

The middle-aged man shook his head with a bitter smile. "It's not about money. Although Black Star is a mercenary, our family is too tiny compared to his background. We have no chance of snatching him from Ames."

Chapter 468: The Four Consecutive Draws of Glory

On the spaceship, everyone was doing their own thing. They had already gotten used to this lifestyle over those two months.

Han Xiao went back to his room alone, opened the interface, and rubbed his hands together.

"Four chances, four consecutive draws, don't disappoint me again."

After failing so many times, he was already very calm about it. As a Mechanic, he believed in making up for quality with quantity.

Beep beep beep!

Just as he was about to start using the Random Reward, his communicator suddenly rang. He received a communication.

"Who is it‽"

The ceremonial feeling was interrupted, so a hint of displeasure leaked into Han Xiao's tone.

"It's me, Nereja. Do you still remember me?"

Looking at the Godoran on the screen, Han Xiao recognized him straight away. "Oh, you're that green... ahem, I'm happy to see you. This seems to be the first time you've contacted me since what happened last time. What is this about? Are you hiring me again?"

"No, I'm here to relay a message." Nereja smiled and said, "Do you know someone called Kerlodd? He was my classmate in the Observer Training Class. He contacted me a few days ago and said that his Observer ID was used by someone else, somewhere else, which happened to be near us. I mentioned you when I chatted with him. When he heard your name, his reaction was a little... er, extreme. He seems to want you to pay him back some money."

Han Xiao understood what had happened. He had entered Kerlodd's ID on the system of the missing spaceship. The radiation storm had blocked the signal at that time, but when he brought the system core back to the space station, the people there had naturally checked the logs and noticed that access attempt.

Kerlodd was the Godora Observer who had been sent to investigate Planet Aquamarine and subsequently captured by Han Xiao.

Han Xiao nodded. "Oh, we are very good friends. How's that guy? Send him my regards."

Nereja's expression was a little strange.

"... Are you sure you are friends? He told me to say, 'Black Star, don't use my ID again! When are you going to pay back the money you blackmailed from me? You're already a renowned mercenary. Are you really this petty about a few hundred Enas?'"

"Hehe, he still loves to joke as always," Han Xiao said. "Our friendship was created through life and death. How can that be measured by money?"

Han Xiao had shown mercy to Kerlodd back then and did not take his life. Was that not a friendship created through life and death?

Speaking of which, he had kept his word and let Kerlodd go back then to have a channel of contacting Godora. He did not expect himself to join Floating Dragon Island afterward. Nonetheless, Kerlodd was still useful.

I told Kerlodd to pay attention to the abnormalities on Planet Aquamarine. I wonder if they sent someone else to investigate. Maybe this will lead to changes in the Version 2.0 storyline... Should be good changes, Han Xiao thought.

"Alright, you tell him that I got the message, and I'm not going to pay him back."

"Okay then..." Nereja gave a bitter smile. He suddenly recalled something and said, "By the way, we had a personnel transfer not long ago. The original station chief was transferred away, and the deputy station chief took over the space station. It's really hard to figure out what the higher-ups are thinking. Anyway, it's a good thing. The deputy station chief is much better than the original station chief. The station chief discovered that I was the one who hired you and gave me a penalty, such an awful guy."

Han Xiao raised his brow and said, "The station chief? I don't have a problem with him—he's a good man. On the contrary, the deputy station chief is a very slippery guy. If he did not have a motive, why did he mention an unsolved internal matter to a mercenary that he had just met?

"Furthermore, the rescued Observers all rooted for you. Who would expose you? Your opinion of the station chief now means that the deputy station chief's act of transferring him was effective. Nonetheless, a good man might not be a useful man. Even though the deputy station chief did not mean well, without him, your wife and those missing Observers would not have been saved. Hence, seeing the results, maybe you won't regret being used."

Actually, the person that gave out the daily missions that rewarded Interstellar Beast Dungeon Crystals was exactly the deputy station chief who later became the station chief. He ordered the players to deal with some internal affairs and quickly improved his performance. If it was the original station chief, he definitely would not have let outsiders interfere with their internal affairs.

"What you said seems to make some sense. After the station chief was transferred away, the deputy station chief looked very happy."

Nereja was dazed for a moment and looked like he had something on his mind. He then sighed and said, "Sigh, speaking of which, the old station chief only followed the regulations. Although he was a little pedantic, he was once a military officer after all, so it's understandable.

"Anyway, I still like the deputy station chief a little more. If everything was done following the rules, the world would not only have that three Universal Civilizations now, and the war would still be going on. The other civilizations would have no choice but to become vassals, or they would be destroyed by the flames of war...

"Sigh, between hypocrisy and war, I would choose the former, and most people would probably do the same. Although I don't know much, I can guess that the Black Forest Age of the exploration history was definitely hell. The peaceful Galaxy Calendar age now was not achieved with ease..."

"Got it, got it. I have something to do, bye." Han Xiao decisively closed the communication. He opened the interface again and exhaled.

Let's begin...

Beep beep beep!

At this time, the communicator rang again.

Interrupted again, Han Xiao was boiling.

Can't I do my consecutive draws peacefully‽ The luck that I gathered is vanishing!

"Who the hell... oh, Ames, hi, are you well? What is it?"

To Han Xiao's surprise, the alluring and sexy Dragon Emperor appeared on the screen. Ames had never contacted him before, so why did she suddenly call him?

"Black Star, I need you." Ames' expression was a little strange.

Han Xiao's mouth twitched. "Pardon me, but what kind of need are you talking about?"

"I found my teacher's whereabouts. He came to the Shattered Star Ring. Black Star, you saw what he looked like personally. Accompany me to look for him." Ames' tone was assertive.

"Okay..." Han Xiao held his forehead. "When?"

"As soon as possible. I will immediately notify you when I return to the Shattered Star Ring."

"Are you not on Floating Dragon Island now?"

"I went to the Federation of Light's mother planet for sightseeing," Ames said.

The Great Mechanic Han was speechless.

"Alright," Han Xiao said, "where's your teacher now?"

"Someone said that he appeared on Noriosse some time ago. Go there to take a look first before I return."

Han Xiao nodded without panicking. Although him seeing the Dragon Emperor's teacher before was a lie, he did indeed know who the Dragon Emperor's teacher was. He was not afraid of not being to recognize that person.

After hanging up the communication, Han Xiao massaged his temple and opened the interface for the third time.

"Let's do this quickly, I have a feeling I'm not in luck again... no one will find me again I hope."

After being interrupted twice, Han Xiao's excitement was gone. He stared at the interface with an expressionless face.

_____________________

Randomizing...

Randomization Complete.

Your Random Reward Type is: [Ability]

_____________________

Han Xiao glanced through and chose the most useful option between the three options. A Cannon Master ability, [Locked Shot]. Its effect was that the next shot would definitely hit with an addition 10 – 18% of critical damage.

Han Xiao's face was calm. He did not stop and immediately started to draw the second Random Reward.

_____________________

Randomizing...

Randomization Complete.

Your Random Reward Type is: [Item]

_____________________

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled. "It's here, a chance!"

_____________________

Please select one from the three reward below:

Gene Awakening Elixir (Luxurious Version): If the user has no Main Class, using this has a chance to turn the user into an Esper.

Double Experience Card: Doubles the experience gained through killing monsters and doing missions. Lasts for 6 days.

Ability Enhancement Card: 70% chance to enhance an ability when used, amplifying its basic effects. 20% chance to mutate the ability into a similar but stronger new ability.

_____________________

"Two cards but no Mission Completion Card." Han Xiao felt his chest was hurting.

Comparatively, the Ability Enhancement Card was somewhat useful to him, but Han Xiao was still frustrated over not getting what he wanted.

Without a doubt, the Gene Awakening Elixir was trash, and he did not need the Double Experience Card, so he chose the Ability Enhancement Card straight away.

"I feel lucky! Third time's the charm!"

Han Xiao felt hopeful as he activated another Random Reward.

_____________________

Randomizing...

Randomization Complete.

Your Random Reward Type is: [Experience]

_____________________

"..."

"Great, very great. I'm in dire need of experience. What good timing..." Han Xiao clapped. Then he smashed his head on the table, clenched his teeth, and yelled, "As if!"

He had always thought that, of all the reward types, experience was the most useless one.

He picked the highest option of 2,000,000 experience and activated the last Random Reward despairingly.

_____________________

Randomizing...

Randomization Complete.

Your Random Reward Type is: [Item]

_____________________

Medium Experience Crystal (x8): Grants 100,000 – 1,000,000 experience after using.

Blazing Battle Aura (Cosmetic): When equipped, grants special light effects when moving. Being strong is a matter of version; being cool is for life.

Mission Completion Card (x2): Marks one mission as complete and receive rewards equivalent to the lowest grade.

_____________________

Han Xiao exhaled deeply and closed his eyes with satisfaction and fulfillment.

"Finally... I finally got it..."

Bang!

The next second, he jumped up and slammed his palm on the metal table, leaving an imprint.

"Consecutive draw is the best in the world!"

Chapter 469: [Gene Liberation] and High-End Knowledge!

After being overjoyed for a while, Han Xiao quickly calmed down. Having been unlucky more than ten times, he was relieved upon finally getting the item that he needed. The Mission Completion Card was not a rare item, yet he had only gotten it after so many times. Nonetheless, he had gotten it in the end.

Now that he had the Mission Completion Card, he did not have to take the risk and fight a Grade A Super—the steady mindset was dependable.

For normal players, their level represented their grade. LV 1 – LV 20 was Grade F; LV 21 – LV 40 was Grade E; LV 41 – LV 60 was Grade D; LV 61 – LV 90 was Grade C; LV 91 – LV 100 was Grade C+; over LV 100 was Grade B and above. Of course, this was just a rough range. Due to the difference in abilities, attributes, talents, and equipment, there would be slight differences. For example, the pro players would usually reach Grade C at LV 60.

The normal players would only enter Grade B after going through the second Race Evolution at level 100. For Han Xiao, who was also level 100, as he had many Molding Talents, he was much stronger than the players, so he was Grade B. Including the advantages of the Mechanic class and how high his attributes were, he was not considered weak even among Grade Bs. His actual combat ability far exceeded the standard of his level. Still, level 100 was the entrance of Grade B—the next grade was tens of levels away.

Hence, Han Xiao had been unwilling to take the risk. Even if he reached level 120 after his promotion, he would still be at Grade B. From this, the difference between Grade B and Grade A was clearly shown. If Han Xiao had to fight against an enemy just a few levels higher than him, he would not have been worried at all, but against an enemy tens of levels higher? Unless he would have special measures, and there was a ninety percent chance that he would die.

Just looking at this percentage made him lose interest in taking the risk.

The method of using a Mission Completion Card was really a tremendous help to him that made him avoid unnecessary dangers. Han Xiao had faced many threats before, so he was not afraid of taking risks. However, since he had more choices, it was better to use the safer method than taking the risk and fighting such a strong enemy.

Even if he really had to fight a Grade A Super, who knew how much time he would have to spend in plotting and how many resources he would waste? By looking for the card while doing missions, not only did he not have to suffer a loss, but he was even making a profit. Why would he not do it?

Han Xiao was worried that his hand might slip. He fully focused and selected the Mission Completion Card carefully.

Before this, it was nowhere to be found, now two of it appeared together. I only need one, so I shall save the other. I might use it in the future when I meet a similarly difficult mission.

Han Xiao did not use the Mission Completion Card immediately. His Class Advancement mission was still stuck, so he planned to buy two High-End Mechanic Knowledges that he had been eyeing up since long ago. Then he would complete the Promotion and Class Advancement together so that he could rush his levels immediately after. He had 1,360,000 Enas in his account, so he was quite wealthy. It was more than enough to buy two High-End Knowledges.

I got an Ability Enhancement Card as well. I shall use that first.

The Ability Enhancement Card will increase the basic stats of an ability, so even a max level ability can be enhanced. If I can get the ability mutation, that would be awesome, but I doubt there's a chance... What should I enhance? A Combat ability or Machinery Affinity type ability?

Han Xiao opened his ability list, and a dense number of ability names expanded out. Han Xiao directly skipped the blueprints and looked at the other abilities. The Mechanic abilities were very important; his raw strength would basically be increased if he enhanced one of them. There would be more Machinery Affinity abilities after he leveled up, so this tiny enhancement had limited effect for him.

It seemed like enhancing an ability with a special use would be better.

With a flash of insight, Han Xiao had a target.

How about I enhance [Flaming Will]? I'm short of damage abilities, so strengthening my explosive power is quite useful for me. If the cooldown is decreased, this enhancement will be worth it.

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled. Flaming Will had both active and passive effects. The former had a ten-minute cooldown while the latter had a thirty-minute cooldown. Although its damage boost was very high, it had a high cooldown as well, causing him to only trigger this ability once or twice during every battle. If the cooldown was increased, his damage would be hugely increased.

He had gotten this ability from Bennett, and it still made a noticeable difference at his current level. He used the Ability Enhancement Card on the spot.

Ability Enhancement Card activated. Target: [Flaming Will LV10].

Enhancing...

You have triggered Ability Mutation.

You acquired new ability [Gene Liberation LV1].

Han Xiao was surprised. Damn, I'm really in luck today!

In the interface, [Flaming Will] was replaced by the new ability, and the new method of using the ability appeared in his mind. Han Xiao looked at the ability introduction.

[Gene Liberation Lv.1]:

Active Effect: By spending 1,000 health points, grants an attack boost for the next 1.5 seconds. 50% chance to deal 200% – 220% damage; 30% chance to deal 300% – 330% damage; 20% chance to deal 400% – 440% damage.

Cooldown: 8 min 30 s

Passive Effect: When health is below 20%, the ability will be activated automatically without cost.

Passive Effect Cooldown: 17 mins

Remarks: You obtained the way to break through your limits. Through squeezing energy out of your cells, you can gain explosive power that exceeds your limit, but it will hurt your body.

Han Xiao read through and felt that this enhancement was truly worth it. Not only was the cooldown reduced, the random stats were better as well.

Initially, [Flaming Will] had four random ranges, and the highest one granted more than five times damage, but the chance of triggering that was too low. [Gene Liberation], however, slightly reduced the maximum boost, but the random ranges changed from four to three. Lower random factors meant more stable damage output.

Most importantly, this boost was not applied to only one attack but all attacks in a certain period. With his speed, it would definitely be more than one attack!

He was an Artillery Style Mechanic; hence, his attack frequency was extremely high. This meant that the effect of this ability was explosive!

Furthermore, this was just its effect on Lv.1. Without hesitation, Han Xiao threw in tens of millions of experience and leveled it up to Lv.10 straight away. Its duration increased to two seconds, and its cooldown reduced to seven minutes. The damage boost of all three ranges was increased by one-tenth, meaning that the lowest boost was 220%, and the maximum was 480%. The cost had also reduced to 800 health points. Han Xiao had close to 20,000 health, so this cost was nothing to him, not to mention the [Self-Healing] ability that he had gotten two months prior, which would recover this amount of health in a mere eight seconds.

"This ability is a little too strong, isn't it!" Han Xiao clicked his tongue.

After packing up his things, Han Xiao pushed open the door, feeling refreshed. In the spaceship hall, Herlous was playing cards with the Volga brothers again. He had a proud expression, while the Volga brothers were despondent.

"I don't want to play anymore. How can you always get the cards you want?" the Volga brothers complained.

Herlous shrugged and chuckled. "Because I'm strong. Don't just stand there. Admit defeat and pay the money."

The three brothers sadly made the transfer. This time, no matter how Herlous tried to ask them, they did not go back to playing. They had already lost four rounds in a row. The three of them played cards with Herlous frequently and had always lost more than they won. It was like God was on Herlous' side; he could always draw the most suitable card. The game experience of the three brothers was always ruined.

Seeing that the three of them were firm in their decision, Herlous knew that there was nothing that he could do. He turned around, looked at Han Xiao, and said, "Black Star, come to play cards."

"Do I look free?"

This time, Feidin walked out from his room and was heading toward the Simulated Combat Room. Herlous' eyes suddenly sparkled, and he hurried yelled, "Feidin, come to play a round."

Feidin paused, turned around, and shrugged. "I don't know how to play it."

"Don't worry, it's very easy, I will teach you. If you can't even play cards, how are you different from the primates?" Herlous stood up and dragged Feidin to sit opposite him.

"Alright, how is this card game played?" Feidin shook his head, picked up a deck of cards, and looked at them.

"The official name of this card is called 'Galaxy War'. We usually call it the Wayne Card. This is Federation of Light's common language, meaning 'Sparkling Card'. See, it even has our mercenary group, isn't it interesting? Let me tell the rules..."

Herlous excitedly taught Feidin the rules.

"Okay, those were the rules. You're a Psychic, so I don't have to repeat it. Let's play a round. You will know how to play it after trying. Use the Volga brothers' cards—they're also using the Shattered Star Ring card set."

Herlous knocked on the table, and the cards shuffled automatically. These cards had simple industrial enchantments on them, so many special effects could be completed automatically. Herlous raised his hand and let Feidin start first. He smiled and said, "Let's not play those official modes this time—we will play the Free Battle Mode. The way to win is to empty the opponent's health bar. This is your first time playing, so I'll let you start."

Feidin nodded. "Okay then, you have to hold back on me."

Three minutes later, Herlous stared at the table with widened eyes and a gaping mouth.

"Did I win?" Feidin blinked. "It seems quite easy."

"Hehe..." Herlous wiped his sweat. "You're just lucky this round. One more round..."

Not long after, Herlous slumped on the sofa with despair on his face.

"Did you lie to me and actually know how to play?"

Feidin smiled bitterly and said, "This is really my first time playing. You're too unlucky."

In such a short period of time, Herlous had already lost five rounds in a row. He had almost started to question the meaning of life. For some reason, his luck had suddenly vanished, and he could never get the card that he wanted. Meanwhile, Feidin won just by using whatever card he drew.

The Volga brothers had been spectating all along, and they could not stop laughing out loud. "That's the feeling!"

Han Xiao shook his head. This was why he did not like playing cards with these people.

As long as lucked played any part in the mode that they played, Feidin basically got godly hands every single time. Herlous' luck could crush the Volga brothers, but he could only get demolished when facing Feidin's High Class Luck Glow.

Han Xiao interrupted them and said, "Stop playing, we have a new mission. Ames told us to help her find someone on Noriosse, so we won't be accepting requests temporarily.

"She's not in Shattered Star Ring now. I need to buy some things from other Star Systems before she returns. I have already set the course."

The rest nodded.

Of course, Han Xiao was going to buy Advanced Knowledges. The Dragon Emperor had yet to arrive, so he planned to put down everything else for the time being and go through his Promotion first. This was a long-awaited chance to increase his strength to a new level.

The stronger he was, the more freedom he would have. In order to complete his plan, being strong was a necessity. Even his plan was to make himself stronger.

Han Xiao traveled across a few Star Systems and successfully bought the two High-End Knowledges. As he did not take the path of farming Faction Favorability and buying High-End Knowledges privately was very expensive, his savings plummeted to 500,000 Enas. The two High-End Knowledges cost him more than 800,000 Enas.

The price that he paid was worth it. He could earn back the money, but the increased strength was permanent.

The two High-End Knowledges were [High Energy Control] of the Energy Branch and [Advanced Artificial Intelligence Technology] of the Control Branch.

[High Class Energy Control] was very important; it allowed control of the higher-level energies and was considered to be one of the core knowledges. It could combine more stable shields and energy weapons. Energy weapons were common weapons that were stronger than electromagnetic weapons.

As only some knowledges were sold, Han Xiao could only choose the comparatively more useful knowledges. Hence, [Advanced Artificial Intelligence Technology] was his second choice, it was used to build artificial intelligence.

The High-End Knowledges of the Mechanic class had very visible uses. Every one of them could make powerful impacts, and none of them were useless. Normal players had to choose carefully as the High-End Knowledges cost three Potential Points to learn and level up.

There was a total of three branches and fifteen High-End Knowledges, so leveling all of them up to level five would cost 225 Potential Points. In order to max the level of all the Advanced Knowledges and Basic Knowledges, it would cost a total of 450 Potential Points!

There were still higher-class knowledges above the High-End Knowledges. The Mechanic class was a bottomless abyss of Potential Points, so it was basically impossible for players to get so many Potential Points. Hence, Han Xiao had been saving his Potential Points from the beginning.

After finishing all his preparations, he was back in the Garton Star System. Han Xiao piloted the spaceship back to Juberly Hub.

He planned to complete his level 100 Promotion there.

Chapter 470: Experience Fully Digested!

After returning to the mercenary group stronghold in Juberly Hub, Han Xiao entered the Simulated Combat Room alone and closed the alloy door behind him. He took out the Mission Completion Card and used it on his Promotion mission.

You have used [Mission Completion Card].

[Trial of the Strong] Current Progress: 1/1

Level 100 Promotion Mission completed!

END bonus increased! 1 END = 50 Health = 60 Stamina.

It's done.

The dust settled, and Han Xiao heaved a sigh of relief. The Level 60 Promotion was the first Race Evolution, and the level 100 Promotion was the second.

I did get the [Void Genes] talent from the Void Dragon Pith, so that will add an option during the Race Evolution and provide a new evolution path.

The options in Race Evolution were randomly chosen from the evolution tree that had higher compatibility. There would also be an option with very low compatibility that gave the players the choice of taking a completely different path.

This time, an evolution notification popped up on the information panel hovering before his eyes.

You have taken another step forward on the path of evolution. You have received refinement of your level of life.

Race Detected: Type I Galaxy Human Race

Randomly selecting 6 suitable evolution paths...

Selection complete.

Please select 1 from the 6 options below as your evolved race.

Warning! The evolution process is irreversible. Please select cautiously! [Appendix - Evolution Path Characteristics Introduction]

[Type II Galaxy Human Race] - 94% Compatibility

[Type III Galaxy Human Race] - 92% Compatibility

[North Wind God Race] - 75% Compatibility

[Void Prowler (Human Form)] - 81% Compatibility

[Half-Dragon Hybrid] 64% Compatibility

[Medium Mechanical Life] 22% Compatibility

Other than the usual type II and type III, the rest are all decent, but none of them are comparable to this... Han Xiao narrowed his eyes. He had already decided.

Selection Complete

Evolving race... Evolution complete.

Your race changed to: [Void Prowler (Human Form)].

Cell structure refined, organs strengthened, metabolism adjusted, adaptability enhanced...

Your potential increased!

You have received attribute bonuses: +28 STR, +45 DEX, +15 END, +24 INT, +36 MYS, +22 CHA, +570 energy. Energy level attribute bonuses changed!

Your Race Specialty [Adaptive Species] has been changed.

You have received Race Specialty [Void Travel].

You have received Race Specialty [Void Mirror Image].

You have received Race Specialty [Void Shadow].

Skinning pain came like a tsunami. Han Xiao had mentally prepared. Every Race Evolution brought a huge change for one's genes and cells. The players could ignore the pain, but he could not. He clenched his teeth tightly, and masses of veins bulged on his face and wiggled like snakes. His eyes were filled with red; all the blood vessels in his eyes had exploded. The diamond-shaped piece of skin between his eyebrows that came from the Void Genes was emitting a gray light as gray lines extended out from it, spreading all over Han Xiao's face and very soon his entire body. It was changing all of his cells.

Buzz!

The tremendous energy in his body could not be controlled anymore. Electric sparkles turned into dozens of lightning whips and danced madly. The air was filled with a burnt smell, and the floor was burnt black.

Han Xiao suddenly opened his mouth and spat out red blood, which was emitting bubbles as if it was boiling. It turned into a violet color at a visible rate.

The pain this time lasted longer than any times before. Void Prowler could almost be considered as a completely different life form, so the change was drastic. This was indeed the special evolution path given by the Void Genes. Whether in turns of Race Specialty or future potential, this was the best choice among the six options.

Type II and Type III Galaxy Human Race were the usual evolution path with different focuses, but they were rather mediocre. Their benefit was that their compatibility was very high, which meant that more paths could be taken. Han Xiao had chosen this path at level 60 because he wanted to discover an evolution path that was strong enough, and now, he had found it. The Void Race was like the Demon Race and the Energy Life; it was a race on its own—rare, strong, and had a lot of potential.

For the other options, the [North Wind God Race] was a special human race that had natural strong bodies and tough vitality, their reproductive capability was over the top. They called themselves the God Race. The [Half-Dragon Hybrid] was also a representation of a strong body. Both of these were suitable for Pugilists. [Medium Mechanical Life] was a completely different race. It was a mechanical life that did not have energy. Plus, its compatibility was too low, so Han Xiao was definitely not going to choose that.

The pain only gradually faded after a long time. Han Xiao looked like he had been fished out from the sea of blood. During the last period, it was not sweat that came out of his pores anymore but human blood. All of his blood had been replaced. His senses felt different as well. Other than the five human senses, he had many more senses. He could feel the flow of stray energy, and he could see in Void Vision; it was like he had opened the gate to a new world.

Han Xiao took out a mirror and looked at himself. He had grown ten inches taller. Luckily, his body was still in human shape, and he did not have an extra tail or arm or anything of the sort. However, inside his body, his bones, muscles, and organ structures had completely changed; it was many times more complicated than a human structure.

He did not look much different from before, still handsome as always. The diamond-shaped skin between his eyebrows became an indigo crystal. This was a controllable new organ used to sense the Void Vision. His skin was whiter than before, and he gave off a mysterious vibe.

"Not bad, I still look human. This is the human form Void Prowler after all. Anyone that turns into a Void Prowler is able to maintain their original appearance, so most creatures can mutate into Void Prowlers."

Han Xiao was very knowledgeable. All three Race Specialties were Void Prowler's natural talents. Among which, [Void Travel] was the core ability.

"Let me try to see how it feels."

The world before his eyes changed. Everything became foggy like he was observing reality through a layer of translucent material. This was the Void Vision; he entered a mirror dimension that reflected reality where time passed at a different speed. When Han Xiao moved, the real world was basically still, but he could not influence reality in any way and would only go through physical objects. The two dimensions were like mirrors that were placed tightly against each other; they could not interfere with each other. It was like a stealth mode that allowed free movement.

[Void Travel] had no duration limit but continuously cost a large amount of stamina during its duration. Its cooldown was five minutes.

Han Xiao walked from one corner of the room to another, counted a few seconds in his head then deactivated this ability and returned to reality. He looked at his watch; almost no time had passed.

"So, this ability is similar to teleportation or a short-range jump as seen from the reality." Han Xiao nodded in his head. According to his senses, this talent was like a weakened version of Esper powers that could slow time—the difference was that he could not influence reality.

He looked at the mirror again and noticed his body's changes. When he used the Void Prowler's Race Specialties, he would deviate from his usual human form and enter Void Form, as only then would he be able to enter the Void Dimension. His skin became crystal clear and gray. Under his skin were dim streaks of light like starlight. His white skin retracted into markings and was spread out on his body following his bone structure. The white markings met at the crystal between his eyebrows.

Han Xiao waited for a while, and his body automatically turned back. The white markings expanded and covered his skin as he returned to his human form. The gray skin tone during his Void Form was absorbed by the crystal like a river.

"Such a magical life form."

Han Xiao continuously switched between the two forms and familiarized himself with them.

As for the other two Race Specialties, as the name suggested, Void Mirror Image could generate a mirror image without any combat ability used to confuse the enemy, and Void Shadow was an ability to summon a Void Shadow that would exist for thirty minutes. The shadow had the characteristics of a shadow—it would not be wounded, could not attack, and moved extremely fast. It could be used to scout or disrupt the enemy's vision. These two Race Specialties also cost a large amount of stamina.

Most races only had one or two specialties—three was exceptional. The Void Prowler's Race Specialties were mainly focused on disrupting, confusing, and dodging. [Void Travel] was the most important one; it was a very strong dodging ability and only had a cooldown of five minutes.

On the interface, the Class Advancement requirements of his Main Class had already been met. A notification popped up.

You have received a new class [War Mechanic LV 1].

+120 Energy, +3 DEX, +3 END, +5 INT.

You have received 6 Free Attribute Points.

You have received 1 Potential Point.

You have acquired ability [Application Level Machinery Affinity].

You have acquired ability [Waste Modification].

You have acquired ability [Mechanical Force Overload].

You have received ability [Mechanical Force Combat Technique (Locked)].

You have acquired talent [Battlefield Wisdom].

War Mechanic was the sixth stage class of the Mechanic class. It was the time where the Mechanic class showcased its power. The maximum level of this class was twenty. As the name suggested, the Mechanic class finally started focusing on combat abilities at this stage. Other than the new Machinery Affinity, all the other abilities were combat abilities.

He spent his experience in the main class and leveled it up.

[War Mechanic] leveled up to LV 16.

+120 Energy, +3 DEX, +2 END, +5 INT

You have received 6 Free Attribute Points.

You have received 1 Potential Point.

Above level 100, every level required more experience to level up. Han Xiao had about 1.6 billion experience at this time; he spent 1.3 billion experience and leveled it up to level 16. He was still four levels from the maximum LV 20, but he had already run out of experience.

The experience that he had harvested from the players in Version 1.0 was about to be used up!

I have close to 300 million experience left. I can level it up one more time, but it's not as beneficial as to use it to upgrade abilities. Also, the two High-End Knowledges need to be combined into new blueprints. It's better to keep it... Haha, I'm finally going to finish this huge sum of experience.

Han Xiao smiled in satisfaction. It had been a very long time since he had last felt in need of experience. Not only did he not feel unhappy, he was joyful, and a sense of nostalgia swept over him. He had calculated it long ago and knew that he would definitely be able to spend all the experience after his level 100 Promotion.

This was great news. Any amount of experience in the interface was just a number, similar to not spending the money earned. Only by turning it into his combat abilities would he fully utilize it. When he played the game in his previous life, the best feeling had been when he spent all his experience.

Now that he had finally digested what he made in Version 1.0, he felt a strong sense of fulfillment.

The players would not be around during the version update, so there was no way to quickly gain experience. The time that the next version began would be the time that he started harvesting experience again.

After spending this experience, I'm now level 116. Good. When the players appear again, it will be a chance for me to become much stronger again.

Han Xiao squinted. He looked forward to Version 2.0 arriving in a year's time.

Chapter 471: Shattered Light (1)

After becoming a War Mechanic, Han Xiao had five new abilities on his interface. Even without looking at them, he was familiar with the effects of these abilities.

[Application Level Machinery Affinity] had more Machinery Affinity bonus than [Advanced Machinery Affinity]. It was the core of the Mechanic class, so he definitely had to level it up. Since he only had 300 million experience left, he only leveled it up to LV5. Every level gave five percent Machinery Affinity, so his Machinery Affinity increased by another twenty-five percent.

[Waste Modification]'s prerequisite was one of the three abilities from the compression technology, [Basic Machinery Construction]. Their effects were somewhat similar. [Waste Modification]'s effect was if a machine was destroyed and became a pile of scrap parts, this ability could recover these parts and turn them into the original machinery. Of course, the machinery would have a twenty-five percent decrease in attributes and be one or two grades lower. Also, this ability could be used multiple times on the same target until the target's grade reached Gray or had a seventy-five percent decrease in attributes. This meant that this ability could be used a maximum of three times on the same target.

As the name suggested, this ability was a highly efficient waste recycling ability. Its effect was much stronger in actual battle than stated in the introduction. Furthermore, it was one of the reasons that the War Mechanic class had a 'War' prefix. It gave Mechanics many more tactical choices. In Han Xiao's previous life, only when the players reached their fifth and sixth main class level in Version 3.0 did the Mechanics first showcase their strength. The War Mechanic class was very complex and hard to master; its combos were difficult to use, and it required a very strong tactical mindset. The War Mechanic class was the most difficult class to operate among the five classes.

[Mechanical Force Overload] was a normal boosting ability, similar to [Surging Mechanical Force] and [Overload] but with higher numbers. The difference between them was that [Surging Mechanical Force] had no side effect, [Overload] decreased the machinery's durability, and [Mechanical Force Overload] would cause the machinery to enter a cooldown where they could not be used. It was not a very impactful ability. However, when it was used together with [Overload] on the same machine, the enhancement would increase by another forty percent, and the durability would decrease by thirty-three percent immediately. Han Xiao had used this ability a lot in the past, but he had only used it on the machinery that he was willing to sacrifice.

The most special ability was [Mechanical Force Combat Technique], which was still 'Locked' till the High-End Knowledge [Advanced Electromagnetic Forcefield] was learned. What was special about this ability was that it was not an ability that enhanced the machinery but the Mechanic themself.

The Mechanical Force was transformed from Electromagnetic Energy, so it was also electromagnetic. This ability allowed the Mechanics to still be able to fight even without machinery, just like how every Mage had a certain amount of melee battle capability.

The talent [Battlefield Wisdom] was a fixed talent of the Mechanic class. After entering battle, this talent would provide an additional one percent Intelligence every minute until it reached a maximum of fifteen percent. Together with the talent unlocked in the previous main class stage [Machinery Analytical Comprehension] that provided one percent Machinery Affinity for every ten Intelligence, it allowed Mechanics to become stronger as their level increased.

During battles between players, a Mechanic's machinery continuously weaken over the course of a battle, and this talent filled the shortcomings of the Mechanics' capability in long battles. When the Mechanic class was fully shaped, it would become very comprehensive in all kinds of battles. One of the basic tactics used by Mechanics was to stall for fifteen minutes with mechanic traps till they gained the maximum bonus, then released all the machinery to deal explosive damage... also known as the Bladder Tactic.

Han Xiao only increased the Machinery Affinity abilities by a few levels and did not touch anything else, spending about 40 million experience. He was left with about 250 million experience, which he planned to save and spend slowly. He then spent the ninety-six Free Attribute Points on his interface all in Intelligence as usual.

Although he hesitated for a split second when he saw the number '1' on his Luck attribute, he did not spend any of it on Luck. Even though his Luck attribute was hard to look at, putting any points in Luck would not be of much use to him. Luck was related to item drop rate and some abilities, but he did not depend on luck for anything, nor did he have any abilities that were related to Luck. Furthermore, just a few points in Luck would be useless. If he wanted to take that path, he would have to at least put in dozens of points. Even then, it would still not make much of a difference. Hence, he continued to put all his Free Attribute Points into Intelligence.

After he finished allocating his Free Attribute Points, his attributes after Promotion were laid out clearly.

Level: 116

Main Class: Mechanic

Race: Void Prowler (Human Form)

Attributes: 163 STR, 349 DEX, 306 END, 872 INT, 102 MYS, 41 CHA, 1 LUK

Free Attribute Points: 0

Potential Points: 55

Health: 27,038

Stamina: 25,880

Energy: 7,700 [LVL 9]

Energy LVL 9 Bonus: +53 STR, +72 DEX, +80 END, +90 INT, +55 MYS, +7,520 Maximum Health, +60% Machinery Affinity

Power Level: 7,637 Ona

Grade: B

[You're a skilled Galaxy warrior. Even those with the same Grade as you won't mess with you easily.]

7,700 Energy Rank, yet to achieve B+. However, my actual combat capability is on par with Grade B+. The standard of Grade A is 10,000 Ona. At this pace, I should reach the Calamity Grade twenty to thirty levels earlier than the players at around level 140.

Han Xiao nodded with a smile.

I'm now level 116, and I still have one Mission Completion Card, so the only thing that I am short of is Experience. In order to rapidly gain Experience and quickly level up, harvesting the players is the best way. Therefore, as long as my plan is successfully carried out in the Mutation Disaster incident and I guide the Planet Aquamarine players to my faction, I will be able to reach Grade A in the next version!

After letting the cleaning robot clear the blood stains on the floor, Han Xiao walked out of the Simulated Combat Room. As soon as he returned to the hall, the people there turned and looked at him with surprise.

"Am I hallucinating, or did you... change?" Herlous asked suspiciously.

Sylvia walked around Han Xiao a few times, patted her chest, and sighed with relief. "I almost thought I mistook someone else for you."

"Is it that obvious?" Han Xiao's mouth twitched. His looks did indeed change after the Race Evolution, but he did not think it was a noticeable change at all.

"Your looks did not change much; its mainly the vibe that you're giving off. You seem to be more mysterious. Also, I don't remember you having this crystal on your forehead..." Herlous felt a shiver down his spine. "Strange, I'm feeling a certain pressure from you, but we should have about the same strength. What did you do when you locked yourself in that room?"

Of course, they did not know that Han Xiao could quickly complete his Race Evolution through the interface while it would take a very long time for others to fully complete the Race Evolution. The difference in the time that it took was incomparable.

"I'm stronger than before." Han Xiao smiled and waved his hand. "I won't explain the details. Anyway, I'm still me."

"Do you also have some special training tactic like Feidin?" Herlous asked.

Feidin, who was meditating, opened his eyes and asked, "Who's calling me?"

"Shut up!"

"Oh."

Herlous always had a problem with Feidin. He snorted, looked at Han Xiao, and asked, "Are we going to Noriosse next?"

Han Xiao nodded. "Yes. I've completed what I wanted to do. Ames asked me to go to Noriosse and find her teacher."

He was much stronger, but it would still take a very long time for him to reach Ames' level. Before then, Han Xiao did not mind having someone to rely on. After all, Galaxy was so enormous; there were too many strong individuals and organizations. Furthermore, Ames had saved him once, so it was only right that he helped her do small things like this as much as he could. Having a good relationship with a Beyond Grade A was definitely beneficial, not to mention that he was under the Dragon Emperor's command.

This time, Herlous intercepted Han Xiao and said, "Before going to Noriosse, I want to return to Planet Sunil and retrieve my armor, [Shattered Light]. Planet Sunil is nearby anyway, so it won't take long."

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

He had been interested in the Commander Class armor for a very long time. Back then, he did not have the ability to work on it, but now, he satisfied the requirements.

"No problem, we will go together."

The spaceship slowly landed on the plains outside the Forest City. This had once been the battlefield to fight against the Catastrophe, a place where blood spilled formed rivers. Now, it had been cleaned up and was an empty, burnt ground.

The six layers of defenses outside Forest City were already built. Pairs of armored guards patrolled the area, and vehicles drove into the forest to hunt from time to time.

As soon as they landed, many guards surrounded them and lined up to welcome them. Herlous had contacted the Sunil government before they arrived. When they disembarked the spaceship, those guards loudly yelled a phrase in the Sunil language, expressing their admiration to Herlous.

"Let's go, I have already contacted the officials, so we will be heading to the research lab to retrieve my armor." Herlous smiled.

They followed the soldiers and entered Forest City. Compared to a year earlier, there were not many changes other than the fact that there were even fewer people on the streets. It was probably because more youngster had joined the military forces.

"Are you Herlous? Oh my god, my hero!"

This time, the pedestrians around them noticed Herlous. They surrounded him excitedly, and even Han Xiao and the others were pushed aside.

Herlous hastily put up a friendly smile and chatted with them for a while. As more and more people joined in, he could not handle their passion anymore, so he hurriedly squeezed out of the crowd. The few of them took a few turns and finally escaped from the crowd.

"You're very popular, I see." Han Xiao laughed.

Herlous was embarrassed. "The officials need a role model to boost the residents' confidence, so they replayed my stories every day on television and radio to praise me. Everyone in this city knows me."

"National hero, so cool." Sylvia's eyes were shining.

"Cool my ass, a hero's ending is always sacrifice," Herlous protested. He still remembered Han Xiao's 'foresight'.

When they sneaked up to the doors of the government in the middle of the city, there were no more residents around. Herlous approached and reported his arrival. Very soon, a few military officers walked out and greeted him. These were matters of the Sunils; Han Xiao had no interest in listening, so he paid no attention along the way.

After talking for a while, Herlous beckoned the others, and they walked into the restricted military site, following the officers. After passing by metal gates one after another, they came to a sealed research lab. It was very spacious and even had a garage that stored machinery in the process of being modified.

They came to an experiment room. Herlous' Commander Class armor was placed on the experiment table. Ten or so researchers were surrounding it and testing its parameters.

The officer walked up to the researchers and said, "This is General Herlous; he's here to collect his armor. These are the permits."

Han Xiao's eyebrows shot up. He poked Herlous' back and softly asked, "When did you become a general?"

Herlous grinned and replied softly as well. "It's just on paper."

The Head of Research was experimenting excitedly when he heard the officer. He glanced over Han Xiao and the others with an impatient expression, walked up to the gate, and said, "I thought we agreed on giving it to me for research. Why are you suddenly taking it away?"

"I heard you have already achieved some results, so I want to take my armor back," Herlous said. "It's very useful to me."

Unwillingness was clearly written on the Head of Research's face. "How can we return it to you? This armor is related to Sunil's top technology; it's a national treasure and doesn't belong to you alone."

"Er... but I was the one that gave it to the nation. I don't see what's wrong with me wanting it back."

"Aren't you a national hero? Are you not even willing to make such a small contribution?" The Head of Research frowned.

Herlous sighed. He gave a look to the officer beside him, and the officer took out the documents that proved that Herlous' request was authorized by the superiors. The researchers saw it and had no choice but to obey the order. They took the armor, placed it into a metal box, and handed it to Herlous.

"I got it, let's go." Herlous touched the box and smiled.

The Head of Research was trembling with rage. "If the armor is with us, we will definitely be able to achieve greater results and provide more help for the race. You're too selfish!"

Herlous' face changed slightly, but he did not say anything. However, just as he was about to leave, he realized that Han Xiao's footsteps stopped.

Han Xiao turned around and walked up to the Head of Research. He grabbed his head, forcing the Head of Research to look him in the eyes, and coldly said, "I remember when he followed me through difficult battles covered in wounds. I remember his misery when he lost an arm. I remember his agony when I planted a prosthetic into him. If not for your bullsh*t race, he could have a very comfortable life in the vast universe. So, what I don't understand is, how is he selfish?

"Is it because he's a good man, so you dare to insult him ruthlessly, knowing that he will not hurt you?"

Han Xiao suddenly turned into Void Form. His pitch-black eyes stared at the Head of Research as he gently said, "But I'm not like him. If you dare speak another word of insult to my subordinate, I will stuff your head up your ass."

Chapter 472: Shattered Light (2)

"Yo—you're not human!" The Head of Research was terrified. His legs were soft, but his head was grabbed by Han Xiao, so he could not even collapse.

Han Xiao's Void Form only lasted a moment before disappearing. The Head of Research, who was staring at him, was the only one who saw his changes. Han Xiao's sudden change in appearance shocked the man.

Void creatures were not murderous, but their mysterious origin and strong powers could strike fear into the hearts of most intelligent species.

Han Xiao let go and allowed the guy to collapse onto the ground. He then looked around; the other researchers were all cowering in the corner and shivering. Those Sunils were just ordinary people, so the pressure that they felt from Han Xiao was because of his far superior level of life.

On the side, the military officers did not stop him and chose to ignore his actions.

"There's no need to hurt him. Let's go, Black Star." Herlous was quite touched. He did not want to bother about it initially, but he did not expect Han Xiao to speak for him or empathize with his words.

It was true. If not for the sake of his race, he could totally not care about them. As a Grade B Super, he could have a very comfortable life in the galaxy. Why would he need to take on the tough life of a mercenary? Those Sunil Supers who left were doing exactly that.

After following Han Xiao through so many adventures, Herlous had already come to view Han Xiao as a close comrade and reliable friend. Han Xiao was someone whom he could trust to have his back. Now that he was contributing to the Black Star Mercenary Group, it was not solely because of Han Xiao's promise. Images of them fighting alongside each other flashed through his mind, and Herlous felt a warmth in his heart.

The sun was setting. They left the restricted military ground and left the city, returning to the spaceship.

This time, Herlous grabbed Han Xiao and laughed wholeheartedly. "Haha, I don't actually care about what others say. When I was opening a bar, I heard these things too many times... but I appreciate it nonetheless."

"It was just frightening someone, small matter. People like you should be more respected." Han Xiao shrugged.

In order to have the officers contribute willingly, building a spiritual bond was crucial. He also had to keep up his image. If he wanted to build an image as a reliable leader, protecting his friends was the most fundamental thing that he had to do. These main characters all had minds of their own. If his actions opposed their creed, they would have conflicts among themselves.

Han Xiao's position was always neutral; everything that he did depended on the benefits and his mood, be it obeying the laws or stirring up chaos. Obviously, in such a situation where he could gain favorability just by expressing his attitude, he would definitely not miss the opportunity.

With a smile, Herlous raised the armor box in his hands and said, "Speaking of which, you have not experienced my combat capability in my final form, have you? Let's have a go at it!"

"Now? Are you sure?" Han Xiao's eyebrows raised. "Do you want to end this beautiful day with an overwhelming defeat?"

"Well, aren't you confident?" Herlous was very certain. "Shattered Light is the Commander Class armor that my brother tailor-made for me. It can increase my strength by more than fifty percent."

He sparred with Han Xiao frequently. Most of the time, he was crushed and could only be a training target. He had been frustrated about it for a very long time and had been waiting for the day that he could erase this shame and regain his pride.

He felt that today was the day.

He felt that it would be very difficult for Han Xiao to beat him after he got back his armor.

"Then I shall be gentler. After all, I'm the one that will repair your armor if I break it."

Han Xiao smiled. He could use this opportunity to reverse engineer the Commander Class armor's blueprint.

In a field under the sunset, the two of them stood two hundred meters away from each other. To them, this distance could be reached with just one dash.

Herlous wore Shattered Light. His face was covered by the helmet, and his armor was silver blue and intricate like a magnificent ancient knight's armor. Two soft, pure white metal plates that looked like cloths extended from each of his shoulders, hanging behind his back like a cape.

Hum!

An enormous, powerful white flame shot into the sky, and rings of shock waves spread out from the center, stirring up dust. It looked incredible. The ten-meter-long Battleship Slicing Blade was entangled in sharp, silver wind. The Shattered Light armor enhanced his Pugilist Energy.

The troops in the camp far away felt this shocking energy wave. Guards rushed to the edge of the camp and looked over with shock.

"Much stronger indeed." Han Xiao's eyes sparkled. From what he saw with his eyes, the energy wave emitted by Herlous while wearing Shattered Light was more than thirty percent stronger.

Boom!

Herlous slashed down with his blade, and a thirty-meter-tall silver energy arc slit open the ground, charging toward Han Xiao like a tsunami. Han Xiao's vision was instantly filled with silver light.

The compressed orbs expanded, and Void Dragon quickly attached itself to his body. Han Xiao stacked his hands together and aimed forward. With a surging gray light, the Void Jet Spray shattered the energy arc just inches away.

Swoosh!

The next moment, a sharp blade dashed past the remnants of the energy arc and slashed down. Herlous had followed behind the energy arc like an arrow shot from a bow. His attacks were precise and quick, closing the distance in no time and not giving Han Xiao any chance to deploy his machinery.

"A tactic I guessed correctly without even thinking." Han Xiao moved aside and dodged with ease. The blade slashed into the ground; the impact spread out under the surface and turned the ground within a ten-meter radius into cracked rocks.

Han Xiao swung his hand, and a black electromagnetic scythe unfolded and appeared.

"I got this close, and you still have the energy to talk?" Herlous snorted. He twisted the blade handle. The Battleship Slicing Blade retracted to about one meter long, suitable for close range combat.

Clank!

In the blink of an eye, the scythe and the blade clashed with each other more than a dozen times.

The two of them moved around swiftly, and the impacts from their clash turned the ground within a mile into a mess. The impact waves from a battle between Grade B Supers could destroy an entire city. The Sunil soldiers spectating from far away continuously exclaimed with shock.

Such terrifying individual destructive powers had these young soldiers astonished and admiring.

Herlous' powerful Energy was like a tsunami, striking one wave after another. When Pugilist reached this grade, their every move could cause huge destruction. Their body was their strongest weapon, especially for someone like Herlous who fought so aggressively.

Melee combat was the strength of the Pugilist class, but Han Xiao was not afraid at all. His various bonuses were not decorations. [One Against the World] alone gave him an eleven percent bonus in all attributes, and [Battlefield Wisdom] had started to stack up once the battle started.

Although I'm not afraid of melee combat, my strength is suppressed in this situation. Normal methods can't restrain Pugilists with such strong destructive powers. Han Xiao blocked the blade with his scythe and simultaneously activated [Repel—Thorns], reflecting a part of the damage.

Herlous' entire body suddenly shook as he was pushed away. His legs split open two fissures in the ground.

Swoosh!

Another compressed orb was activated, and two mechanical wings expanded behind Han Xiao. The wings released a hot wind, and Han Xiao levitated in the air. Although he could build anti-gravity devices, they were too large to become independent parts of the mechanical suit. He had yet to combine the blueprint for mini anti-gravity devices.

His ability to fly still came from the wings. Their power output was already enhanced, so reaching Supersonic speed was a breeze.

Clank!

Han Xiao opened his arms in midair, and almost a hundred compressed orbs shot out from the pipes. They landed on the ground and quickly expanded, turning into artilleries and many mechanical beasts.

The rain of bullets focused on Herlous; his armor was covered in countless fire sparkles.

Even though Han Xiao had yet to update and enhance his machinery and was still using gunpowder and electromagnetic artillery, his Machinery Affinity received higher bonuses after his Promotion, so their damage was increased too. At least it did not deal the minimum '1' damage due to not being able to penetrate Herlous' defenses.

Countless '-5' and '-6' damage numbers popped up continuously on Herlous' body, mixed with the odd '20' to '30' dealt by electromagnetic artilleries.

The damage dealt on one single instance was not high, but the horrifying attack frequency caused damage numbers to pop up from Herlous' body like a waterfall.

This time, Herlous growled, "This tactic... is not useful against me anymore!"

Chapter 473: Shattered Light (3)

Bang!

Before the mechanical beasts pounced, Herlous stomped the floor, cracked open the ground, and jumped into the sky.

The white cape on his shoulders suddenly started dancing. His Energy turned into power and gave these two soft alloys the ability to hover through some special method. Herlous had started flying! He jumped in the sky and charged toward Han Xiao.

Clunk!

The Battleship Slicing Blade collided with Han Xiao's armor, making Han Xiao fly back and roll in the air.

This armor can fly?

Han Xiao stabilized his position and squinted. A Pugilist that could fly would be a much bigger threat.

Han Xiao realized that Herlous had hidden this up his sleeves. If he had yet to go through Promotion, he probably would not have been able to beat Herlous in this state.

Not only was he not shocked, he was delighted. The stronger Herlous was, the stronger his mercenary group would be.

"Now this..." Under the mechanical suit helmet, Han Xiao grinned. "This is interesting!"

...

On the ground, Aroshia, Feidin, and the others looked up at the intense fight in the sky.

"Herlous the Fraud can fly, too. Looks like it's the end for captain. A Mechanic that is forced into melee combat with a Pugilist is basically dead." The oldest Volga tutted.

"Teacher won't lose!" Sylvia's palms were sweaty, her knees weak, as she watched the battle closely.

The two of them were flipping midair. The mechanical beasts on the ground were useless, and the artillery could not hit Herlous due to his speed. Herlous' combat style was smooth, swift, and left no openings, giving Han Xiao no time to increase the distance between them. The way that Sylvia saw it, Han Xiao was clearly disadvantaged.

However, she had an indescribable confidence in her teacher.

The oldest Volga brother's eyes sparkled. "Want to make a bet? I bet that the captain will lose, and you will bet on him to win—what do you say?"

Sylvia was troubled. "My teacher says that gambling is a bad habit."

"Bullsh*t, he only says that because he can't win," the oldest Volga brother said. "Let's bet 300 Enas. Are you this unconfident in the captain?"

"Okay, I'll take it!" Sylvia clenched her teeth and agreed to the bet.

Hum—

Suddenly, a formless disruptive electromagnetic field expanded from Han Xiao's helmet. Herlous' mechanical suit vision instantly turned black, and he lost his sight for a second.

Herlous quickly opened his helmet and observed with his eyes. Seeing that Han Xiao did not get far, he immediately slashed Han Xiao's back sideways with his blade

"You want to run? Have you asked for permission from my blade‽" Herlous laughed.

However, this slash cut Han Xiao in half without any resistance. Herlous was shocked.

Then, the two halves of 'Han Xiao' shook like ripples and vanished.

Void Mirror Image!

"What ability is this? Why have I not seen it before?" Herlous suddenly had a bad feeling.

With his opportunity, Han Xiao discreetly returned to the ground directly under Herlous. A new machine had appeared under his feet. It was a huge metal disc that was placed flat upon the ground. At the heart of it were three equilateral triangle shaped holes emitting a dim blue light—these three holes formed a larger hole, which was pointed at Herlous.

Hum!

Before Herlous could move, the triangular hole shot out a wide, translucent blue light beam that covered him. He lost control of his body and quickly descended. With a loud clank, he was tightly sucked and fixed onto this machine, unable to escape quickly.

This was a mechanical trap. It was initially used by spaceships to draw in objects and not used for combat at all. It was very difficult for it to hit a high-speed target, but if it successfully hit, it would be a very strong constraining method. Shamefully, in his previous life, Han Xiao had been the first player that used this in actual combat.

Han Xiao snapped his fingers. All the artillery aimed at Herlous, who could not move and fired. At the same time, he activated [Overload], [Surging Mechanical Force], and [Mechanical Force Overload] for all of his artillery before activating [Gene Liberation].

Although he only got the lowest 2.2 times damage bonus, it was more than enough to end this battle.

Boom!

Thick smoke from the attacks completely covered Herlous.

"Stop stop stop! I admit defeat! Stop hitting, my armor is going to explode!"

Herlous' panicking voice came out from thick smoke. Han Xiao slowly walked to the side, stopped the artillery, and deactivated the trap.

Herlous stood up. The magnificent and cool Shattered Light was covered in burn marks and cracks. Herlous was heartbroken by how damaged it was.

Not long ago, he had totally held the upper hand, but he had never expected that one single flaw would cause him to lose in an instant. When did Black Star become so strong? Herlous could not beat him even by wearing Shattered Light. Why did the difference between them not grow smaller but larger instead‽

He had thought that he could finally defeat Han Xiao and erase his shame, but now he was more frustrated.

"How much of your strength did you use?"

"Not all anyway of it. You mad?" Han Xiao grinned. As the weak spot of the Mechanic class was melee combat, he was most not afraid of that. After playing the Mechanic class for so many years in his previous life, the people whom he had beaten who tried to force him into melee combat could stack up to a hill.

However, although Han Xiao did win, he still discovered some problems. These cheap styles that he had been using looked rather weak when he used it on an opponent who had the same Grade as him; he had to use the explosive abilities in order to win.

There's nothing wrong with the tactics. It seems like I need to build stronger machines.

Herlous was still grinding his teeth. He was used to being aggressive in battle and fighting the enemy head on, but he felt very restricted when he fought Han Xiao, and it made him feel uncomfortable. It looked like he always had the upper hand, but it was more like he was following Han Xiao's plan. The battle seemed intense, but only he knew how well Han Xiao dodged his attacks. He had only landed a few hits.

Herlous could not maximize his fighting skills as a Pugilist at all. So, all in all, it had been a very uncomfortable and restrained fight for him.

"Alright, stop moping. Not like it's the first time you've lost to me. Take it off, I'll repair for you."

Han Xiao patted Herlous' shoulders and comforted him.

On the other side, Sylvia's face was red from excitement. She extended her hand and chuckled. "300 Enas, a bet's a bet."

"My hard-earned money!" The oldest Volga brother whined in regret.

Regret of trusting that Herlous!

...

The spaceship took off and left Planet Sunil. In the machinery modification room on the spaceship, Han Xiao repaired Shattered Light. Since he satisfied the prerequisite knowledges, he successfully got the Commander Class armor blueprint after paying some Experience.

It was armor specifically for Supers, so its attributes were stronger and could enhance one's Energy. Other than it not having many functions, its performance was not much lower than his Amphiptere. Plus, in comparison, its materials were much cheaper, so the cost of mass producing it was much lower.

Han Xiao had already gotten all of the armor sets from Sunil—Enlistee Class, NCO Class, and Commander Class. He could sell these to the players gradually, which would basically be the first faction specialty. After all, Sunil would not sell their top armor, so the players would have to farm Faction Favorability if they wanted to buy from them. Han Xiao, however, was selling them for money.

Spending money could save time, and time was priceless. This way, the players would be buying their priceless time with money.

How worth it was that‽

Noriosse was very far, located at the border of the Shattered Star Ring like one of the gates into the Star Ring. Even with the various stargates, the spaceship would still have to travel many days before arriving.

This time was more than enough for Han Xiao to build new, stronger machinery to make himself stronger.

Furthermore, he would have the time to think about what preparations he had to make for the upcoming Version 2.0.

The Promotion difficulty was over, so Han Xiao felt very relieved. He had solved it much earlier than he had expected, so it meant that he saved quite a lot of time.

After he completes Ames' mission, he would officially start making preparations for his plan.

It's just finding someone, so it won't take long.

Chapter 474: Shattered Star Ring's Door—Noriosse!

Many days later...

A metal planet was getting closer. It had no green forests, no gray ground, and no blue seas. Metal completely covered the planet's surface.

"Destination detected, hum... Arriving at Noriosse, hum... Surface temperature suitable, hum..."

In the spaceship hall, a round, chubby robot was speaking in a very mechanical voice. Its cylindrical body looked like a can, with two long, thin mechanical arms on both sides, and was about one meter tall. At the bottom of its body was a wheel that allowed it to move.

Suddenly, a big hand grabbed this robot's head and lifted it up. The robot seemed to be panicking, its two mechanical arms swinging randomly in the air. With its round robotic body, it looked strangely adorable.

"Got caught, hum..." the robot said.

This time, the man wearing a black shirt sitting on the sofa spoke.

"Put it down. How many times have I said, Herlous, don't play with my robot!"

Herlous shrugged and put the robot down. As soon as this little guy returned to the ground, it quickly rolled to beside the sofa and tried to hide behind Han Xiao's legs while shivering.

Han Xiao petted the robot's metal head gently.

Herlous scratched his head and said, "Can this artificial intelligence you built really fight?"

"Can't you remember its name? It's called Phillip!" Han Xiao said. "It's still semi-finished."

During the time the spaceship travelled, Han Xiao occupied himself. He had combined quite a few stronger blueprints, updated his combat machinery, and used the new [Advanced Artificial Intelligence Technology] that he had obtained to build Phillip—an artificial intelligence. Compared to the smart chips, the calculation speed, logical structure, and data capacity of an artificial intelligence was many times higher.

There were a few types of artificial intelligences, among which there were two types that were more special. One was giving the system its own virtual personality but still retaining its fixed logics, simulating an intelligent creature. The benefit of this was that artificial intelligences made this way would always obey orders. The other was giving the system a true independent mind; it would have imagination and would be able to think. It would only follow fundamental orders.

Clearly, the latter was smarter and livelier and would have the potential to become a Virtual Life or Mechanical Life. Of course, the risks were higher as well.

For the time being, Han Xiao only needed a good assistant, so Phillip was the former. The reason for it being semi-finished was that some logical orders were not set up yet. Its virtual personality still had flaws and needed to be improved. Nonetheless, running it was not a problem. Phillip could download data through the network, but it would not affect its fixed virtual personality. Han Xiao later built a robot body for it.

Regarding why its name was Phillip, this was the name of his pet turtle in his previous life. To lazy people that wanted a pet but did not like cleaning, turtles were the perfect choice. It would probably not die even if its owner died.

Han Xiao looked out at the planet that was closing in and said in a deep voice, "We'll be arriving soon. This is one of the interchanges into the Shattered Star Ring, and there will be many people from other Star Fields. It's unknown how many strong Supers will there be. We have to keep a low profile and not cause any unnecessary trouble. The goal is to find the Dragon Emperor's teacher. Ames is rushing back from another Star Field. Even if her carrier is very fast, it would still take quite some time. Until she arrives, we will look for clues on Noriosse."

Noriosse was at the border of Shattered Star Ring. This planet did not belong to any civilization. Very long ago, a large financial group had their eyes on the strategic location of this planet and bought it. Back then, this planet had just been a desolate planet with a serial number, its environment very harsh. That financial group had modified the planet, using countless devices to change its ecological environment and make it habitable. Hence, this place became an interchange to enter the Shattered Star Ring.

As there were no planets anywhere near Noriosse and even the nearest stargate was at least three days of jumping away, many travelers would choose to rest there to refuel, restock supplies, repair spaceship, and have some fun. Therefore, that financial group made a lot of profit and earned back their investment in less than fifty years.

The prospering economy there attracted many galactic residents. They smelled financial opportunities and opened stores there. Many commercial organizations started operating there as well. Countless travelers gathered in Noriosse, but Noriosse did not tolerate criminals like Floating Dragon did; their wanted status was effective there. Hence, almost no galactic pirates or wanderers went to Noriosse.

Nonetheless, the financial group that controlled Noriosse deployed many frigates outside its atmosphere to prevent galactic pirates from having their eyes on this prosperous area. They also set the harbor outside the planet, not allowing any spaceship to enter the atmosphere of the planet, not even the frigates. This was to prevent frigates being stolen by someone to enter the planet. Furthermore, the financial group also deployed a large energy shield that shrouded Noriosse's atmosphere, guarding against long-range attacks that would destroy its surface.

All visitors had to leave their spaceships in the port. If any spaceship forcefully entered the atmosphere, the frigate would send out a warning immediately, and if the warning was not taken, they would fire on the spot. If travelers wanted to go to the surface city for entertainment, they had to take the ten thousand meter lift that connected the sky with the ground.

These were the security measures of Noriosse, extremely tight but made the travelers feel safe.

However, in the past, there had been galactic pirates that did not give up. Some tried to force their way in and were blasted into ashes by the frigates; some robbed on the surface and were captured by the security forces waiting for them at the lift. The situation that happened most was, when the galactic pirates robbed others on the surface, they were killed by the travelers that happened to pass by. No one knew who these travelers from other Star Fields were.

Crouching Tiger, Hidden Dragon!

At a closer distance, five enormous metal space stations could be seen floating above different locations in Noriosse. These were five outer atmosphere ports. They were filled with all sorts of guarding turrets and surrounded by a large number of frigates.

The spaceship parked at the closest port. Han Xiao registered for spaceship storage and brought the others to the lift area. It was overwhelmingly crowded, and the queue was full of all kinds of species and creatures.

Aroshia looked up and said, "This place feels familiar. I might have come here before..."

This time, a notice popped up on the interface!

Han Xiao looked at it, and to his surprise, the progress of [Reboot]'s second round had increased by one.

Looks like Noriosse is one of the locations in Aroshia's memory pieces. She came here in one of her lives, and we coincidentally came as well.

Feidin looked around and said, "I felt at least forty Grade B presences around this place."

"No wonder we have to keep a low profile." Sylvia was a little nervous. She felt like she was a sheep that had entered a tiger cave. Luckily, her teacher, Herlous, and Aroshia were just as strong, making her feel more secure.

In Han Xiao's previous life, Noriosse had been a high-class area. If the players wanted to go to other Star Fields, they had to pass by similar interchanges. Of course, when the players could leave their Star Fields, their level was definitely not low.

After queuing for a while, it was finally their turn. The lift ticket inspector continuously collected tickets with a professional smile on his face, greeting every passenger with words of welcome.

When it was Han Xiao's turn, the ticket inspector suddenly smiled and said, "Welcome to Noriosse, Black Star."

"You know me?" Han Xiao looked at him with a slight surprise.

"I'm just relaying a message. Have an enjoyable trip."

When anyone entered the port, the monitoring devices would automatically detect their identities. This was how the high-level managers came to know Han Xiao's identity. The Black Star Mercenary Group was well known in the Shattered Star Ring, especially since their Floating Dragon background was not to be underestimated. Financial groups paid attention to those who were well known in every industry, so the managers gave the order to be more polite to the Black Star Mercenary Group.

The lift was very spacious—every trip carried hundreds of passengers. After waiting for a while, the lift started moving and very quickly slid out of the space station through the track. The wall of the lift was transparent, allowing the passengers to see the magnificent aerial view.

There were tens of lifts nearby like towels that extended into the sky, all operating. At that altitude, they were above the clouds, and the track below them connected the ground that they could not see any more. When looking into the distance, the sky was right before their eyes, turning from black to dark blue as it extended to the end of the horizon where the artificial Fixed Star was shining brightly.

"How beautiful! Phillip, take photos." Sylvia's eyes were sparkling.

Phillip's mechanical eyes kept blinking to shoot photos. It was an assistant, so Han Xiao had given the other officers authority to order it when he was not giving it any order.

As they passed through the clouds, the view of the entire city entered Han Xiao's eyes as he looked down. Countless aircrafts flew around at an altitude of two thousand meters—that was the highest that they were allowed to go. Buildings that pierced hundreds of meters into the sky stood in the city like iron spears.

This was a city entirely made of metal; there were not any vegetation in sight. However, it did not look lifeless. On the contrary, it was very vigorous and filled with colorful and bright neon lights. Large ecological devices provided fresh air for the city. Many devices controlled by the city management system were hidden under the metal ground.

The foundations of the city was made from a type of mass-produced machinery that the Noriosse financial group had purchased from the Crimson Empire. Once this machinery was thrown onto a planet's surface, it expanded into a city like this, easily modifying the planet.

There were ten or so cities on the surface of Noriosse, connected by an electromagnetic railroad for high speed trains. Han Xiao and the others were heading toward City 4.

Looking at the approaching planet surface, Han Xiao suddenly frowned as his heart skipped a beat.

I feel somewhat uneasy. It feels like something is going to happen...

...

As the lift reached the surface, they walked out of the station with the crowd. The streets were crowded with various species.

Clank!

Phillip was knocked into by a passerby and spun a few times. Seeing this, Sylvia bent down and hugged the robot in her arms, preventing it from being kicked away.

"There are way too many people here. How are we going to find the person?' Herlous asked loudly as he pushed away a rather forceful creature that he suspected was a female in the sex industry.

Han Xiao had planned for such an issue. "As Noriosse is a very important traffic junction, many intel organizations have set up divisions here recording information of all travelers. I know what the target looks like, so as long as I ask at an intel organization, there will definitely be some clues."

"You actually know so many things," Herlous said. "That's very reliable."

They walked in the crowd for about twenty minutes before stopping at the door of a high building.

"This is it. The ninety-seventh floor is an agency of a regular intel organization." Han Xiao looked up.

The gang took the lift up to the ninety-seventh floor. Its theme was very dark. The floor to ceiling windows were covered by black clothes, as if they were deliberately trying to create a mysterious atmosphere. After going in, the only receptionist stood at the door, and to the side was a narrow and long corridor. The space there was supposedly very huge, but everywhere else was filled up by black walls.

To guarantee the privacy of customers, this level was divided by walls into opaque rooms for discussing the details of their deal. The path between these rooms were like a maze. This corridor was the only entrance. There were many intersections inside so that the guests would not meet each other.

"I'm here to purchase intel." Han Xiao expressed his intentions to the reception.

"One moment."

The receptionist pressed the button on the table.

After a while, a human dealer in black formal clothes walked out of the corridor and said with a deep voice, "Follow me."

Han Xiao and the others followed the human dealer into the corridor, took a turn at an intersection, and headed to the room.

A few seconds after they walked into the intersections, a birdman dealer led a customer who had just purchased intel out of another intersection and headed to the door, barely missing Han Xiao and the others.

"Thank you for your business."

At the door, the birdman dealer bade farewell to his customer.

This customer was wearing a hoodie, and his entire body was covered by a black cape, blocking his looks.

He did not speak as he walked out and pressed the button on the lift.

The instant that the lift door opened, he looked down, and the light illuminated his face under the hood for a brief second.

Ember!

Chapter 475: Strange Godoran

Of course, Han Xiao did not know DarkStar's people were on Noriosse chasing a traitor and that they had bought intel from the intel organization.

He passed by Ember, and neither of them discovered the other's identity.

This time, the dealer took them to a room to sit.

"What intel would you like to purchase? Our organization has a very strong intel network, be it current matters or secret information, we have it all," the dealer bragged.

"I want to look for someone. Give me a pen and paper. I will draw what he looks like."

The higher one's Intelligence attribute was, the clearer their memory would be. Han Xiao quickly drew out a portrait of a human on the paper. According to the lifespan of a normal human, this person looked to be about fifty years old. He had an extended goatee, an angular face, and many wrinkles. The person looked like an ordinary middle-aged man.

"This person should have come to Noriosse before. I hope to know the time and place that he appeared here," Han Xiao said.

The dealer nodded. He took out a device and searched for a while before saying, "We have fitting intel—this is an ordinary man. We records all the travelers who enter Noriosse. We have been running a 'Person Searching' promotion recently, so this piece of intel only costs 100 Enas."

Sylvia tutted. Intel was indeed expensive. It cost 100 Enas just for the intel of a target marked as an ordinary person. 100 Enas was more than enough to travel across several Star Systems with galactic travelling agencies. Back when she bought intel on Han Xiao's whereabouts, she had spent quite a sum as well.

If she was a coward that did not seek revenge but hid, she would never have known about her father's true face and forever lived in false hatred. How pathetic would her life have been? She would also not have become her teacher's student because of that and never touched the territory of Supers. Thinking back, she could not help but feel gratitude toward Han Xiao for not killing her, or she would never have ended up where she was.

The dealer transferred the information as soon as Han Xiao paid the fee, and the others looked at it together.

"This person came to Noriosse thirty-eight days ago in a cross Star Field voyage that took off at [Ancient Star Desert] Star Field. He did not do anything irregular on Noriosse, and it looked like he's just travelling. Last seen sixteen days ago, south of City 8."

The detailed address was written in the intel—this was where the target had last appeared.

"Sixteen days ago? Is he still in Noriosse?" Han Xiao asked.

The dealer nodded. "We have people in the port, and there are records for every registered ID. He did not leave Noriosse, so he should still be in that place."

"That might not be the case," Han Xiao said.

Intel organizations were not almighty. If someone changed their appearance and used a pre-prepared fake ID, it would be very easy to fool them. Han Xiao could easily do it himself.

Furthermore, the Dragon Emperor's teacher was an Oracle!

After experiencing the effect of the Destiny's Child Character Summon Card, Han Xiao was familiar with the foresight ability. Prophecies were not all knowing. Plus, the future shown in the foresight would not be too far away in advance. If the target did not use his foresight ability, he would be no different from an ordinary person, so maybe he did not know that Han Xiao and the others were looking for him. However, that was delusional—the target should have known about it long ago!

Oracles were all difficult to deal with. If they did not want to get caught, it would be way too easy for them to hide with their powers.

Just like how the Germinal Organization could not find Han Xiao back then no matter what.

Han Xiao could not figure out what that person was thinking. If he wanted to see Ames, he would not have hidden. Although he still had the Destiny's Child Character Summon Card, he did not intend to use it here as the results would not impact him much.

What was important was to carry out the 'search'; the result was not crucial. After all, as long as he gave Ames some clues, he would have done his job.

Whether Ames could see her teacher or not, Han Xiao was not bothered.

Upon getting the clues that they wanted, he and the others left the intel organization. They headed straight to the train station and took the high-speed maglev train to City 8.

The train had many cabins, and the cabin that they were sitting in was for groups. Their seats were around a table.

The scenery outside the window dashed by. Herlous was playing cards with the three brothers again, and Feidin was observing how normal people played cards from the side. Aroshia was eating snacks, and Sylvia was playing with Phillip.

As they had gone to Noriosse just to find someone, their mood was relaxed as they chatted and joked around. Anyway, Black Star was the best at finding things—they had nothing to worry about.

Han Xiao crossed his arms and rested with his eyes closed.

This time, a voice from a strange man appeared beside them.

"Can I sit here?"

Han Xiao opened his eyes—a golden skinned man was standing beside him. He was carrying a backpack and smiling; it was a Godoran. However, his skin color was very light, meaning that he was not a pureblood Godoran.

Han Xiao's heart tightened, instantly alarmed. He had become naturally alert around all hybrid Godorans.

"Who are you?"

"Haha, it seems like I was too direct, allow me to introduce myself." This Godoran bowed elegantly and said with a well-mannered tone, "My name is Alvin. As you can see, I'm a Godoran. However, do not worry, I'm not an arrogant pureblood, just a normal Godoran and Galaxy Human Race mix. I apologize for disturbing, I just hoped to find some company on this short trip."

Han Xiao and the others were puzzled.

A stranger came out of nowhere and wanted to be friends with them. No matter how they looked at it, it was really strange!

Could it be that someone's charm had attracted this guy?

They instantly looked at Feidin then at Han Xiao.

Han Xiao pointed to the side and said, "There are empty seats over there. If you're just looking for a place to rest, please do not disturb us."

"No, no, no, please don't misunderstand me..." Alvin suddenly sat down and pushed Herlous in, as if he was going to sit there no matter what. He smiled sincerely and said, "I'm a traveler in Noriosse too; my friends stayed at the port, and I'm the only one who came to the surface. It's too lonely to travel alone, and I love to make friends. There's a saying in my home that goes 'Making friends with strangers is a man's way'."

"Hey, don't push me. We haven't agreed to let you sit down!" Herlous was displeased.

"Hmm? You're playing Wayne Card?" Alvin saw the cards on the table, and his eyes sparkled. He took out a deck of cards, slammed it on the table, and said, "Well, I happen to be a master in Wayne Card. I use the Light Territory card set and have yet to lose to anyone. Come on, dare to play a round?"

"How are you so quick to become friendly! Who wants to play cards with you‽" Herlous was speechless.

Alvin laughed loudly with confidence and said, "Indeed, just playing is not fun at all. Let's add some stakes to it. 50 Enas for a round, do you dare play with me?"

"Haha, are you challenging me?" Herlous was provoked. He felt that his position and pride as the 'Black Star God of Gambling' had been insulted... although there were few people in the Black Star Mercenary Group.

At the same time, Herlous discreetly turned to look at Han Xiao.

Han Xiao gave him a hand sign, signaling that it was okay.

He had checked Alvin just now. This Godoran was very weak, and his energy sign barely reached Grade C's standard. He could crush him in a second, so it was not much of a threat.

He wanted to see what this Godoran was trying to do and what his motives were, so he allowed him to stay and observed him closely.

Chapter 476: Attack

Herlous received approval. He sat opposite Alvin, arranged his card set, and sneered, "Since you want to give me free money, I shall grant you your wish."

"Haha, it's still uncertain who will lose." Alvin laughed loudly.

His laughter could be heard in the entire cabin. The other passengers looked over.

The two of them started the round, which quickly became intense. Alvin was very quick to familiarize himself with others and spoke in a tone as if they were already very close friends. After the initial awkward stage, the atmosphere soon became harmonious as they chatted and joked with each other.

Han Xiao stared at Alvin from start to finish, preventing him from having any ulterior motives. At the same time, he discreetly activated the metal detector and wave detector in case he had some devices on him.

However, Alvin did not make any strange movements at all; everything that he had on him was normal. He was just playing cards excitedly along the way, shouting and joking, seeming very forthright.

Two hours later, the train arrived at the station.

Alvin took a deep breath of the fresh air, turned around, and slightly bowed toward Han Xiao and the others. "It was a short trip, but the time spent was amazing. It will be engraved in my mind as a beautiful memory. I sincerely thank you guys for your company. We are friends now. I hope that we will have the chance to meet again in the future."

Then, he waved, turned around, and left with his bag.

"Strange guy," Sylvia murmured.

"Such an amiable guy," said Feidin with a smile.

"He's probably just an honest passerby. We might have been overthinking," Herlous said.

Han Xiao glanced at him and did not comment. Although he still did not know Alvin's motive, he rarely believed that anything was coincidental. Even if this guy called Alvin did not do anything abnormal during the trip, he still did not let his guard down. He patted Phillip's metal head and said, "Captured his looks?"

"A total of 372 photos, hum... There's one for every angle, hum..."

"Let's not care about him for now. We shall go search for our target." Han Xiao nodded and walked forward. Then he casually asked, "By the way, I did not see earlier, did you guys win money in cards?"

Herlous scratched his head.

"That guy is quite good; he won a few hundred from me... I lost a lot, so I let Feidin help me. He won a few rounds, and then we arrived. In conclusion... hmm? It happened to be a tie. No one won or lost any money."

Han Xiao's footsteps suddenly paused, and he rubbed his chin.

"Alvin, never heard of this name before... interesting..."

...

As Han Xiao did not know Alvin's motive, he put the matter to the back of his mind, followed the clues from the intel, and found the last place that the target appeared.

It was a narrow, rural street surrounded by tall buildings. Between the tall buildings, there was surprisingly a comparatively short villa. Its construction style fitted the aesthetic of humans—smooth, symmetrical, and with a yard. It looked like a private mansion.

The alloy door was sealed shut, so the inside could only be seen through a small window in the door. There was no one in the yard at this time.

Han Xiao looked around and noticed a button beside the door, likely the doorbell for visitors.

"We're here to search for someone, not to kill... ahem, sneak in. It's best to knock. The target has foresight anyway. If he wants to see us, he will walk out himself."

After pressing the doorbell, they waited at the gate. They were used to climbing over walls, so now that they had to walk the front gate, they felt uncomfortable.

After a while, Han Xiao pressed the doorbell a few more times, but still, no one responded.

"There might be no one in, or the person inside doesn't want to open the gate. What do you say, break in?" Herlous shrugged.

"Since no one responded, we shall go in and take a look before..."

Boom!

Han Xiao's sentence had yet to finish when a loud bang suddenly came from above. He was way too familiar with this sound—it was the sound of a cannon being fired. Han Xiao could analyze the cannon's model with just the sound. "Dodge!"

Everyone there was a Super, so their reaction speed was extremely fast. They immediately jumped away from their initial spot.

Boom!

A chain explosion happened on where they initially stood, and black smoke filled the air—this was the effect of an exploded rocket.

Looking up following bullet trajectory, it was from one window in the building opposite the villa. Quite a few vertical creatures were extending their heads out of the window and looking down. One of them was still holding the rocket launcher.

The next moment, ten or so creatures jumped out of the window and fell right onto the ground from dozens of meters high!

The thick smoke dissipated in the wind, showing the true face of those creatures—a group of stone creatures. They had four arms, two legs, and one head, wearing simple and plain battle suits, and had some firearms in their hands. Some even had melee weapons like mechanical axes, war hammers, and the like. They gave off a mercenary vibe as they were on the verge of attacking.

Han Xiao and gang were just looking for someone; they did not expect to be attacked, so they were surprised.

"Why did you attack us?" Sylvia asked.

"Someone paid us to teach you a lesson," a stone man said.

Teach us a lesson?

Sylvia was about to reply, but suddenly, her face changed, and she yelled, "No, Phillip!"

Han Xiao looked over following her voice. Around the feet of these stone mercenaries, broken parts were spilled all over the floor.

Phillip had been too slow and could not dodge the earlier explosions. It had been blasted into pieces and become a pile of scrap metal.

At this time, these stone warriors struck. They growled with a weird voice and charged toward Han Xiao and the others.

Han Xiao tutted. He pulled out a compressed orb from his necklace, threw it onto the floor, and it rapidly expanded into the black Amphiptere mechanical suit. However, he did not wear it—it stood beside him.

This time, Han Xiao said with a deep voice, "Beat them up!"

Hum!

The eyes of the Amphiptere mechanical suit suddenly lit up!

This mechanical suit moved on its own. It swung its leg sideways like a black lash, whipping the foremost stone warrior on his chest.

Pa!

The huge strength blew him away and smashed him against the wall, shattering a huge pile of pebbles. It was unknown whether it was from the wall or from the stone warrior's body.

"Order effective, hum... Combat Mode activated, hum... The enemy is blown away, hum..."

The empty Amphiptere mechanical suit was in combat mode, and Phillip's voice came out of the helmet.

Phillip was an artificial intelligence, so it lived in computer systems. Machinery was just what he controlled. When the shell was destroyed, it would not be damaged with it. Its core was behind layers of protection. With the computing speed of an artificial intelligence, it could simultaneously control dozens more mechanical beasts than before. Furthermore, with the combat simulations in the database, it could improvise on the spot and battle independently with a high standard!

This meant that Phillip could replace him and pilot the mechanical suit, and it could pilot more than one!

The smart chips before this had limited computing speed, comparatively weak combat capabilities, and could not react quickly. These were the most necessary attributes in the everchanging battlefield, so the smart chip could only be used as an assisting feature in combination with Han Xiao's nerves connection. However, with the new smart system built with [Advanced Artificial Intelligence Technology], like the improvement from gunpowder weapon to electromagnetic weapons, it was a complete update and enhancement!

Han Xiao's Hound Style had very limited effectiveness against enemies at the same Grade, but together with the strong mechanical suits operated by an artificial intelligence, it would make an entirely different level of impact. His mechanical suits were high quality mechanical weapons, so this made up for his shortage of robot warriors! Even if it was against someone at the same Grade, it would still last very long!

All High-End Knowledges were useful. The artificial intelligence technology that had powerful computing speed was one of the prerequisites of completing the Army Style!

Han Xiao turned around to Sylvia and said, "Go back and copy the theory for smart chips five times."

Sylvia's face immediately dropped, completely downcast.

Buzz!

Mechanical Force gushed out from Han Xiao's fingertips and entangled with Amphiptere mechanical suit, providing it with his bonuses.

There was no need for him to fight; Phillip controlled the mechanical suit and dealt with the enemies. It analyzed all the movements of the enemies and accurately dodged all their attacks. Its heavy punches cracked the rock skin of the stone warriors, making suppressed loud noises.

Dong, dong!

Pebbles spurted everywhere!

"Don't hit too hard. We can't randomly kill people on Noriosse."

Han Xiao leaned against the wall and watched the one-sided battle. His eyes flickered. "Furthermore, these stone men were probably hired by that Oracle to wait for us. It looks like he indeed knows that someone is looking for him. Humph."

Chapter 477: DarkStar Traitor

Clank!

With a set of effortless punches and less than two minutes, the Amphiptere mechanical suit controlled by Phillip defeated those stone warriors. The rocks lay down on the ground and whined weakly.

They were just Grade C, so the mechanical suit enhanced by Han Xiao easily crushed them.

"No! My smooth skin!" The head of the stone warriors looked at his cracked body and wailed. In terms of stone man aesthetics, the quality of the stone on their body's surface was the same as their attractiveness. The most beautiful ones were, of course, diamonds, crystals, and minerals of the same sort. Even if it was normal stone, if it was as smooth as a mirror, they would be considered handsome.

Even if they could digest stones to heal their wounds, it would take a very long for them to recover.

This enormous sized guy's moaning made Han Xiao feel like beating him up again.

"You're not even stronger than us, yet you want to teach us a lesson? Where did you find the courage‽" The oldest Volga looked at them disdainfully.

Han Xiao was a little surprised by how weak those stone warriors were. It was impossible for their employer not to know how strong Han Xiao and the others were. What impact would it make for him to send these weaklings? Was it just a warning or welcome gift? Could he have guessed incorrectly and the stone warriors' employer was not their target?

Matters involving Oracles were always a headache. Han Xiao did not want to dwell on it; he grabbed the stone warrior and questioned him directly. "Who is your employer?"

Accordingly, mercenaries would not sell the identity of their employer. Han Xiao was already prepared to interrogate then, but to his surprise, these stone warriors gave him an expected reply.

"The employer wanted us to come here today to deal with the person that pressed the doorbell of that villa and said that our lives wouldn't be in danger. If we got defeated, we should tell you a location to find a person there, and there will be someone there that knows his whereabouts," the stone warrior said nervously. "He also said that you will forcefully ask for the employer's identity and told me to relay his exact words. 'You guessed right—it is me indeed. Don't think I don't know you used my name fraudulently. Play a game with me if you want to find me'."

Everyone's expression changed slightly.

"Damn Oracle!" Han Xiao clenched his teeth.

Herlous slapped Han Xiao's back heavily and laughed loudly. "Hahahaha, you met a colleague!"

"Colleagues hate each other." Han Xiao snorted and asked for the location. The stone warrior said the next location while shivering—north of City 8. They had to cross the entire city to go there.

Han Xiao stood up and pondered. The intention of the Oracle to hire these stone warriors was actually to leave some clues and lead them to the next location.

The target had intentionally left traces sixteen days ago then used his foresight ability to peek into their whereabouts, knowing that they would be arriving at this place today. Hence, he hired these stone warriors. The ability to foresee was not omnipotent or omniscient; it could not be used randomly and needed some attached strings, which was why the target deliberately left clues for the intel organizations.

He could certainly break the prophecy and kill these stone warriors. The problem was whether that would be in the Oracle's calculations, telling the stone warriors there would be no danger to provoke Han Xiao's rebellious thought, while his true intention was to make Han Xiao kill these stone warriors, which would attract the security forces. Would there even be a possibility that the counter thoughts that Han Xiao was currently having had been seen through by the Oracle? Could he have used Han Xiao's personality as the foundation for telling these stone men that they were definitely safe‽

"This is exactly why I hate Oracles." Han Xiao felt a headache.

Despite knowing the powers of the Dragon Emperor's teacher, this feeling of restraint and following the opponent's plan unwillingly made Han Xiao very irritated.

Oracles were good at using their powers to plot. To Oracles who were strong enough, intelligence had no meaning. When someone dealing with an Oracle thought that they were being smart, what they did not know was that the Oracle had used their 'smartness' from the start. One never knew what the Oracle really wanted one to do.

Luckily, Han Xiao had his advantage. He knew the target's powers and ability very clearly, so he could judge his mindset from an Oracle's perspective. It would not guarantee that he would escape the target's calculations, but it would at least ensure he would not get tricked unknowingly. Furthermore, from what he knew about the target, although the target had a bad character, he rarely meant harm.

This was a good piece of news. After all, although Oracles were not physically powerful, being their enemy would be something very, very, very troublesome!

"What's next? Should we go where he said?" Herlous asked.

"Let's see what game he is playing."

Han Xiao snapped his fingers, creating a Mechanical Force spark. Amphiptere quickly turned into a compressed orb and attached itself to his necklace.

At the same time, Mechanical Forces spread out like electric currents, connecting the broken robot parts with each other. Suddenly, these parts levitated and gathered, then quickly assembled. Some distorted parts recovered to their original shape under the Mechanical Force. In the blink of an eye, the pile of waste parts turned back into the round robot body.

Basic Machinery Construction and Waste Modification!

The tiny round robot started moving again. Phillip waved its mechanical arms, slid beside Han Xiao's feet, and reported, "Self-checking, hum... performance decreased by twenty-five percent, hum... storage data backed up, hum..."

Sylvia's eyes were sparkling so brightly that stars almost jumped out. "Teacher, I want to learn this!"

"You want to run before you learned to walk?" Han Xiao glanced at her. He retrieved the mechanical flying bugs that he had discreetly sent out earlier to detect the inside of the villa, confirmed there was no one inside, and turned away. "There are no more clues here, let's go."

They left this rural street, leaving a group of wailing stone men behind.

At the same time, in a secret location in Noriosse City 4, many DarkStar members were gathered in a dark room. They often liked to host secret operations in dark places like that.

"According to our intel, the traitor appeared simultaneously at the center of City 7, northeast of City 6, and City 4's train station. His ability is to have five doppelgangers. One of them is in our hands, the whereabouts of the other three have been exposed, and the last one has yet to be found. That should be his original body that he hid. His doppelgangers can't be too far away from his original body, or they would vanish. The exact distance is unknown, but it won't be further than a planet. Hence, he's still on Noriosse," a DarkStar warrior said.

In the corner of the room, a Godoran was tied tightly to a chair. This Godoran was covered in blood, and it was unknown how much suffering he had gone through. He looked exactly like Alvin, and he was sneering.

"What are you laughing at?" a DarkStar soldier yelled.

"Hehehe, you will never catch my real body."

Alvin was indeed the traitor that DarkStar was tracking down. His Esper ability was creating doppelgangers, and the one that had been caught by DarkStar was one of the doppelgangers.

If Han Xiao was there, he would most likely be reminded of Black Spider, who was imprisoned in Bell of Death Island on Planet Aquamarine. Both of them had doppelganger-type Esper abilities, but the specific effects were different. Black Spider's doppelgangers were puppets—he could only manipulate them to carry out simple tasks, and his consciousness could only exist in one puppet at a time but could be transferred. As long as one doppelganger lived, he would not die. He was very difficult to kill.

Alvin was different. Up to five doppelgangers could exist at one time, and every one of them could fight on their own. His consciousness was divided into five—these doppelgangers were all him, and one of them was his real body. As they shared senses, if the doppelganger was injured or died, the pain would be fed back to the consciousness in his real body, and his mind would be damaged. Furthermore, the doppelgangers would shatter if they were too far away from the real body, which was the same as dying and would also deal a certain amount of damage to the real body's consciousness.

So as long as they had control of one doppelganger, they would be able to determine the approximate area that the real body was in—Alvin was still hidden on Noriosse.

"Captain Forsyth," a soldier suddenly said, "the latest intel shows that the doppelganger in City 4 is taking the train to City 8. Lieutenant Sherman did not follow the plan and attack..."

"Okay," Forsyth replied indifferently. He was a hybrid Godoran, a Grade B Super of DarkStar. He was also the captain of this team... on the outside.

Forsyth looked at the intel for a while more then walked out of the room. Outside was a long corridor. He turned two corners, walked into an empty room, and pressed a disguised button on the wall. The wall silently slid open, and behind the door was a secret room.

He went inside, and there were only two people there, Anur and Ember.

To pursue this traitor, not only did DarkStar dispatch a large number of elite soldiers consisting of seven Grade B Supers, they even dispatched Anur and Ember who were two Calamity Grades. This was a huge operation!

DarkStar abhorred this traitor. Alvin had leaked part of DarkStar's information to Godora, leading to one Grade A member, Vivira, falling into a trap during mission, getting captured by Godora, and being imprisoned in Rainbow Prison. Moreover, Alvin had more information on his hands. If it was revealed, Godora would come to know even more about them. This was a huge hidden danger.

DarkStar would not allow traitors to live. Now that the team had trapped Alvin on Noriosse, it was a game of cat and mouse. Sooner or later, they would find him. Therefore, the information would not be leaked for the time being. If Alvin wanted to live, he could only rely on the rescue, and if he gave out all that he knew to Godora, he would have no value to Godora anymore. Hence, he could not say anything until Godora sent someone to save him.

DarkStar was also very clear on this point. Because of Noriosse's specialness, neither DarkStar nor Godora would not dispatched battleships to surround the planet. This consortium had a very deeply rooted network and complex connections with several Star Cluster level Civilizations. If they wanted Alvin, they could only send their Super warriors to act on the planet.

"Your Excellencies." Forsyth bowed respectfully and said, "We have new information. A doppelganger of the traitor took the train toward City 8. Sherman did not follow the plan of attack."

"Why?" Anur asked with a deep voice.

"He accidentally met the Black Star mercenary group on the train!" Forsyth said. "Alvin sat down with them, and Sherman didn't have the confidence to attack."

"Black Star?" Anur frowned and looked at Ember on the side. He still remembered how obsessed Ember had been with Black Star. Anur said with a deep voice, "The task is more important. We're hidden in the dark, so there's no need to provoke him."

When Ember heard this name, his face did not change at all. To him, this name seemed to have become meaningless. His emotions did not fluctuate at all, and his tone remained indifferent.

"Rest assured, he's nothing to me now. The traitor is our goal; as long as the Black Star does not interfere with our affairs, he can live."

"That's right." A sense of satisfaction flashed within Anur's eyes and disappeared in a split second.

"Sherman's decision is very correct," Anur said. "Behind the Black star is the Dragon Emperor, so there's no need to cause more problems. Alvin was lucky to have accidentally met this gang of mercenaries, but his luck will not keep going. Have Sherman continue to track him...

"Looking at the time, Godora's reinforcements should be arriving very soon. Alvin's doppelgangers share their senses, so all his doppelgangers know that you're tracking him. Tell those acting outside to be cautious, don't fall into his trap."

Chapter 478: There Is One Type of Book That Will Never Be Obsolete in Any Era

Han Xiao and the gang took the low altitude transport aircraft to the north of City 8, the popular commercial street that the stone mercenaries' clue pointed to. It was crowded, noisy, and wide. In the middle of it was a fountain square, surrounded by shops of all kinds.

Following the address, they came to the door of a shop. This building was colorfully painted, and vibrant magic lanterns were installed on both sides of the open door.

Herlous looked up at the shop's name, and his face twitched.

"Universal Love Bookstore... what kind of name is this?"

"Go in and see."

The layout of the shop inside was surprisingly very simple. The floor was made from smooth, brown wood, and there were rows of glazed wood shelves filled with books. These books exuded a rich magic vibe; they seemed to be high-grade magic books. The store was filled with the fragrance of books. In a place like Noriosse, Mages were almost the only ones left still using books. This was clearly a bookstore for Mages.

According to the clue, there was a person there who knew the whereabouts of the target. Han Xiao looked around, but because there were so many bookshelves, he could not see if there was anyone inside. He patted Herlous on the shoulder, telling him to call for someone.

Herlous was about to open his mouth when he suddenly noticed a problem. "Wait a minute, why don't you do this little thing yourself?"

"You have a great physique and a loud voice," Han Xiao said with no expression on his face. "It's mainly because I'm lazy."

"..."

Herlous stared at him before letting out a thunderous shout. "Is—any—one—in!!"

Swoosh!

A sound came from deep within the bookshelves. The person inside was shocked and accidentally bumped the shelves, causing a pile of books to drop.

"On—one moment, I'm coming..."

A male human in a Mage's robe walked out limping while still hissing from the pain on his foot caused by the books that had fallen. When he saw Han Xiao and the others, he put up a warm smile.

"I am the owner of this bookstore. Do you like single or multiple people? Beautiful or rough? What race do you like? Oh, you are all humanoid species. I have humanoid creatures of all skins tones here!"

They were confused, and Sylvia asked, "What are you talking about?"

The mage store owner blinked, then gave a look of understanding and said, "I see, we have hybrids too. Be it insects, beasts, machinery, or anything you can think of, I have it here. I'm sure it will suit your taste!"

The more Han Xiao heard him talk, the more he felt something was wrong. "Aren't you selling books?"

At this time, Aroshia opened a book on the shelf, and the others looked over. The magic book was filled with illustrations, and the pictures were moving like they were alive. This was a kind of magic often used to make videos. Like movies in a book, every picture was a fragment.

It looked very high-end, but the content was...

"Ah!" Sylvia's face suddenly turned red, and she hurriedly turned away, but she could not help but to peek at the book.

"Th—this..." Herlous was bewildered. His world view was impacted.

Aroshia was amused. "So, this is the material life reproduction process..."

"Unknown information discovered, hum... Ongoing data acquisition, hum... " Philip's mechanical eye was wildly flickering, capturing every frame of the picture.

The Volga three brothers took out a huge pile of books from the bookshelf extremely quickly, placed them on the counter, and asked, "How much? I'll take all of them!"

"Stop it." Han Xiao closed the book in Aroshia's hands and threw it aside. He stared at the Mage owner and said with a deep voice, "I'm looking for a guy with foresight ability. He should've left you a message."

The Mage shop owner's smile suddenly turned stiff. He become disappointed and mumbled, "Not here to buy books again. I have already made the decoration so formal, how are there still no guests? Is it really necessary to be this afraid of letting others know about this kind of thing?"

The Mage glanced at Han Xiao and the others, adjusted his clothes, and stood straight. His temperament suddenly changed. Now he looked like how a Mage should look like. He said, "Let me introduce myself. You can call me Yi Xuan; I'm a Teleportation Mage. This bookstore is just a side job; my main business is operating a portal service."

In some of the magic focused planets or advanced civilization planets, there were always Mages that ran teleportation businesses. They sent the customers to another location on the same planet, saving their time. The further the distance transported, the higher the consumption and difficulty was. Hence, most of it were same planet teleportations, rarely to other planets. If the coordinates were not set correctly, the customer would be thrown into space. Only Mages that were strong enough dared to do extremely long range teleportation.

Back then when Ames demolished the DarkStar mothership, she had used teleportation magic and arrived instantly from several Star Systems away. The caster was another Beyond Grade A individual who she fought with to kill time. That person had accurately located Floating Dragon Island from several Star Systems away with no deviation. Their magic power was unbelievable.

"You are a Teleportation Mage?" Han Xiao asked. "So, was the target that I want to find sent to another place in Noriosse by you?"

Yi Xuan shrugged and said, "He paid the fees, so I teleported him. It was a normal transaction."

"Where did he go?"

"Ha, I will not give away clients' privacy." Yi Xuan chuckled. "By the way, he also left me a message to convey to anyone that wants to find him."

"What did he say?" Han Xiao frowned.

"He said, he wants to play a game with you. As long as you steal the Heart of Crystal Fire, he will meet you."

"Heart of Crystal Fire?" Han Xiao kicked Phillip lightly and said, "Search it."

"Searching, hum... Found, hum..." Philip's mechanical eye suddenly emitted light in the air to form a translucent projection screen. On it was information about the Heart of Crystal Fire.

Heart of Crystal Fire: A ring made by a rare crystal born in lava, a very exquisite luxury. Legend says that it is immune to high temperature and burning. It was once sold for a high price of 7,930,000 Enas to the leader of the Noriosse financial group, Rockfess, for his wife. When Rockfess and his wife appeared in public, his wife is always wearing this ring.

"Sev—seven million and nine hundred thirty thousand!" Herlous spat blood. Spending so much money to buy a lousy ring just to please a woman‽

This could buy numerous battleships!

His world view was once again shaken.

Han Xiao's expression also changed. "He wants me to steal a Super financial group's leader's wife's price jewelry, huh? Is he trying to use us, or is he trying to make a fool out of us‽"

Stealing some precious jewelry from the wife of the leader of the financial group that controls Noriosse in Noriosse?

The Dragon Emperor's teacher clearly wants to ridicule me!

"Don't ask me, I just took the money and pass the message." Yi Xuan shrugged. "Rockfess' wife is in Noriosse, but don't expect me to send you there directly; I don't want to be as your accomplice."

Squinting, Han Xiao said with a low voice, "I have no interest in completing this ridiculous request anyway. Where did you send him?"

"Haven't I already told you?" Yi Xuan said impatiently. "I will not disclose the privacy of customers. Also, don't think about bribing me, I have my professional ethics."

"Then don't blame me for beating you up." With a ferocious expression, Herlous raised his huge fists and stepped forward. He planned to scare this Teleportation Mage.

His hand was just about to touch Yi Xuan's collar when a change happened!

Hum!

A light door suddenly appeared right in the gap between the two of them. Herlous was shocked. His reaction was very fast, so he stopped his forward momentum immediately and was about to retreat. To his surprise, a red tentacle suddenly extended out quickly of the light door and wrapped around his body. A huge force blasted from the tentacle and pulled Herlous into the light door as Herlous disappeared.

Then, a whirlpool-like sound appeared in the air. The light door rotated around the center point, narrowed, and quickly disappeared without a trace.

"Herlous!" the oldest Volga exclaimed in shock.

The face of everyone suddenly changed.

The atmosphere was stiff for a moment.

Yi Xuan glanced at everyone proudly.

"What that person said was exactly right. When the people that are here find that they can't get the information they need, they will threaten me. Humph, you didn't expect this, did you? I'm prepared!"

Han Xiao was very calm, but he held his forehead in frustration. When Herlous acted, he was already aware that something was not right. He wanted to stop him, but before his mouth opened, Herlous was already caught. Pugilists being able to move too fast actually had its disadvantages!

Sure enough, the target guessed this situation, so he reminded the Mage in advance to trick them. When the target made the over the top request to steal the Heart of Crystal Fire, it became a 'trigger' to his prophecy. Furthermore, even without the use of his prophecy ability, their reaction could be guessed. He knew that there was a great chance that they would refuse the request and find another way from the Teleportation Mage, and threatening was clearly highly likely. Hence, he did this to put them in a dilemma.

"Teleportation magic, such an irritating ability..." Han Xiao discreetly sighed. Herlous was unluckily caught, so getting him back was a pressing matter.

The atmosphere was intense. This time, Yi Xuan pointed to the door, and with a tone of having everything under his control, he said, "I'm trained in teleportation magic and always maintain it at a state that can be triggered anytime. Before you can touch me, I will be able to teleport away, so don't even think about threatening me.

"Your friend wanted to attack me, so I will let him suffer for a bit. In two hours, I will send him back and throw him at the northern entrance of City 8 where you can find him. Now, I have no interest in fighting with you. If you're not going to buy a book, please get out of my bookstore, you are not welcomed here!"

Chapter 479: Blink

The red tentacle seemed to belong to a monster, and it looked like Herlous had been thrown somewhere that they did not know of. If they wanted to bring him back, they could only find a solution from this Teleportation Mage.

Teleportation magic was very powerful, but there were many restrictions when players used it. The requirements to learn it were very high. Furthermore, most teleportation spells could only be used in non-combat state or needed some kind of guide, and they could not be interrupted halfway. Basically, it could only be used as a travelling method.

"There are strong people everywhere. Noriosse is really so scary." Sylvia swallowed her saliva nervously.

"Should we fight?" the second oldest Volga brother said gravely. "There are many people around here. If a fight breaks out, the security team will soon intervene. I can sense his teleportation magic is at the state that can be triggered at any moment. He will leave before we move, and we absolutely can't follow him through the light door. If he closes the light door halfway, we will be cut in half."

Yi Xuan interrupted and said, "Your friend is right, so quickly get out of my..."

Before his sentence finished, Han Xiao activated his mechanical suit and rushed out without saying a word like a bolt of lightning.

"You really don't understand what I said do you, you're still not giving up and want to attack me? I've already read your plans. You are so violent!"

Yi Xuan did not panic at all. He sneered and activated the standby teleportation Magic. A light door suddenly appeared behind him, and he stepped into it in an instant.

At this time, the mechanical suit warrior that wanted to attack him was still a distance away from him. With his casting speed, he would be able to close the portal before the opponent got close.

Just then!

A big hand suddenly appeared in front of his eyes like it appeared out of nowhere, and before Yi Xuan had time to respond, the hand passed through the portal and strongly grabbed onto his face.

With a palm covering his eyes, Yi Xuan could not see anything. At that moment, he finally panicked.

What happened‽

The next moment, a huge surging force came from the hand. Han Xiao, who was in his Void Form, pulled Yi Xuan out of the portal!

Because Yi Xuan's body had to cross the light door again, he had no choice but to quickly stop his already prepared spell to close the portal, or the person that would be cut into half would be him!

The situation had instantly reversed!

With a surging Mechanical Force, the Void Dragon mechanical suit that was now an empty shell behind Han Xiao split into its parts and covered Han Xiao again.

He swung hard, throwing Yi Xuan out like a cannon, breaking rows of shelves on the way. Torn paper fluttered all around.

Bang!

Yi Xuan slammed into the wall, which broke. His head was bleeding. He had yet to recover from the dizziness when he suddenly felt a weight on his body.

Han Xiao followed him like a shadow, pressing his hands against his back and locking it with his knees, while his other hand pressed his face on the floor and instantly subdued. Yi Xuan was unable to move!

A heart-stopping energy was gathering in the arms of the mechanical suit as if it would erupt any time. Then, Yi Xuan heard Han Xiao's banter.

"What did you just say? Say it again."

Blood flew down from Yi Xuan's forehead, wetting his hair. His eyes were wide open and filled with intense horror, and his face was covered in disbelief.

He did not expect this life saving method that he had used countless times to fail!

What Han Xiao used was his Race Talent—[Void Travel].

In the almost static Void Vision, the movements of everyone were halted. No matter what escape method Yi Xuan had, it did not make a difference. Han Xiao easily got close to this Teleportation Mage, then deactivated Void Vision and returned to reality, directly closing the distance between them and catching the opponent. In the eyes of the others, Han Xiao clearly appeared before Yi Xuan out of nowhere.

"Ho—how did you..."

Han Xiao increased the force in his hand and said coldly, "Let my companion out, and don't play any tricks, unless you want your brains to splash all over your bookstore."

"I—I give up, don't misfire!" Yi Xuan hastily did as he was told. His life was threatened, so he did not dare mess around. A few meters away, a teleportation light door slowly appeared.

Fifteen seconds earlier...

Hum!

In a red sky, a light door suddenly appeared. Countless red tentacles rushed into the sky and into the light door. The next moment, Herlous was pulled in.

With little time to react, he forced the tentacles open with arms, drew the Battleship Slicing Blade from his back, slashed horizontally around his body, and cut all the tentacles in half. However, he was in midair, so he fell right down. At about thirty meters from the ground, he could see the maroon ground.

Bang!

Herlous slammed onto the ground.

He looked up at the sky, and the teleportation door had already disappeared.

"It was a trap. This is not good. I can't go back myself." Herlous was angry and frustrated. "What is this place. What were the tentacles just now?"

He looked around. On the red plain, there were no creatures, only black holes on the ground.

Herlous' face suddenly changed, and he jumped up right away.

Boom boom boom!

The next moment, a large number of tentacles broke out of the ground from where he had just stood. There were hundreds of them, and they all went directly at him.

"These tentacles seem to belong to a creature hidden in the ground. How big is the size of this monster‽" Herlous was sweating on his forehead. He was just about to attack again when a red stream of light suddenly appeared in the edge of his line of sight.

Swoosh!

This red stream of light bolted past all tentacles in an instant. The hundreds of tentacles stopped simultaneously. At the position where the red light passed through, a smooth cut appeared on all the tentacles, and they were all cut into two. The half that had been cut off fell onto the ground, and the tentacles retracted back under the ground.

The red light made a circle and stopped in front of Herlous, showing its true identity.

"It's you!" Herlous was surprised.

"Hmm? I've seen you before." The other person obviously knew Herlous and was surprised as well.

Before the conversation could carry on, a buzz from a spell appeared in the sky, and the portal appeared again.

"Ha, it seems that captain is done with that Teleportation Mage. That was really efficient."

Herlous' eyes brightened as he laughed out loud. He had a lot of trust in Han Xiao. After being thrown here, he believed that Han Xiao would bring him back very soon.

As expected, the petty tricks of that Teleportation Mage were nothing in front of the captain. He did not even last for a minute.

"Great, I can finally get out!" The other person was surprised as well.

In the bookstore, the portal was open, and they stared at the light door. Not long after, Herlous flew out, but he was not the only one; another person followed him out of the light door.

"There are other people inside!" Sylvia exclaimed. "Who are you?"

Han Xiao looked over and was stunned.

"Wilsander‽"

This person was shockingly the Floating Dragon Island Dragon Guard Captain, Wilsander!

"Hey, it's been a long time." Wilsander was boney and depraved looking as always.

"Why are you here?" Han Xiao said with surprise. "And coming out of the portal‽"

Wilsander dry coughed and pointed at Herlous. "I got in the way he got in."

Han Xiao's mouth twitched as he figured out what had happened.

It turned out, in addition to himself, Ames had also sent Wilsander to find her teacher. Then Wilsander was played by the Dragon Emperor's teacher as well. He found Yi Xuan and encountered the same problem as them. As a big time galactic pirate once, Wilsander's mindset was to do things with violence. Hence, he was thrown somewhere else by this Teleportation Mage.

Han Xiao did not expect to meet Wilsander here. "When did you get here?"

"A few days ago, not much earlier than you."

Wilsander looked at Yi Xuan, who was pressed down on the ground by Han Xiao, and his face suddenly turned furious. He rushed over, the pair of wings behind him suddenly unfolding, shining with a bright red glow on their edges. With overflowing murderous intent, he yelled, "You dare to trick me! I'll kill you!"

The wings slashed down quickly, and Han Xiao hurriedly reached out to hold onto Wilsander's demon wings firmly.

"Don't act in the heat of the moment. Noriosse doesn't allow random killings. Plus, we have to dig out clues about the Dragon Emperor's teacher from his mouth."

"Fine." Wilsander felt that Han Xiao's logic was sound, so he put the wings back. Suddenly, he realized that something was wrong. His face suddenly changed, and he turned around and looked at Han Xiao with uncertainty.

With his Grade B+ strength, how could Han Xiao withstand his attack this casually and easily?

When he first met Black Star, he had been far from that strong!

Not bothering about Wilsander, who was discreetly being shocked, Han Xiao questioned Yi Xuan. "Tell me, where did you send my target to."

"I—I don't know," Yi Xuan said with a trembling voice.

"Huh, you sure are bold. It seems that you really aren't afraid of death!" Herlous clenched his fist. The sound of bones cracking came from his fists, and an eager expression could be seen on his face. "I have yet to settle things between us."

"N—no, you misunderstood," Yi Xuan wailed. "I really don't know. He asked me to use the random portal, and the coordinate range is the surface of Noriosse. Since the position is random, I don't know where he went."

Han Xiao frowned, turned around, and said, "Feidin, do me a favor."

Feidin nodded. He walked forward and placed his finger on Yi Xuan's forehead. His Psychic powers penetrated into Yi Xuan's brain, and he told the Teleportation Mage to repeat what he had just said. Then Feidin closed his eyes, only opening them after a while. He shook his head, saying, "He's not lying; this is true. He honestly doesn't know the whereabouts of the target."

They looked at each other and were all a little beaten. They had thought that they finally had the upper hand, but the clues ended again.

Sylvia bit her lips and said angrily, "I got it, this is exactly his intention. Even if we successfully force out his whereabouts, we will still come to no result. He deliberately used the random portal to let us see some hope before upsetting us. This guy is so annoying!"

Wilsander swung his tail, irritated. "Is following his request to steal the Heart of Crystal Fire the only thing that we can do? This is the only clue."

Han Xiao was frowning heavily. Suddenly, an idea flashed past his eyes. He quickly suppressed his smile and said with a serious tone, "I'm not going to bother about his request. Since this is the case, we won't find him anymore. Anyway, what we've done is enough."

"Are we going to give up?" Herlous clenched his teeth, he was not very satisfied with the result. He really wanted to catch this Oracle and give him a good beating!

"There's no need for us to follow what the target wants us to do. Ames is going to arrive soon. As long as we tell her this clue, our job is considered complete."

Han Xiao stood up and clapped his hands. He took out a healing agent, threw it to Yi Xuan, and walked away.

"Yo—you're just going to give up like this?" Yi Xuan stood up, surprised. He had thought that he would inevitably get a beating.

"Exactly, why not teach him a lesson? I was tricked so badly by him," Herlous added.

Han Xiao rolled his eyes and said, "Come on, at least he did not throw you into outer space. He didn't want to kill you, and that saved his life."

Then, the Great Mechanic Han turned around, looked at the mess, and said, "But I'm not going to pay the repair fee."

"I didn't want you to." Yi Xuan smiled bitterly. He did not plan to provoke Han Xiao ever again. Han Xiao had some kind of instant teleportation ability, so he would not be able to run no matter how fast his teleportation spell was. He was only good at teleportation spells and knew almost nothing about attack spells. Since even his core ability was useless, how would he be able to fight at all? He just wanted to wait for that group of people to leave and never return.

They left that strange, weird bookstore. There was a new member in the group of people, Wilsander. He thought that he would rather work together with his colleague than act alone.

On the way, Wilsander pulled Han Xiao aside and said in an apprehensive tone, "Are we really going to give up on the target? Will Ames be angry about that?"

"There is no need to; the target is definitely still on Noriosse. When Ames arrives, it will take no time for her the search through the entire planet given how strong she is. Hence, we don't need to hurry to find him. As long as the Dragon Emperor arrives, he will have nowhere to hide," Han Xiao deliberately whispered, as if he did not want anyone to hear.

Chapter 480: Eternal Oracle, Aesop Hurricane

Three days later, in Noriosse North Space Port, where countless travelers came and went, an ordinary space human female was slowly walking, carrying a backpack.

In fact, this was someone in disguise. In actuality, it was the target whom Han Xiao was looking for—Ames' teacher who had once adopted her in her childhood and guided her to awaken her Super talent.

His name was Aesop, and his power was foresight. However, as compared to his rare prophetic ability, his race was even rarer.

Aesop had been born before the Galaxy Calendar started. He was an Eternal, a being who lived for countless years.

Long before Han Xiao had contact with the Teleportation Mage, Aesop had already foreseen that Han Xiao and the others would refuse to participate in his 'game'. The prophecy itself was vague because the future was full of uncertainties and could change at any time. If the future could not be changed, the prophecy would be meaningless. Generally, prophecies with no goal usually only led to a fog. A theme was needed for the ability to be activated, which would be the 'trigger' that would limit the future possibilities.

The more experienced the Oracle was, the more factors they would set up to limit the future. The variety of clues and mischievous arrangements that Aesop had left were all plots that he used to limit the possibilities.

The future was in the superposition state, and the 'trigger' could make the future 'collapse'. In simple terms, when people are not hungry, they could do all sorts of things, and when they were hungry, there was one action that would become determined—they would eat. Aesop deliberately left the trail for this purpose so that people who searched for him would follow the clues that he had left. If a bead on the ground was rolling in all directions, when the bead fell into a groove, it would only move back and forth. This meant that the 'future' turned from a free answer question to a multiple-choice question with limited options. Only in that way would his prophecy be able to see the future.

Prophecies could not see too far into the future and had no combat capability. The ability itself was not powerful, so it all depended on the user. Being an Oracle required intelligence!

At this time, Aesop had already purchased a seat on a long-haul flight. Even if he did not use his prophecy ability, he had already seen through Han Xiao's goal. It was nothing more than to stall for time so that when Ames arrived on Noriosse, he would have nowhere to run.

"Too young." Aesop thought that it was funny. With such an obvious intention, only a fool would not be able to see it. They refused his request, yet they thought that he would be stupid enough to stay on the planet. Why would he?

Putting himself in Han Xiao's shoes, Aesop felt that he would lie about agreeing to find the Heart of Crystal Fire in order to stall time, which would be at least better than rejecting it directly. However, no matter what Han Xiao chose, the result would be the same—Aesop had actually never planned to stay there. Even if Han Xiao had lied and agreed, he would still have left.

"If he agreed to my request, my following arrangements would get them into trouble. They would be chased off this planet by the Noriosse financial group. Even if they reject my request and intend to delay me, after I leave, Ames will also be unable to find me. She will be angry at this group officers who quit halfway and 'missed the golden opportunity', which will also give them a hard time.

"From the moment you got the clue I left from the intel organization, the result was already determined."

Under the mask of disguise, Aesop smiled. "You used my name; I give you a little punishment. Fair and square."

"Is that so?"

Suddenly, a man's voice came from behind, and a hand tapped Aesop's shoulder and stayed there.

Aesop's face suddenly changed. He froze and slowly turned around.

A stranger stood behind him. This man tore off an extremely thin mask on his face, exposing Han Xiao's face.

"Mister Aesop Hurricane, damn good morning to you." Han Xiao smiled.

"How did you know I'm here?" Aesop was shocked. His eyes changed slightly and flashed with wonder.

He did not ask why Han Xiao was here; it needed no explanation. He figured it out instantly the moment that he saw Han Xiao. He was puzzled by another question at this moment.

There were five harbors on Noriosse. How did he accurately find the correct one?

He might have heard from Jenny that this Black Star seemed to be an Oracle as well.

"Good question, allow me to introduce." Han Xiao pulled a man from the side, took off the mask on the face of the person, revealing the face of Feidin. He smiled and said, "This is my mascot."

"... You mean by luck?"

Aesop's face stiffened, and then he looked relieved. Oracles as skilled as him were very clear on one thing—there would never be a perfect plan. No matter how good the plan was, it would often be disrupted by accidents. Although luck was something very uncertain, the simplest thing was usually the most inexplicable.

Han Xiao had the Destiny's Child card, so he understood the mindset of Oracles and the so-called trigger, but this time, he did not use the Destiny's Child card as there was no need to.

When he refused Aesop's request, to his understanding of Aesop, he knew that Aesop could easily see through his 'intention'. Hence, only one choice was placed in front of Aesop. In order to avoid Ames, who was going to arrive, he had to take a spaceship and leave Noriosse. Therefore, the possibilities were narrowed. He just had to spread out across five harbors and wait, as Aesop would definitely pass by one of them.

As a result, the person in the dilemma became Aesop. If he did not leave, he would definitely be found. If he left, he might be found.

Hence, even if Aesop had foreseen this possibility, he would have no choice but to fall into this trap. Not to mention the fact that Aesop did not use his power due to the lack of a trigger.

Those who delved into logic tended to fall into a paradox that they themselves could not see. Aesop wanted Han Xiao to act while complying with his rules of the game, but Han Xiao turned it around and made his interlocked plan into a fair environment for the both of them to compete in their luck. Then, Han Xiao used his rich experience to beat him. Feidin could solve any and all difficulties involving luck.

Aesop's lousy disguise was good enough for the identity check at the harbor but not disguise veteran Han Xiao.

According to the normal way of thinking, if Aesop left Noriosse long ago right after he made the arrangements, the plan would have had no solution, meaning that he would be in an invincible position. However, Han Xiao had one of the biggest advantages—he knew Aesop's personality from his previous life. This ancient man had experienced too many things, so his personality was strange and abnormal.

Power? Not interesting. He had once served as the vice president of a star-class civilization.

Wealth? There was no meaning. Resources did not have a real owner, so wealth was only a false definition.

Beauty? Tired of it long ago. The species that he had mated with could circle a Fixed Star several times.

Strength? Experienced before. He had once erased the entire planet from the map with a horrifying weapon.

Aesop was really tired of living, and this was not derogatory but literal. His life was left with a few fun things—freedom, curiosity, and excitement!

So, he had become a treasure hunter who travelled everywhere with unknown whereabouts. He could only experience the feeling of being alive at the edge of danger. Hence, when he plotted and planned, Aesop would absolutely never hide behind the scenes. He would create a fair situation and let the opponent have the opportunity to taste the fruit of victory. To him, it was a dangerous game.

If he won, he would feel empty.

If he lost, he would rejoice.

He had lived too long and really become incomprehensible to ordinary people.

Aesop also took off the disguise, revealing his old appearance, and heartily laughed. "It seems that my apprentice found a powerful partner."

Han Xiao smiled as well. He showed no flaw on the surface, but he had other thoughts in his mind.

He was thinking of killing Aesop.

Aesop was such a powerful Oracle. Even if he was not his enemy, who could guarantee that he would not be a threat to him in the future?

Han Xiao was very clear about Aesop's ability; his power was prophecy, so his combat capability was almost equal to zero. As long as he seized this Oracle, killing him would not be much harder than killing a chicken.

This was a good opportunity to get rid of hidden dangers. He just had to tell Ames that he did not find her teacher and let Aesop be forever 'missing'.

So...

Before Ames arrives, should I...

Kill him‽

Han Xiao eyes flickered.

In his eyes, there was not a single person that had to die no matter what, and there was not a single person he must not kill no matter what.

Chapter 481: Thank You

Aesop coughed. "You've won this game, but I don't want to see Ames. Black star, can we discuss it?"

Han Xiao suppressed his murderous intent and said with surprise, "Do you not want to see your apprentice that much?"

"Back then, I only casually adopted a little girl, spent some time with her, and taught her the method to awaken her Super talent. How could I have known that she would go on to become a Beyond Grade A whose name has spread across an entire Star Field?" Aesop shook his head. "If only I'd known, I wouldn't have adopted her. With her strength, if she finds me, there definitely won't be any way for me to escape. Those kind of days without freedom will be the same as imprisonment. It brings me horror just thinking about it."

Han Xiao's mouth twitched. Casually adopting a little girl who turned out to be one of the strongest people many years later, why does this sound so familiar?

Furthermore, this old man looks so reluctant. Hey, you can show off, but don't go over the line, damn it!

Holding back the desire to criticize, Han Xiao asked, "So, why did you come back since you don't want to see her?"

Aesop did not possess the demeanor that one would expect from someone who was countless years old. Like a stubborn old man, he said, "The more she wants to find me, the more I want to linger before her eyes."

A horrible personality as always...

Han Xiao was speechless. In his previous life, Aesop had wandered everywhere and was a mystery shopkeeper in the players' eyes. But one day, he was dragged into a conflict between two Star System civilizations. As always, he carried out a 'game'. However, having walked along the shore for so long, it was inevitable that he would get his shoes wet one day. Aesop failed, and it cost him his life. He did not met Ames again. After a hundred years of searching, Ames only saw Aesop's tombstone in the end.

Ames did everything based on her mood, and she acted out of impulse. She vented her rage and smashed every planet in the territory of these two civilizations, including their mother planets, ending countless lives. The survivors not in the territory at that time filed a complaint to the three Universal Civilizations. Such a violent act severely violated the lawful accords, so Floating Dragon lost its privileges and was besieged by numerous armies.

At that time, a large number of players accepted missions and took part in the siege.

Countless battleships were destroyed in the battle, as was Floating Dragon Island. Although Ames did not die in the battle, she disappeared.

The renowned Beyond Grade A from the Shattered Star Ring was never seen again.

Of course, that all happened in a very late version.

Since Han Xiao had captured Aesop, if he let Ames meet Aesop, it would be something that had not happened in his previous life, so he did not know how it would turn out.

Nonetheless, the tragedies of two civilizations with trillions of civilians being slaughtered, Floating Dragon Island destroyed, and Ames being heavily injured should not happen again.

Never mind, I owe her a favor. I shall give him to Ames. Killing him will only cause unnecessary risks.

Shaking his head, Han Xiao kept his thoughts about killing Aesop to himself.

Aesop could only see into a small part of the future, but what he knew about was the overall trend!

There was no reason for him to be afraid!

Han Xiao placed his arms around Aesop's shoulder and whispered to Aesop's ear, "I refuse."

Aesop's expression stiffened. Why did he whisper then? It gave him false hope...

Han Xiao contacted Ames on his communicator. As soon as the image showed up, Ames saw Aesop, who was standing beside Han Xiao. Her beautiful eyes brightened as a tint of a smile appeared on her face.

"Aesop, my teacher, I've really missed you."

Aesop smiled bitterly. From Ames' tone, he could hear a strong sense of dissatisfaction. Even without using his foresight ability, he could tell that he was in a bad situation.

After hiding for so many years, who knew how much unhappiness Ames had suppressed; falling into her hands would be truly horrible.

Then, Ames turned to look at Han Xiao and said, "Wait for me, I'm almost there!"

The image turned black right after; she was very quick to act.

Aesop was frustrated. He turned to look at Han Xiao. "Won't you reconsider?"

"She has already seen you. Do you think I can possibly let you go?" Han Xiao smiled.

Not much later, Ames' spaceship arrived at the port. Han Xiao took Aesop to the pier, and Ames saw him as soon as she got off her spaceship. She walked over with a fearsome aura!

Han Xiao's hand that grabbed Aesop's shoulder clearly felt the old man's body shiver.

"Dragon Emperor‽"

At this moment, the pedestrians near the pier were in an uproar. With faces of horror, they hurried back far away. They had not expected one of the strongest people in the Shattered Star Ring to suddenly appear.

"Don't you have something to say to me?" Ames was expressionless.

Aesop sighed as if he accepted his fate. "Alright, I should have come back to see you long ago and shouldn't have hidden from you. Let's not stand here and let others watch, let's go."

As he was speaking, he walked up the gangway. Before entering the spacecraft, he looked back at Han Xiao, and a smile suddenly appeared on his face.

Ames was about to return to the ship, but she suddenly thought of something and turned around to look at Han Xiao.

She paused. With a serious and solemn tone, she said, "Thank you."

Han Xiao waved his hand. "It's a small matter. I'm just repaying my favor."

"No, I owe you."

Ames' tone was unquestionable. She suddenly hesitated before slowly reaching out. The soft black sleeves slid down her smooth arm, revealing her slender white palm, and she patted Han Xiao on his shoulder.

She was a neat freak and would never willingly touch others, but this time, she made an exception.

Although she looked calm on the surface, she was actually very happy, so she was very grateful to Han Xiao, who had captured Aesop. She knew how cunning Aesop was. She had caught wind of his whereabouts before, but she had ended up disappointed every time. This success surprised her.

After a short pat, Ames quickly pulled back her hand and turned around to go up the ship. Han Xiao, however, did not think it was unusual. At that moment, he thought of something and hastily used the blank Character Summon Card in his interface before Ames closed the door, generating her Character Summon Card.

Boom!

The ship unleashed a deep rumbling sound and left the dock along the track, soon disappearing.

Han Xiao stayed on the dock. He had just informed the others, so they heard the news and quickly gathered, watching the spaceship fly away.

"Black star, since we're done here, where are we going now?" Herlous asked.

"Let's take a break at Noriosse and leave tomorrow." Han Xiao turned to Wilsander and asked, "Do you want to stick around with us?"

"I'm not in a hurry to go back. Plus, it's too boring to stay on Floating Dragon Island. Hehe, it seems like I'll have to disturb you for some time." Wilsander gave his standard cheeky smile.

"As long as you don't spend my money, you can disturb us for as long as you want." Han Xiao shrugged.

This time, they heard a commotion from the direction of the hall. A group of superiors from Noriosse financial group had heard the news of Ames' arrival and hurried here. They did not dare neglect such an important person, but after picking up Aesop, Ames had left immediately. The whole process had only taken a few minutes, so these financial group superiors were too late.

Thus, the executives of the financial group approached Han Xiao and chatted with him enthusiastically with warm smiles on their faces.

The Dragon Emperor had left, but they would never go away with nothing, so they decided to form a relationship with Black Star and see if they could provide any help, showing the attitude of Noriosse.

Originally, when Han Xiao first arrived on Noriosse, those financial group executives had only told their employees to send a greeting. However, now that the Dragon Emperor had appeared, things were different. They felt that they had to personally come to say hello to show their sincerity. The attention that the financial group superiors paid Han Xiao rose many levels.

As they were talking, the sound of several footsteps came from not far away. The people subconsciously looked in that direction.

A group of Godorans in combat suits hurried through the hall, looking to have just arrived. The leader looked brave and extraordinary.

"Godorans? What are they doing here?" Han Xiao's eyes were also attracted. He curiously looked at the leader of the Godoran, and his expression suddenly changed.

He knew that person.

This was a Grade A Super!

On Ames' ship, Aesop stood before a porthole, silently looking at the distant Noriosse.

"What are you looking at?" Ames asked from behind.

Aesop stopped looking and smiled with satisfaction.

"You have a good officer. He's trustworthy."

"You mean Black Star?" Ames nodded. "He is indeed very capable. Didn't you meet him long ago? You even told him to send me a message."

Aesop shook his head and laughed.

"I'm old now. I almost forgot about that."

As he spoke, Aesop lowered his head, opened the communicator, and deleted a letter that had been set to send at a certain time. The receiver was shockingly Ames, whom he always blocked communication requests from.

Aesop shook his head.

"If it wasn't for you, I wouldn't have come to the Shattered Star Ring into this trap..."

Aesop knew Ames too well—capricious, arbitrary, not good at plotting. Just as Black Star had asked, if he did not want to be found by Ames, he could have hidden far away, so why did he have to return to Shattered Star Ring?

As for his motivation, of course, it was not to tease Ames. Although he was indeed tired of living, his taste was not that boring. His goal was surprisingly Han Xiao!

Someone had used his name to deceive Ames. What if this person had found Ames' weakness and deliberately used it to get close to her while harboring ulterior motives?

Aesop had been very worried about that.

No matter what kind of power Ames had, in his eyes, she would always be the little girl who needed someone to take care of.

Hence, he had returned to Shattered Star Ring, exposing his whereabouts and leading Ames' officers to track him down. If Han Xiao did not catch him, then this man was only so capable. If Han Xiao did catch him, Aesop would start the second round of his test. He had made the follow-up preparation long ago; he deliberately showed his prophecy ability while at the same time angering Han Xiao. If Black Star was really the Dragon Emperor's enemy, he would not allow such a dangerous enemy to live.

If Aesop died, that timed messages that he had set long ago would have reminded Ames of his death, and the culprit would have been the one who lied to her.

Aesop placed his own life, that of an old man, on the line and made a bet. If he died, Ames would not easily believe in others again, which he felt would be very worthwhile. After living for so long, the habit of looking for death had integrated into his blood—it would only make him feel thrilled and excited.

Although he looked like he did not care on the surface, he actually cared a lot about Ames. Aesop had no children, so Ames was like an adopted daughter to him.

Of course, Han Xiao did not know that his casual words to convince Ames back then on Floating Dragon Island would cause such a butterfly effect, leading the two of them who had never met each other in his previous life to meet for the first time, indirectly changing the fate of hundreds of trillions of people.

Black Star... Aesop thought, Very promising guy. If he lives for a thousand years like me, he will be a hundred times more horrifying than I am.

With his help, Ames will at least have an easier time...

Chapter 482: Trap

After helping Ames catch Aesop and completing the mission, Han Xiao had been in a good mood. However, when Han Xiao saw a bunch of Godora warriors rushing over, his mood plummeted.

He recognized the Godoran's battlesuits, and these warriors were not low-grade Observers. Instead, they were special forces that specialized in battle, and their leader was a Super who had been extremely famous in his previous life. In Version 2.0, this person had been the key figure in dealing with the mutation disaster on Planet Aquamarine. The majority of the battle quests that the players accepted from the Godoran camp had also been issued by him. He was like a commander level character and an important NPC to the players. Thus, Han Xiao was extremely familiar with him.

Nagakin, an officer of the War Bureau, Grade A Pugilist. He would only take action during important missions, and for him to appear on Noriosse, it meant that something important was about to unfold on Noriosse. A thought suddenly popped into his head, and Han Xiao immediately thought about the mixed blood Godoran that he had met a few days ago, Alvin.

The two should probably be related... Han Xiao thought to himself.

There was another strange sight that puzzled him. The Nagakin in front of him was majestic and full of valor. His strides were wide, and every step of his was taken with stability. In Han Xiao's memories, when the players of Planet Aquamarine first met Nagakin, he had been half crippled. Half of his face had been reduced to a skeleton, and not only was he disfigured, his left arm and both legs had turned into prosthetics. He had also needed numerous life support systems to be injected into his body in order for him to be alive.

It was less than a year away from Version 2.0.

As such, Nagakin must have been crippled during this period, but the exact time was not certain.

Han Xiao's eyes flashed, and he immediately sprang into action. He broke away from the upper echelons of Noriosse and stood in front of Nagakin.

"Who are you? Don't block the way." The Godoran warriors stopped, and Nagakin looked at Han Xiao with a frown.

Han Xiao introduced himself simply.

"Black Star? Oh, I've heard your name. You and some other mercenaries successfully destroyed a DarkStar mothership. Good job."

Nagakin nodded and did not take it to heart. A figure of his caliber would only be concerned about more important matters. He only knew about Han Xiao's name because his subordinate had mentioned it in passing. At that very moment, he was pushed for time, so he asked impatiently, "Why are you stopping us?"

"I only wanted to say hi. At the same time, I wanted to ask if you guys needed help." This was a common phrase that players used to start a conversation with NPCs. Han Xiao was also trying to see if he was able to receive a mission and understand the Godorans' reason for appearing there. He was lacking intel and did not know that DarkStar and Godora were having a confrontation on Noriosse. He only felt that something was strange.

Those warriors were the reinforcements sent by Godora, and their mission was to rescue Alvin. Over the past few days, two of Alvin's doppelgangers had been captured, and the situation did not allow a single second's delay. From Alvin's doppelganger, they had found out that the strongest individual in the squad chasing after Alvin was a grade B Super called Forsyth. As such, Godora had sent out Nagakin, who was the nearest to the location, and felt that it was sufficient to take care of the enemy.

Nagakin felt that he did not need any help and that he was sufficient to take care of the enemy. As such, he casually replied, "We do not need your help. I'm pushed for time and will take my leave now."

After finishing his sentence, Nagakin moved past Han Xiao and led his men away.

Studying the backs of those Godorans, Han Xiao stroked his chin and muttered to himself, "Tsk, I wasn't able to activate a mission. For a Calamity Grade Super to take action personally, it's probably a risky mission."

Since Nagakin did not welcome outsiders, Han Xiao would forget about the matter. He would not lower himself and continue sticking to them uninvited.

He then opened the interface. After obtaining the Ames Character Summon Card, he had not checked its effects yet.

[Character Summon Card—Ames]

Force Field—Gaze of the Dragon: Compress the medium within a certain area (effective for all states of matter) and target a single character. The targeted character will fall into a [Trapped] status. For every 100 points of STR the target has, 1s of control time will be reduced.

Basic control time: 18s

Usages: 0/1

Han Xiao felt that the strong control effect was still acceptable. Ames had many different skills, and at her level, almost seventy percent of her skills were useful. While he did not obtain an attack skill, a control skill was more flexible and had its own advantages.

He then left the port and returned to land. After renting a temporary stronghold, he was prepared to spend rest a few days there. At the same time, he would purchase some resources. Noriosse was home to many shops, and he intended to strengthen his war machinery. Two High-End Knowledges and his many Advanced Knowledges gave him the option to obtain better blueprints, and it was sufficient for him to have an all-round upgrade. He still had more than twenty million experience points, and as long as he spent it sparingly, it would be sufficient for him to obtain enough blueprints.

Just when everyone was resting, a storm exploded.

...

Nagakin took dozens of Godoran warriors in aircrafts and arrived at a skyscraper at the periphery of Noriosse's City 4. Tall buildings filled the district, and the magnetic floating bus station that connected the cities was not too far away.

According to Alvin's reports, the temporary base of DarkStar's forces was on the eightieth story of the skyscraper, and it was located right at the center of the building.

Alvin's main body had always been in contact with the reinforcements from Godora, and he used his doppelganger to observe the members of DarkStar to provide Nagakin with information. His request was for Nagakin to get rid of all the DarkStar forces chasing him before his main body would appear. He was extremely cautious.

"The enemy's forces are inside. We will first destroy their base before dealing with those DarkStar members operating on the outside to prevent us from alerting the enemy. Currently, the enemy's base is unaware of our arrival, and we have an advantage in terms of intel. Attack with me!"

The aircrafts ascended slowly and approached their target building. Nagakin's gaze was solemn as he clenched his fists. A golden flame began to flow down his arm as though it was liquid.

His fist smashed onto the outer wall of the building.

Boom!

The next instant, a white shockwave was sent out in all directions!

All the glass in this building was shattered!

The might of his fist shot through the entire eightieth floor, and a large hole could be seen on both sides of the building. The entire building began to let out unsteady creaks, and the middle of the building bent slightly like a wooden pole that was almost smashed in half!

Not to mention a building, it was a piece of cake for a Calamity Grade Pugilist to destroy even a battleship. As long as he had enough time, he could even turn into an excavator and change the landscape of the entire planet.

After destroying the building with a single punch, Nagakin charged in with his subordinates and attacked the enemy base. Upon entry, he immediately spotted Forsyth and the others, who were in a daze.

Nagakin made a few hand signals and the Godoran warriors surrounded Forsyth's troops. He then said in a deep voice, "I am Nagakin from Godora's War Bureau. All of you are surrounded. Drop you weapons and surrender now. I will send all of you to Rainbow Prison."

The building was shaking unsteadily, and Forsyth finally managed to steady himself. Revealing a malevolent smile, he chuckled as though his prey had fallen into his trap. "It seems like we've caught a big fish. Nagakin, look around you. Who do you think is surrounded?"

Two powerful auras exploded and trapped Nagakin's troops in the middle.

Nagakin hurriedly turned around only to see Anur and Ember glaring at him.

The intense killing intent seemed to have frozen the space around him.

"Why are there two Calamity Grade Supers‽ There is an error in our intelligence!" Nagakin's face changed drastically.

Alvin's intel had stated that the strongest person pursuing him was a Grade B Super. For Godora to send out a Grade A Super, it could be considered a foolproof plan. With Nagakin taking action, even if a Grade A Super was hiding amid the enemy's ranks, he would still be able to fight the other party equally. However, Godora could never have expected that DarkStar would actually send out two Calamity Grade Supers to kill a single traitor. This was akin to killing a chicken with an ox's blade. This was the trap that DarkStar had set.

Anur and Ember did not appear in front of Alvin's doppelganger, and Forsyth had acted as the leader. As such, Alvin had believed that there were no Calamity Grade Supers in the team. DarkStar had already predicted that Godora would send reinforcements and intentionally tricked Alvin into thinking that there were no Grade A Supers. They had predicted that there would be a single Grade A Super in the reinforcements at most, and this Grade A Super would become Anur and Ember's prey!

DarkStar did not only want to chase their traitor down. They had even laid a trap to make Godora lose one of their top fighters!

This was the reason for Anur and Ember to take action together. Godora had fallen for DarkStar's trap.

The Godoran warriors present felt a chill run down their spines, and their backs were drenched with cold sweat. The immense pressure from facing two powerful enemies had almost caused their hearts to stop beating. They were extremely anxious and did not even know which side they should focus on defending.

Nagakin's face was solemn, and he knew that it would be difficult for him to escape alive. Taking in a deep breath...

"We will die today..."

Hu!

The Pugilist's flames covered his entire body, and the aura exploding out of his body matched Anur and Ember's auras. He then got into his fighting stance, and a resolute gaze could be seen in his eyes. Gritting his teeth, he let out a deep roar.

"Before we die, let's fight!"

Chapter 483: Seeking Aid and Recruitment

In the hall of their temporary base, everyone was currently busy with their own things. All of a sudden, the image on the television screen flashed, and the news was suddenly broadcast.

"Noriosse emergency report. Ten minutes ago, a building in the periphery of City 4 was attacked, and three streets were completely destroyed. The bus station is completely crippled, and the number of casualties is being calculated. According to initial analysis, the cause of the destruction is a fight between Supers. More details will be released after further investigation. The Public Security Office is already investigating the matter. Now showing the scene of the location..."

This news drew everyone's attention. Sylvia immediately went to knock on the machinery modification room and called Han Xiao out to watch the television.

The news displayed scenes of the location. A few dozen tall buildings had collapsed and been reduced to rubble. Just ten minutes earlier, that had still been an extremely prosperous location, but the entire place had been destroyed with thick, black smoke billowing. The aircrafts of the Public Security Office were flying around, trying to save as many casualties as possible. The entire place was filled with noise as corpse after corpse was bagged up before being thrown aside.

"That explains the tremors. I thought that it was an earthquake," the oldest Volga brother said.

Wilsander was using a brush to clean his wings, and he asked with a shrug, "Are they fighting a war?"

"For them to create such extensive destruction in such a short time, it is probably a battle between Calamity Grade Supers," Han Xiao said with a deep tone.

He immediately thought about Nagakin. Considering when he had met Nagakin, he felt that it was extremely possible.

However, this had nothing to do with him. He had not activated any missions from Nagakin, and since there were no benefits, Han Xiao did not care about the matter.

Beep beep!

Right at that moment, his communicator rang; an unknown number was calling him. Han Xiao accepted the call.

The next moment, Nagakin's figure appeared on the screen. He was breathing heavily, and his entire body was covered in blood and wounds. He was obviously in an extremely pathetic state.

"Black Star... please help me," Nagakin said with grit teeth.

...

Just a while ago, Nagakin had met the ambush of DarkStar, and after an intense battle, three streets had been destroyed with all his elite warriors dead. That foreign Calamity Grade Super had reduced all of them to ash in a single instant. They could not even let out a single cry for help.

Those were his subordinate who had accompanied him into battle for many years, and they had all been wiped out easily. Nagakin was furious but had no choice but to force himself to remain calm and face the two experts in front of him.

While he was the only one left, Nagakin did not entertain the thought of retreating. As long as he could exchange his life for one of his opponents' lives, it would not be a complete loss.

There was also a divide between Calamity Grade Supers. Nagakin's strength was not superior to Anur or Ember, and he was at a clear disadvantage. Both of his opponents were Espers who were extremely difficult to deal with. In just a short exchange, he was already injured all over.

The intense battle between them had quickly drawn the attention of the Public Security Office, and they arrived swiftly. Anur had originally intended to continue chasing, but after considering for a moment, he had decided to make a strategic retreat as he did not want to end up being chased by those from the Public Security Office. The result of the ambush was not up to his expectations. He had originally wanted to kill Godora's Grade A Super quickly, but Nagakin was a Pugilist with a powerful physique and had only been severely injured.

If not for Nagakin having a powerful physique, he would probably have died.

Dragging his severely injured body away from the battlefield, Nagakin did not immediately tend to his wounds. Instead, he contacted the headquarters and reported the entire event while bearing the pain. Godora's War Bureau was shocked and ordered Nagakin to wait for his orders with the priority being the preservation of his life.

He requested aid from the headquarters, but travelling required time, so it would be impossible for them to send anyone in time. Giving up and retreating had never been part of his vocabulary. Even if he was alone, he would stop DarkStar from accomplishing their objective.

Just when he was considering killing his way back, Nagakin suddenly thought of Black Star, who he had met at the port.

Perhaps only mercenaries could help him.

Noriosse was located far away, and there were few mercenary groups operating in that region. Currently, the Black Star Mercenary Group was probably the only mercenary group around, and he could only seek their help.

He had rejected Han Xiao's help just a while back but had no choice but to seek help now. This was far too embarrassing, and Nagakin had never imagined that such a scenario would occur. However, he could only grit his teeth and contact Han Xiao. For his mission, casting aside his pride was not a problem at all.

"Nagakin?" Han Xiao had a weird look on his face. His guess was right. Nagakin was related to the news shown on the television, and he had already been severely injured by an unknown enemy. The help that Nagakin was requesting was obviously related to this matter. With none of his subordinates in sight, they had probably all been wiped out, and thus, Nagakin had no choice but to seek help from mercenaries.

With just a short pause, Han Xiao came up with a rough idea of what had happened. He then recalled Nagakin's crippled appearance, but after glancing at Nagakin's body once, while Nagakin was covered in blood all over, his limbs were all still intact.

"I have a mission to fetch a character who betrayed DarkStar from Noriosse. His name is Alvin, and DarkStar sent forces to chase after him. The other party has two Grade A Supers, and I fell into their ambush..."

Nagakin described the situation honestly.

While he knew that revealing the truth about two Grade A Supers might cause Han Xiao to act warily and not help him, Nagakin would never hide the strength of his enemies and deceive mercenaries. He was an extremely straightforward person, and even if he knew that the mercenaries might reject him, he would still tell the truth.

Han Xiao was immediately enlightened. When he met Alvin before, he had already been somewhat suspicious but had no intel. This matter was really related to DarkStar.

"Who are the two Grade A Supers of DarkStar?"

"I am not sure." Nagakin shook his head.

"What are their abilities?"

"One of them is able to reduce the human body to ash and can control a large amount of dust to form various weapons. If I did not raise my defenses with my energy, he would have been able to slowly peel away my flesh..."

A cold glow flashed through Han Xiao's eyes, and he said, "Carbon element control, Ember!"

He had originally thought that this fellow had died in the explosion of the battleship, but never had he expected that Ember had actually escaped. Furthermore, he had even entered the Calamity Grade. When he fought Ember back on Floating Dragon Island, Ember had already been B+ Grade and far stronger than him. If not for his talent restricting the trump card of Ember, it would have been impossible for him to fight Ember to a draw.

Ember was capable of instantly wiping out any carbon-based life form, and his ability was extremely difficult to deal with. It was like a divine AOE skill. Only Aroshia and himself were immune to Ember. Wilsander was a mixed blood demon, and his body constitution was unknown. If he was not carbon based, perhaps he would be able to escape the outcome of being instantly wiped out.

However, after Ember reached Grade A, his Esper abilities might have new ways to be used. Even his ordinary attacks would be much more powerful than before.

"What are the abilities of the other one?" Han Xiao asked.

"He is a shapeshifting Esper. He can change into a strange flying creature roughly four to five meters tall. It seems as though he has the ability to control the flow of air. He is extremely fast, and it is difficult to follow him with the naked eye. When he is flying, wind pressure is generated around him. Not only is it able to form a protective shield, it is able to provide a certain degree of invisibility. It seems as though he is using a trick to bend the light rays. The faster he flies, the stronger the wind pressure generated, and everywhere he passes is destroyed by the wind pressure. He is just like a wind pressure cannon."

"Shapeshifting... wind pressure..." Han Xiao's mouth contorted. "Could he be the Wind Demon Anur?"

DarkStar had a limited number of Grade A Supers, and according to the abilities that they had displayed, Han Xiao was able to guess their identities. Anur was an old member and a powerhouse of DarkStar who was extremely difficult to deal with. After his transformation, not only would his speed increase, if he flew a few times around the planet, the accumulated wind pressure would form a cyclone gigantic enough to flatten the entire planet's surface.

The two of them were extremely difficult to deal with. Before Version 2.0, Han Xiao did not really want to provoke DarkStar. However, this was a good opportunity for him to get closer to a Grade A Super from Godora and a channel for him to get in contact with the upper echelons of Godora. With Nagakin around, it would be much easier for him to gain trust when he handed over the mutation source in the future, and it would be more convenient for him to discuss benefits.

Nagakin bit his lips as he waited for Han Xiao's response. He silently prayed that Han Xiao would not reject him—Han Xiao seemed like his last chance.

After a long while, Han Xiao shook his head. "It is too dangerous to fight two Grade A Supers..."

Nagakin's expression froze. While he had expected the outcome, he was still a little disappointed.

"However, your mission isn't to kill the both of them, right?" Han Xiao asked. "As long as Alvin is able to leave Noriosse alive, your mission will be completed. The problem now is that your Godoran reinforcements require time to arrive. Thus, we only need to stall for time and help Alvin escape from DarkStar. If this is the case, I can try helping you."

Nagakin's eyes lit up—he was overjoyed.

At that moment, a new mission was shown on Han Xiao's interface.

Nagakin's Request

Mission Introduction: You have agreed to help Nagakin. His mission is to save a DarkStar traitor.

Mission Requirements: 1. Aid Alvin in hiding until Godora's troops arrive. 2. Kill all of the pursuing DarkStar forces. (Completing one of the two requirements would complete the mission)

Failure Conditions: 1. Alvin's death. 2. Nagakin's death.

Rewards: 5,800,000 Experience, 240,000 Enas, +850 Relationship with Godora Faction, +30 Alvin Favorability, +30 Nagakin Favorability

There are two mission requirements. It seems like it will be easier to stall for time, Han Xiao thought to himself. While it was more straightforward to defeat the enemy, the other party had two Calamity Grade Supers.

Han Xiao had three Main Storyline missions, and one of them was [Godora's Ally]. The mission requirements were plenty, and Anur and Ember were all included on the hit list. While the reward for killing them was high, Han Xiao only thought about it and did not think that that it was possible for him to accomplish it.

Just when Nagakin was about to ask how they should work together, Han Xiao interrupted him.

"Just the few of us will be far too little manpower. Let me find more manpower for you."

He then turned around to Herlous. "Go through the Mercenary Alliance and issue a recruitment notice near Noriosse. The target will be all the mercenaries in the vicinity. As long as they can rush over in time, we want them all. As many as possible."

"What should we write for the person issuing the mission?" Herlous asked. "Nagakin or Godora?"

"No, their names aren't the best option." Han Xiao shook his head. "Use my name."

Chapter 484: Chaotic Entry

The mercenaries in the Shattered Star Ring were extremely active. Even in the region of Noriosse, there were many active mercenaries, but the majority of them were second or third grade mercenaries. Han Xiao issued a recruitment notice through the Mercenary Alliance, and this recruitment notice quickly spread through the Noriosse mercenary groups.

Majority of the mercenaries had the same two reactions—surprised and curious.

In the past year, Han Xiao had completed plenty of missions, and because of the backing of Floating Dragon, he had built up a large network consisting mainly of large mercenary groups including the likes of top-notch armies such as Blades, Purple Gold, and Sky Ring.

While Black Star's position in the mercenary world of Shattered Star Ring was not considered top notch, he was considered a first-rate small mercenary group. Many mercenaries wanted to build a relationship with Black Star and tap into his connections to gain better missions. After all, the rich employers usually wanted to hire the best mercenaries, and the Mercenary Alliance would only issue these missions to the lower grade mercenaries if the large armies did not accept them. The people at the top ate meat while those below drank the soup. This was pretty much the situation everywhere.

As such, the moment that Han Xiao posted a recruitment notice, countless respondents applied, and he activated at least half of the mercenaries in the Noriosse region.

The gathering location was extremely crowded, and everyone was packed like sardines. The colorful mercenaries squeezed together and chatted with each other as they waited for the appearance of their employer.

Clap clap...

At the very front of the group, a clapping sound could be heard, and everyone turned to take a look. Seeing the legendary Black Star before them, the noisy crowd slowly became silent.

Their gazes were all fixed on Han Xiao as they sized him up from head to toe. They were all interested in Han Xiao's connections but did not think too highly of his personal strength. The majority of the mercenaries were wild and untamed characters. The way they saw it, Black Star was not any much more powerful than them. He was only lucky enough to gain the recognition of Ames.

Han Xiao was unmoved, and he said emotionlessly, "Everyone, I am the one who issued the recruitment notice, and I believe that all of you should recognize me. I shall not introduce myself, and since we are all mercenaries, I shall skip the pleasantries. I received a difficult mission with bountiful rewards, and I require more manpower. I hired all of you to find partners to complete the mission together. You can treat me as a middleman, and the details of the mission shall be explained by the employer."

Nagakin made his entrance and described the situation honestly.

Very quickly, the mercenaries below broke out in a large commotion.

Many of them were thoroughly frightened by the two Calamity Grade Supers and backed out immediately. At the same time, they stared at Han Xiao in disbelief as though they were looking at a dead man.

You actually accepted a mission that requires you to face two Grade A enemies? Have you seen how powerful Calamity Grade Supers are‽

Don't drag me down if you want to die!

The war between DarkStar and Godora was known to everyone in the Shattered Star Ring, but the majority of the mercenaries kept their distance from the battle and were not willing to get involved.

"Our mission isn't to fight the enemy, but there will be some risks," Han Xiao said in a deep voice. "If any of you aren't willing to accept the mission, you may leave now. For those who stay behind, after this mission is over, I will sign a cooperation contract with all of you to enjoy my resources."

As everyone heard that, many of them fell into a dilemma. If they could cooperate with Black Star, they would have the chance to get better employers. It was like starting a company. Them running around to find odd jobs definitely could not be compared to working together with a large organization and easily enjoying jobs.

Many mercenaries did not dare take the risk and took their leave. The crowd began to thin, and Han Xiao did not stop them.

Only a hundred odd people were left behind. They were the mercenaries who were willing to take the risk.

Phillip read out their information, and Han Xiao viewed it once.

"Three mercenary groups, seventeen lone mercenaries. There are four Grade B Supers and the rest are Grade Cs. This is better than my expectations." Han Xiao nodded. Because of the limited time, he did not dare wait too long, and it was not too bad for him to hire this bunch of mercenaries.

Han Xiao got the mercenaries to rest and reorganize themselves as Nagakin walked over.

"What are you planning to do?" Nagakin asked. The day before, he had just met Han Xiao, and meeting him again that day, he felt a little embarrassed. As a Calamity Grade Super, he actually had to rely on a bunch of mercenaries. This was truly an embarrassing mark on his record.

However, he quickly shook away such useless emotions and focused on the mission at hand. While he did not understand Black Star much, it did not stop him from treating Han Xiao as an ally.

"We aren't the most anxious ones now; DarkStar are," Han Xiao mused. "With Anur and Ember's ambush failing, they know that Godora will definitely send out fresh reinforcements. Thus, they will try to capture Alvin as quickly as possible, so we have to try and interrupt their search.

"Alvin's main body has remained in hiding, and he didn't dare to reveal himself. Thus, it wasn't possible to take him away from Noriosse. Furthermore, there may be many DarkStar battleships hiding in Noriosse's vicinity to block all routes out."

Based on the present circumstances, they had to first contact Alvin before they could formulate a plan. Nagakin took out his encoded communicator.

"Nagakin? Weren't you defeated?" Alvin's voice sounded from the communicator, but there was no image displayed. In order to prevent anyone from finding his location, Alvin did not turn on his image display.

"Your intel was wrong, and DarkStar sent out two Calamity Grade Supers. I survived and found some helpers. We will help you escape from DarkStar's pursuit, and new reinforcements are on the way. As long as we can stall for enough time, DarkStar will have no choice but to retreat. You will be safer if you accept our protection. Where are you hiding?"

"I do not need your protection; my main body is extremely safe. You have already lost once, and if it wasn't for my cautiousness, I would have been caught. I would rather believe in myself. I have three doppelgangers in DarkStar's hands, and they aren't able to return to my main body. I have to suffer the pain from their torture every day, and only a single doppelganger of mine is able to move about freely. If you really want to help me, protect my doppelganger. He is still being followed by the enemy..."

Alvin hung up, and Nagakin frowned, feeling pretty helpless. If he could not protect the main body, whether or not the main body was found would be up to the heavens' will.

Han Xiao smiled and said, "DarkStar obtained three doppelgangers, and the doppelgangers will die if they are too far away from the main body. As long as split the main body up in three different directions, it will be easy for them to pinpoint the region that the main body is in. With some simple calculations, they will then be able to determine the center of the region. Thus, Alvin will not foolishly stay in one place."

"There is one more thing," Nagakin said with concern. "For us to recruit mercenaries openly, DarkStar will probably receive news about it, and they won't sit still without doing anything."

"Hmm, I have a guess as to what they will do. It seems like we will have to take some risks."

Han Xiao stroked his chin and decided to mess up this storm midway. Apart from the plentiful reward, this was also a good way for him to contact the upper echelons of Godora. He was pretty tanky, and he would be able to exchange a few blows with Grade A Supers. Retreating with his life definitely would not be a problem, and he did not have to be as cautious as before. With the advantage of understanding his enemy, there was no need for him to be anxious. If his opponent was Ember, he felt that he would be able to last a long time.

Because of the destruction caused by the battle between the Grade A Supers, DarkStar decided to change to a new secret base to discuss their next move. Anur felt that it was a waste that they had not been able to kill Nagakin, and he knew that Nagakin would have called for more reinforcements. Thus, they needed to seize every second.

At that moment, the troops on the outside was spying on Alvin's final doppelganger. Without daring to delay any further, Anur sent out all of his men, preparing to capture the final doppelganger.

However, before they could, the DarkStar troops received new intel. Nagakin had found some helpers—the Black Star Mercenary Group.

"Nagakin still isn't giving up, and he thinks that he can face the two of us alone?" Anur's expression was dark, and he revealed a sneer. "Since he isn't willing to hide obediently, we will use the opportunity to kill him."

He had originally thought that Nagakin would not dare reveal himself again after being ambushed by the two of them. Now that he had a chance to kill Nagakin, Anur was naturally overjoyed.

In truth, in Han Xiao's previous life, when Nagakin was ambushed, he did not suffer any severe injuries as well. However, he refused to give up on the mission, and even without any reinforcements, he had faced the two DarkStar Supers alone, eventually being crippled. At the same time, the Calamity Grade Super who participated in this battle was not Ember. In Han Xiao's previous life, Ember had not been forced to enter seclusion, so he had entered the Calamity Grade far later.

A large reason was because Han Xiao had caused the butterfly effect... or perhaps it was because Han Xiao served as a great motivator for Ember.

"So what if he's found a bunch of mercenaries? What can they do? They are no more than a bunch of weaklings." Anur was completely unconcerned. Only an elite army like Blades or Sky Ring was worth his attention.

Ember's gaze turned cold.

"Black Star again... I have given him a chance already."

Ember no longer placed Han Xiao in his sights, but since Black Star wanted to interfere with his mission, he had to wipe out all obstructions.

With the threat of Floating Dragon, Ember had not decided if he wanted to get rid of Black Star. However, he had to wipe out all of his companions at the very least and let Black Star know the price of provoking DarkStar.

While Black Star had some talent to be immune toward his abilities, Black Star's companions were not immune. Ember could still remember that he had managed to rip off the arm of one of Han Xiao's subordinates previously.

If you want to interfere in matters that you shouldn't, you will also place your life at risk.

Anur looked at the intel. "None of these mercenaries can be kept. I don't want any accidents to happen."

"You can take people to catch the doppelganger; I alone will be sufficient to get rid of the mercenaries." Ember stood up. "With my abilities, I will crush them all in less than a minute. I will meet up with you after taking care of this matter."

Chapter 485: The Gangster Mechanic

Ta, ta, ta!

Alvin escaped hurriedly. He was the final doppelganger left on the surface, and DarkStar's pursuing forces followed behind him like parasites. The one chasing after him was a Grade B Super called Sherman, the vice-captain of Forsyth's squad.

He had already noticed that DarkStar was getting ready to take action and had informed Nagakin and the others to request reinforcements. However, reinforcements still had not arrived, so Alvin was getting anxious.

Bang!

A thick light cannon pierced through the walls and smashed into Alvin's body. A magical shield appeared with ripples on it and blocked the damage before exploding in the next instant. Alvin was sent flying by the shockwave and rolled a couple of meters out.

Not too far away from him, a short dwarf-like man walked over wearing a pair of targeting goggles. He was dressed in a gray mechanical suit and held onto a gigantic cannon almost the size of his body. The design of the cannon was complicated with an extremely thick barrel. Apart from the main cannon, there were a couple of subsidiary cannons, and it was obvious that this was a multipurpose firearm.

This person was Sherman. It is said that he had the bloodline of the dwarfs and was a Cannon Master.

"I only have three protective talismans left, and I wouldn't be able to escape far. If the reinforcements do not arrive, I will be finished for sure. Those from DarkStar definitely won't show any mercy to me..." Alvin's face turned solemn; he knew that things were bad.

Sherman remained expressionless, and he pointed his cannon at Alvin, who was trying to crawl back up. "Don't move. Unless you find your legs too long."

Before he could even finish his sentence, the sound of something descending from above could be heard. Looking up, he saw someone weaving through the gaps of the buildings nimbly, dressed in a mechanical suit that looked like the armor of a knight. The white cape on his shoulders fluttered in the wind, and he approached Sherman at high speed. With a Battleship Slicing Blade that was a couple of meters long, it could only be Herlous.

Without saying a single word, Sherman raised his cannon and fired.

Boom boom boom!

Wave after wave of large light balls assaulted him. Herlous' eyes were extremely sharp, and he cleaved apart the ball of lights before they could even reach him.

Weaving through the balls of exploding cannon fire, Herlous cleaved his blade down at Sherman's head right before he reached the ground. However, Sherman had already foreseen this attack and avoided it.

Boom!

This attack landed on the ground, and a long ditch was created with silvery flames spewing out like lava. The cracks on the ground then extended out a few dozen meters.

"Reinforcements?" Sherman was sent flying by the shockwave of the attack and was half kneeling on the ground. Licking his lips, he could taste the slight metallic taste of blood, and his killing intent burst out.

At that moment, all of the hired mercenaries also appeared and surrounded Alvin to protect him. Alvin could finally heave a sigh of relief.

Reinforcements are finally here.

Over a hundred mercenaries glared at him fiercely, but Sherman was not anxious in the slightest. He pointed his finger at Herlous, who caused him to suffer a small loss, and pointed his finger at his head like a gun before 'firing'. He obviously meant that he had his eyes on Herlous.

The next moment, the members of DarkStar arrived as well. They did not lose in numbers at all and had even more elites. Anur walked out from the crowd and said with a deep voice, "Godoran, don't hide in a corner. You cannot escape from my senses."

Hearing that, Nagakin walked out, and the two powerhouses glared at each other in a faceoff. Nagakin's expression was solemn as he asked, "Where's the other one?"

Anur did not reply, and his gaze swept past the mercenaries. Counting the number of mercenaries present, he began to frown. Almost all of the hired mercenaries were there, and the enemy's camp should be empty. He knew that Ember would definitely return empty handed. However, that did not matter; Ember would not need much time to return, and they would be able to form a pincer attack to cut off all paths of retreat.

Since they were enemies, neither party spoke about their plans. Glaring at each other without a word, the situation was extremely tense.

With a single command, the killing began.

The battle had erupted!

Siii...

Anur's body swelled up, and he turned into a strange looking creature in the blink of an eye. His body was four to five meters tall with an inverted triangle as the head. His body was that of a streamlined beast with thick skin and small little holes all over. Those holes were the key to controlling the wind pressure. A long tail trailed behind the body, and his limbs turned into powerful claws. Eight strange, dog-ear-like bones could be seen on his back with its appearance looking a little like a pair of winds. However, it was a special organ like a tube for it to shoot out air. It extended out from Anur's ribs and allowed the high-pressure gas to cycle between the inside of his body and the atmosphere on the outside. It also ensured a balance of pressure on the inside and outside of the body to protect the body under high speed.

This was what Anur looked like after its transformation. His nickname was Wind Demon, and he had the special ability to control the flow of air.

Bang!

Anur's eight tubes spat out high-pressure gas, and he sped up rapidly. In the blink of an eye, he covered the distance of a few hundred meters and clashed together with Nagakin.

With him as the center, to his left and right were formless wind pressure cannons. The usually gentle air had been transformed into a powerful shockwave and decimated everything in its way.

Boom!

Wherever the wind pressure cannon passed by, the ground would crack, and the windows on the buildings to the side would be shattered. Everyone present felt that it was becoming difficult to breathe as though they were in the middle of a storm.

Nagakin broke through the wind barrier, and his fist smashed squarely onto Anur's body. His golden flames clashed straight on with the formless wind pressure, and both of them were sent flying in two different directions. Wherever they landed, a gray cloud of dust would be kicked up, and a circular crater would form.

By the time he raised his head again, Anur's figure had already disappeared, and only the violent winds were left behind. Nagakin had witnessed this ability before. The little holes on Anur's body would control the air surrounding him to coat his entire body like a shield. He would then use some unknown method to absorb the light rays and make sure that his body was no longer reflecting any light. As such, Anur's body could no longer be seen.

The two Calamity Grade Supers had to restrain each other. If not, the others fighting by the side would be in danger. Just a single Anur forced Nagakin to use all of his strength. If there was another Calamity Grade Super, he would be dead for sure.

Black Star said that the enemy will probably split up their forces. One of the Calamity Grade Supers will probably charge into our base alone. Black Star chose to stay behind to restrain the enemy. Only if we can hold down that Calamity Grade Super will we have a chance to save Alvin.

However, he is only a Grade B Super, and the Calamity Grade is too dangerous to him. Can he really do it?

Nagakin was worried.

...

At the same time, Ember walked into the mercenaries' base and was already prepared to unleash a massacre. However, the place was covered in darkness, and there was not a single person inside.

"Everyone abandoned the base and took action with the Godoran? It seems like this was a wasted trip. I'd better regroup with Anur."

Ember was expressionless. Just when he was about to turn around and leave, the lights lit up in the base.

"Don't go. I have been waiting for a long time."

Ember's eyes narrowed.

I know this voice.

He looked up and looked at the camera in the corner.

"Black Star?"

"Ember—this is the nickname that DarkStar gave you, but you do not have a real name. When you were very little, you were accepted by DarkStar. They were interested in your talent, and they treated you like a weapon, forcing you through endless strict training. You are not a Godoran, but you were brainwashed with a hatred that does not belong to you. DarkStar groomed your loyalty, but you are no more than a useful tool in their eyes. Your beliefs are completely meaningless because those aren't your true thoughts."

Han Xiao narrated slowly. Because of the information from his previous life, he understood Ember's life story. While he had killed many and was extremely hateful, he was also extremely pitiful.

If he had not been groomed by DarkStar from a young age but led a normal life, he would not have been the infamous Ember. He might have had his own name and would not have given his all only to be treated like a weapon and tool.

Ember clenched his fists tightly before releasing them slowly. He did not have any intention to argue with Han Xiao. "All of the other mercenaries have left? Why are you the only one left behind?"

"To wait for you of course."

Ka-cha.

A metal door opened, and Han Xiao walked out with his gaze clashing with Ember.

Sparks flew.

DarkStar had sent out two Calamity Grade Supers, and Han Xiao had guessed that they would try to fully utilize their advantage by sending one of them out alone. On a strategic level, this will allow them to be more agile. Thankfully, he had guessed correctly, and there was indeed a Calamity Grade Super who worked alone with his strength.

During the recruitment, Han Xiao knew that he would not be able to hide the recruitment from DarkStar. If the enemy wanted to barge into their camp alone, the most likely person to come would be Ember because his ability was the most suited for a group battle. All carbon element beings that were weaker than him would essentially be killed instantly. As such, Han Xiao got the majority of the mercenaries to aid Nagakin in saving Alvin. They would only be committing suicide if they stayed behind.

Only he would be able to restrain Ember. The longer he could restrain Ember, the higher the chances of Nagakin rescuing Alvin.

If he wanted to fight a battle of attrition, Han Xiao was extremely confident.

"Wait for me?" Ember's expression was odd. "You want to hold me back alone?"

"Not really alone." Han Xiao shrugged his shoulders. By his side, a light flashed, and Aroshia drifted beside him. Apart from her, there were another few useless mercenaries in another monitoring room with their attention focused on the screen.

Han Xiao had left them behind on purpose, and their mission was to ignite the explosives that were laid all around the building to hold Ember down. At that moment, their palms were completely soaked in sweat and their breathing heavy. The look of nervousness could be seen all over their faces.

It was understandable for them to be nervous. After all, the figure in the surveillance image was a Calamity Grade Super. If they had been standing in Han Xiao's position, they probably would not even have been able to speak fluently. They could not help but feel nervous for Han Xiao.

The moment the enemy takes action, Black Star will be in danger.

If Black Star dies, we won't be able to benefit from his connections.

Ember raised his finger and found out that there was no reaction from Aroshia when he used his Esper abilities. He then shook his head and said, "It turns out your trump card is this energy lifeform. Do you think that you can stop me like that?"

Han Xiao twiddled a compressed orb and said with a smile, "We never decided the victor in our previous battle. Could it be that you are afraid?"

As Ember heard that, he could not help but chuckle. He had already entered the next grade and was no longer the same as before. He did not understand where Han Xiao's confidence came from. Could it be that Han Xiao thought that he was the same as before?

"Overestimating yourself." Ember's tone became cold. "Even though the rest aren't here, it isn't too bad to get rid of you. I will be able to fulfil a small wish of mine from the past. It won't be too late for me to provide reinforcements after getting rid of you."

A rustling sound could be heard as though there were numerous grains of sand rubbing against each other. However, this rustling sound quickly turned into the sound of rushing waves. Around Ember, countless carbon atoms had already formed a mysterious black cloud that was rapidly expanding.

The range of Ember's Esper abilities was greater than before, and he could control it much more easily than before. Countless carbon atoms were stuck to the surface of his clothes and skin, and it was just like a weapon that he could bring around with him. He was not afraid of fighting in a place without any carbon.

"This is the strength of a Grade A Super..." The sound of the mercenaries gulping with nervousness could be heard. They felt a wave of pressure emanating from the screen, and their legs turned to jelly.

But the next moment, they saw Han Xiao's body shaking and bolts of electricity being shot out in all directions. It accurately connected to the ceiling, ground, and the compressed orbs in every corner. With him as the center, he seemed to have formed a web of electricity!

Ka ka ka!

The next instant, hundreds of machines were activated. The scene was truly breathtaking!

Those compressed orbs had been set up by him before the battle!

The entire base was a trap that he had laid!

Chapter 486: Fierce Battle

Ka ka ka!

The sound of the machinery unfolding covered the sound of Ember's carbon particles rubbing against each other.

Following the walls and corners, hundreds of artilleries slammed onto their pedestals. The three-pieced large caliber cannons gave out a sense of ferocity. The majority of the gunpowder artillery had been replaced with electromagnetic kinetic artillery, and there were ten additional laser light ray artilleries, providing higher penetrative force. [High Class Energy Control] had allowed Han Xiao to obtain the energy weapon technology.

Dong! Dong!

The artillery let out an angry howl as the large caliber cannons started to operate. The metallic hum of the turrets was reflected in the roar of the machinery.

Thirty to forty Black Panther mechanical beasts pounced out, their shoulder cannons spitting fire non-stop. On the ceiling, the mechanical spiders gleamed coldly as they scuttled around. Other than the Black Panther mechanical beast, Han Xiao was also able to manufacture smaller machines, such as the mechanical insect series. Other than spiders, he could also produce centipedes, scorpions, and wasps.

He only needed the blueprint of the mechanical spider for reference, and he could come out with the blueprints for other insect series by himself.

Phillip launched a unified attack, commanding all the machines to fire toward the ash.

The black carbon particles that were originally saturating the air contracted inward to form a sphere, with Ember wrapped inside it. The outer layer was made up of diamonds, and as the bullet rain cluster bombed it, the diamonds shattered, disintegrating into particles and reforming to fill the gaps. The capability of the shield seemed to be almost endless.

Seeing this, Han Xiao's face twitched. This is the Carbon Shield? It's practically cheating!

At this time, Ember's indifferent voice could be heard inside the ball of diamonds. "Even if you planned a trap in advance, even if you are immune to my Carbon Deconstruction, in the face of my current strength, you only have one outcome... Defeat!"

Boom!

The next moment, the diamond sphere transformed into a black-colored wave, slapping down with a force that could destroy mountains. Dozens of the mechanical beasts were caught within, and they turned into a pile of scrap metal in the blink of an eye. Not only did the metal bear signs of being crushed, it also had grooves and marks, traces of violent tearing.

What a strange force this is. It can instantly cripple the armor of my mechanical beasts!

As this thought rang through Han Xiao's head, he did not pause to observe further but slammed his palms together, releasing a compressed orb from each side of his hands. The orbs expanded to form thirty-two golden-white Hovering Shield Shuttles, which lined up in a circular manner around himself. They each spat out a thin ray of light, with every four beams combining into one, causing eight points of light to appear before Han Xiao's body.

The connection between each light point caused a reaction to occur immediately. A glowing line strung the eight light points together, forming a circle. Within the light circle, a mirror-like golden protective light shield appeared, as though painted by an artist!

The black wave welled up, slamming on the golden shield. The scene resembled one where waves from the sea dashed against the reefs, only to be split apart to move on either side instead. Under Ember's control, the split waves recombined behind Han Xiao, rushing from his back this time.

However, at that moment, the formation of the Hovering Shield Shuttles changed yet again. The eight light points were arranged in a 3D manner, forming shields surrounding Han Xiao's figure. It formed a trapezoidal shape, causing the black wave to be unable to attack from any angle. While the trapezoid flickered every time that the waves hit it, it ultimately remained motionless.

"Hovering Shield Shuttle Formation, Halo Array!"

[High Class Energy Control] was one of the core knowledge of the Mechanic class. During this period of time, Han Xiao had built quite a few interesting toys, and this [Halo Array] could be considered a stronger version of the Sonic Sphere, integrating offense and defense into one.

Han Xiao squinted as he scrutinized the waves and finally understood the reason for its weird strength difference.

The black tide only existed as a wave on the surface. If one looked closer, they could see that some carbon particles inside had been transformed into diamond fragments, and supported by high speed spinning inside the waves, they turned into something resembled a circular saw. The cutting force was abnormally strong as a result.

This swathe of black contained at least a few hundred of such 'diamond wheel saws'. Just like the undercurrent in a river, it would be difficult to notice without careful observation. It was no wonder the mechanical beasts had turned into scrap metal in an instant.

The significance of this was that if the wave was set to engulf a whole building, it would be able to turn it into rubble in a matter of seconds. This destructive power far exceeds that of its appearance on the surface, like a Golden Ant Colony that could strip an elephant down to its bare bones in a matter of seconds.

While he was confident in his tanky body, Han Xiao had no desire to let his tender skin be exposed to such a horrifying force.

They indeed live up to their names as Calamity Grades, to be able to have such control over conflicting operations of subtlety and aggressiveness. Ember was unable to achieve that in the past, but now he has more control over his abilities. I have to be more careful, Han Xiao reminded himself.

Even as the thoughts spun in his head, the Void Dragon Mechanical suit covered his body. He strode with large steps toward Ember in assault mode. There was no way of him breaking past Ember's defense from mid range; he had to get within close range to be able to have a chance.

Aroshia turned into a stream of light, penetrating into the diamond sphere that enclosed Ember. The carbon particles within could only cause her energy body to swell up but were unable to perform an effective attack, since she was highly immune to physical damage after transforming into energy.

Hum!

The rays coming from an energy explosion shone out from within the diamond sphere.

Ember had eaten a close-range energy bomb from Aroshia. Unable to retreat, he could only choose to deactivate his diamond sphere, turning it into a flat shield to ensure his visibility. He felt extremely uneasy in the presence of Aroshia, whose energy form made her immune to physical damage.

Numerous bullets sparked on the surface of Ember's diamond shield, ricocheting off with metallic noises. Ember glanced over the scene once before waving his hand. The carbon particles surrounding him wildly spread out, no longer clustering together. They turned into a black colored sandstorm, drilling into the various machines and destroying their internal circuits.

Buzz!

Sparks flew out as a large number of machines became crippled.

Ember coldly laughed. "The battle has ended."

As long as he managed to destroy all the machinery, the Mechanic class would become akin to a tiger whose teeth and claws had been pulled out.

While Black Star could mitigate his abilities, he could do the same to Black Star!

However, upon casting his eyes forward, Ember found out that Han Xiao seemed to have no intention to stop, as though he was indifferent toward what had happened.

With quick footwork, Han Xiao rushed up to Ember as a complicated machine unfolded in the palm of his hand. This melee weapon was very thick and almost two meters in length. It resembled a giant knife with a hand guard, but the shape was more futuristic, akin to a rifle with a barrel. This was a weapon in that category, named [High Frequency Strike Cannon], a multipurpose, close-range weapon.

This new equipment replaced his original electromagnetic scythe, which could not keep up with his strength.

The blade of the weapon was a protective shell covering the inner structure. The blade inside consisted of a high-frequency oscillation, which was hard to trace, carrying a strong cutting force. Along the side of the blade were two rows of holes, and each time the blade came into contact with the target, those holes would spew out gunpowder to ignite and cause an explosion.

The gunpowder could also cause internal heating, resulting in an electromagnetic overclocking of the equipment, allowing it to enter a second stage of Super power output, something akin to a Great Release[1].

Surrounded by sparks and carrying lightning within, it was violent.

Boom boom boom!

One strike after another rained down, and the explosions continued unabated as Ember repeatedly used his diamond shield to resist. His brow was slightly furrowed. His forte did not lie in melee battles, so he attempted to retract the particles to surround his body, trying to sabotage Han Xiao's armor. However, the Sonic Spheres that followed Han Xiao disrupted the particles, foiling his scheme.

Sound waves were constantly released toward Han Xiao, forming an invisible shield around him. The moment that the carbon particles neared him, they would be forcefully repelled, bouncing off instead of adhering to the surface of his mechanical suit.

The three of them seemed to have rolled into a ball from the fighting. Ember's expression no longer showed ease, as Han Xiao was giving him more trouble than expected. It seemed like he was not the only one who had improved. He had originally thought that he would be able to eliminate Black Star quickly, but to think that he was tangled up with him now!

In Ember's original vision, only Nagakin would pose some trouble. Now, he found out that Black Star was also not easy to deal with. However, Ember thought that this was a good chance!

To be able to discover this point sooner was a blessing, compared to being caught off guard.

Because the enemy soldiers had split in two, Black Star had taken the risk to hold Ember up. However, he did not have many helpers with him. Thus, this could be considered the best chance to get rid of a strong enemy.

As he thought up to this point, the look in Ember's eyes changed.

He had initially wanted to resolve this quickly and meet up with Anur once more, but now, he would not mind putting in some more time to remove any possible hindrances.

At this time, a carefree laugh suddenly rang out from Han Xiao.

"Ah-ha, that's a good look you have there. I feel more killing intent. It seems like you're finally willing to waste more time with me."

"I certainly do not think it a waste of time," Ember coldly replied. "The majority of your machinery has gone to waste, and I can destroy your mechanical suit sooner or later. By that time, what other methods will you show me?"

"What other methods, you say?" Han Xiao chuckled twice before his tone suddenly turned ferocious. "Then, I'll let you experience it firsthand!"

Hum!

His Mechanical Force gushed out, and as though a shockwave of electricity, it swept across all the machinery present.

The next instant, the crippled machines were reactivated with [Waste Modification], and all of the weapons came back to life, awaiting orders!

The War Mechanic Class was one that was borne from war itself!

The mechanical roar resounded once again!

Ember was caught unprepared and was blasted flying. His face was blackened with soot, and he quickly blocked the follow-up attacks using this Esper abilities. While it was not a huge problem...

... he had indeed been injured!

Ember suddenly looked up, the anger blazing within his pupils.

The pain that he was suffering awakened his body's memory of Han Xiao.

The shame and humiliation that he suffered, which he had gradually forgotten, came rushing back like a tsunami!

[1] Also known as Bankai, this is the ultimate technique of a Bleach character. Back

Chapter 487: I Do Not Believe Heroes Cannot Fall to Their Deaths!

The enthusiasm from the duo's battle radiated outward, causing the mercenaries that were hidden in the surveillance room to stare with their mouths hanging agape.

Black Star could actually fight equally against a Calamity Grade Super‽

The first thought that came into everyone's minds was that the opponent might not be so strong after all. While they had never seen the full capabilities of a Calamity Grade Super, they had heard many rumors about their frightening powers and how Grade B Supers were effortlessly destroyed in front of them.

However, looking at the battle between Han Xiao and Ember, maybe the rumors about the Calamity Grade Super's combat capability were simply overexaggerated.

This gave the mercenaries some form of confidence.

"I want to go down and help." A bearded mercenary suddenly stood up, withdrawing his gun from its holster.

Everyone else had a strange look on their face. While the enemy was not as strong as expected, it was definitely safer to be seated where they were. Why do you have to seek danger?

The bearded mercenary glanced at everyone, secretly disdainful. He thought that this was a godsent opportunity!

Since there was little danger, going down to help meant showcasing his good side to Black Star. If he left a deep enough impression, he might be invited to join the Black Star Mercenary Group!

This person thus hurriedly left the surveillance room. Nobody else dared to lecture him, turning their attention back to the surveillance cameras.

When the bearded mercenary reached the battlefield, the atmosphere made him feel a little nervous, causing him to start regretting his decision. He took a deep breath before telling himself that riches were obtained through encountering dangers.

Following which, he barged through the door loudly, firing continuously at Ember's back as he shouted, "Black Star, I'm here to reinforce you! Quickly...."

Pa!

In the blink of an eye, before the bearded mercenary could even finish speaking, his body 'collapsed'. Dust leaked out from within his clothes.

"He—he's dead just like that‽"

The mercenaries in the surveillance room were all stunned silly, fear coloring their faces.

Weak my ass!

This guy can literally kill people through fright!

The Calamity Grades are too terrifying; we're better off hiding here and slacking!

The guts that had just begun growing within those mercenaries were nipped at the bud, and whatever courage they still had left was thrown out the window.

The group of mercenaries now understood that Black Star, who was able to compete with those of the Calamity Grade, was not just so-so as described by the other mercenaries. Most likely, even those Grade B mercenaries who secretly scoffed in disdain at Black Star could not beat him even if they fought together against Black Star.

Indeed, a person with reputation would definitely have some form of ability to back it up!

...

On the battlefield, Han Xiao felt that this matter was a little strange. Why did this bearded mercenary not bother to quietly hide? Could it be that he had been possessed by Aesop and purposely went there to seek death?

At this point, Ember repeated his tactic, attempting to paralyze the machines again. He did not believe that Han Xiao could repeatedly rejuvenate his machines.

His hypothesis was correct; Han Xiao indeed could not use his [Waste Modification] skill infinitely. Other than the limited number of uses, the energy consumed each time was not a small amount.

However, Han Xiao was clear of another point. Those carbon particles that Ember employed based on his control were similar to the relationship between him and his machines. Without them, Ember's ability would also weaken.

As such, Han Xiao had long made preparations.

With a snap of his fingers, a trap machine that had not yet been activated suddenly shone.

Within the black wave, countless spherical shaped lights appeared, trapping huge clumps of carbon particles within them. In an instant, the black wave was reduced by a great margin.

Those traps were nothing unique, just ordinary shield generators. In an orthodox sense, their purpose was not even made to trap items within. However, in Han Xiao's eyes, any machine could be a trap. To have those shields locking in a huge number of carbon particles was as good as trapping them within, causing them to become prisoners within the shields.

Even though Ember could still control the carbon particles, he needed energy and time to break through the shields. All that would create distractions for him.

This move of his effectively shaved off a portion of Ember's battle strength!

As for this location, it was comprised of an alloy that did not contain carbon within. Han Xiao's machines were also not made out the carbon steel materials, and thus, other than the mercenary who blindly sacrificed himself, there was nobody else whom Ember could extract carbon from. While the range of his ability was great, he still required time to extract the carbon from his sphere of influence and bring it over, unless he decided to extract the carbon particles from his very own body.

The remaining carbon particles suddenly started spinning, forming the shape of a tornado as it tried to cut through the ceiling. Ember had discovered that this battlefield was extremely disadvantageous to him. He wished to change the battlefield, and going out into the open would allow his combat capability to increase a few folds.

Ember did not realize that his attitude toward Han Xiao had imperceptibly changed—from the disdain and contempt early on to now, where he had even begun to consider the effect of the battlefield. He could clearly feel a sense of pressure from Han Xiao, from a Grade B Super, a pressure that this was an opponent who could threaten his life!

At that moment, Han Xiao strangely did not retreat but rather rushed toward the dangerous cutting tornado as he shouted, "Explode!"

Boom!

The mercenaries in the surveillance room hurriedly detonated the explosives, causing the base to collapse. Numerous building materials fell down and buried the area.

Han Xiao greatly respected any Calamity Grade Super, so he had prepared and buried a huge payload below them. Detonation was an art, and due to his positioning of the explosives, the entire floor of the building collapsed. The duo entered a state of weightlessness as they rapidly fell.

Rumble!

Bits of debris and rubble ricocheted around them, and their vision and breaths were obscured and stifled by the thick clouds of dust. The momentum caused by the explosion was so large that it was as though an entire mountain had shifted.

Ember hurriedly formed a diamond panel under his feet, stabilizing himself. He intended to fly out of this collapsing building while using his carbon particles to shield himself.

Hu!

From afar came the sound of loud whistling. Having fought with Han Xiao for so long, he recognized the sound coming from the High Frequency Strike Cannon. He understood that Han Xiao was pursuing him like a rabid dog. Ember did not wish to carry out a fight in such a complicated environment, but he had no choice but to retaliate.

Suddenly, a lump of black shadows appeared in front of him, obscuring his limited vision.

Ember jumped in shock. He was totally blind, and no matter what he tried, he was unable to escape from the cage of shadows. Furthermore, this thing could not even be touched, so he had no idea what contraption this was. The sound of howling winds was getting closer, but mixed within the various sounds of the collapsing building, it was difficult to pinpoint the exact position.

With no other alternatives, Ember could only deploy his diamond sphere defense once again.

Clank!

A tough object pierced into the sphere, and Ember immediately utilized micro-manipulation to reveal a small hole to appear at the moment of contact, trapping the hard object. Based on the size, it was obviously Han Xiao's Strike Cannon.

While he could not see, Ember immediately dispelled his diamond sphere, changing it into a long spear, and pierced in the direction of the Strike Cannon. He predicted that his reaction speed would still be able to catch Han Xiao.

However, his strike only hit thin air.

"Not good!"

Ember instantly reacted, but it was already too late. A large hand from the mechanical suit firmly latched onto the back of his head, and without any warning, a Void Jet Spray was discharged directly.

At the same time, Han Xiao utilized the skill [Armor Piercing Consecutive Attacks] from the Germinal Organization's Leader's Character Summon Card. In the next five seconds, all his attacks would have a certain chance to break the armor of his enemy, reducing his defense by twenty-four percent.

Boom!

Ember felt as though he was struck by lightning. His brain shook, and stars flew in his vision, causing his Esper ability to dissipate for that instant.

But this instant was enough to cause the diamond panel that he had below him to disintegrate. The duo once again fell down the collapsed building!

Swoosh!

Dust blew in their faces, and they could only hear the sounds of collapse and the whistling of wind.

Before this, Han Xiao had borrowed the messy and complicated environment to create a diversion attack. He had first used [Void Vision] to inhibit Ember's line of sight, followed by throwing his weapon and using [Void Travel] to appear behind Ember soundlessly, creating the scenario where he attacked Ember from behind.

This opportunity was rare; thus, Han Xiao would not let go. He ignored the cost of energy, releasing burst after burst of Void Jet Spray. This was the additional ability granted by the Void Dragon Mechanical suit. While it had no cooldown, the energy consumed would rise by thirty percent if used again within ten seconds.

"Forty-two percent of Energy remaining, hum... Twenty-six percent of Energy remaining... Energy level critical, hum..."

The energy of the mechanical suit was spent at a torrential rate, with the voice of Phillip constantly sending out warnings.

Ember was hurriedly attempting to gather energy within his body. No matter the class, Energy had a universal function, which was to raise resistance for a short period of time.

Suffering a series of heavy blows, Ember had no choice but to focus his attention on defending himself. As such, the control of his ability dropped by almost seventy to eighty percent.

Han Xiao had managed to see Ember's attributes through the interface. This guy also had a Boss template, with his defense and health at insane values. Furthermore, because he was a Grade A Super, his conversion of Endurance was too high, so much so that his health was comparable to Han Xiao's. Thus, Han Xiao could not afford to be stingy. All kinds of explosive abilities such as [Gene Liberation] and [Overload] were activated, and Han Xiao even chose to activate the Character Summon Card of Hila, [Whisper of the Dead]. Causing mental damage could also help to shave off a target's attention.

This series of buffs was activated extremely quickly. They had only fallen around half the distance, with both of them still weightless.

Ember's head was still being clamped, and the pain and humiliation caused him to sink into fury.

While he could not see what was happening behind him, he could feel the power fluctuations given off by Han Xiao weakening. This indicated that his energy in his mechanical suit was low, which meant that his burst of attacks was about to end.

While he had taken a hit, he had at least achieved his objective. The moment that they came into contact with the outside world, that would be his stage!

The last Void Jet Spray completely drained the energy in the mechanical suit. Ember could clearly sense this point, and he endured the splitting pain in his head, hoarsely saying, "You have no more energy left... Just wait for me to drag you out from your turtle shell. I'll turn you into mincemeat!"

When Han Xiao heard this, he gritted his teeth and lowly shouted, "Aroshia!"

Aroshia was not affected by gravity at all, merely following beside both of them, her body easily phasing through the rubble. When she heard her name, she turned into a beam of light and accelerated, sticking to Han Xiao's back. She opened her arms and embraced him from the back.

Hum!

Her energy body was like melting ice, flowing into the core of the mechanical suit.

In an instant, the Void Dragon Mechanical suit's energy capacity shot through the roof!

"Energy levels at 327%, hum... Circuit is overloaded. Please expend the excess energy as soon as possible, hum..."

To Han Xiao, Aroshia's energy was the biggest reserve battery for him!

Han Xiao's tightened his hand, holding Ember's head as though he was clamping it with tongs.

"Energy? I'm not lacking in that! Are you ready for a severe concussion‽"

Boom!

Feeling the new surge in energy levels, Ember's eyes opened wide, shock and anger filling his face. He felt that something was amiss, as though the entire matter had proceeded out of his control.

This sort of feeling... made him subconsciously remember the time when he first fought Han Xiao! He gritted his teeth.

Every time... it's the same every single time!

This b*stard has all sorts of schemes!

The continuous series of explosions drowned whatever thoughts he had. The duo slammed into the ground, the impact jolting both to their bones. They lay prone, unable to muster the strength to stand due to the pain in their bodies.

At this point, a huge shadow rapidly expanded where they were situated.

The next second, the collapsed building slammed down on them.

Boom!

Dust billowed!

The earth shook!

Chapter 488: Retreat

The commotion of the collapsing building startled the pedestrians and they gathered together at a distance, pointing at the rubble as they discussed about the chaos with shock.

In the skies, a large number of aircrafts stopped in midair and looked down at the rubble below.

While the destruction of this battle was not as bad as the battle between the three Grade A Supers, because of something similar happening a while back, the citizens of Noriosse paid close attention to the battle.

"How is Black Star? Who won?" A couple of mercenaries who ignited the explosives had long escaped from the base and were currently in midair within an aircraft.

Swoosh!

A mechanical arm pushed off a large boulder, and a figure could be seen climbing out of the rubble with difficulty. With his hands on his knees, Han Xiao panted heavily.

"Ouch... a few of my ribs were fractured." Han Xiao felt a dull ache in his chest. An entire building had crashed down on him, and even with the powerful defense of his Void Dragon armor, its durability had fallen from the original sixty-seven percent to about thirty percent. Black crack marks could be seen all over the armor, and sparks could be seen coming out from some of the cracks. Thankfully, the equipment's passive [Indestructible Toughness] was activated, and the resistance of the armor was increased many times over.

A portion of the damage penetrated through the mechanical suit's defenses. Han Xiao looked at the interface in front of him, and it showed that he had lost more than 4,000 HP together with light fractures and slight dizziness effects.

The majority of the damage had come from the falling debris. Thousands of tons of debris had smashed down onto his body, and when he was falling, his entire attention had been placed on attacking. He had let Phillip take over the control of the machines so that he would not need to divert his attention. When he landed, both he and Ember had landed in two different regions. Phillip had immediately turned the Halo Array into a shield to block the majority of the falling debris. Without that, the damage that he had suffered would definitely have been much worse.

Because of the collapsed building, the majority of his machines were buried under the rubble. However, he still had over seventy compressed orbs on him and still had the ability to fight. Aroshia separated from the mechanical suit, and her glow was obviously dimmer than before. Han Xiao had used up plenty of energy.

The dust cloud spread, and his visibility was limited. Han Xiao looked around him to find Ember.

Killing a Calamity Grade Super was not that easy, but this series of attacks would definitely be enough to make Ember suffer. Ember did not have the powerful physique of a pugilist or any Esper abilities to strengthen his body. If he did not use his Esper abilities to put up a defense, his durability would not be very high.

Sha sha sha!

At that moment, a familiar grinding sound could be heard, and Han Xiao's expression changed. He immediately jumped back, and three thick black spears shot down where he had been standing just a moment ago. Those black spears had easily penetrated through the rubble and created a pit over ten meters long.

The dust cloud was blown away by the strong wind, and Han Xiao could see a thick, black wave that was double the size of before. It spanned over two to three hundred meters and was still expanding. Now that he was not in a building, Ember was able to gain access to a never-ending supply of carbon.

All of a sudden, the black current condensed into a large, lifelike python, which was two to three meters thick and a hundred meters long. The body of the python stood erect with its snake head looking at Han Xiao, sticking out its tongue. It looked as though it was truly alive. On top of the snake's head, Ember's figure could be seen.

He should have been full of elegance and majesty, but he was currently looking a little pitiful. His clothes were torn all over the place and blood was seeping down from his forehead with half of his face dyed red. The skin at the back of his head all the way down to his neck was torn apart. Being shot by the Void Jet Spray twenty to thirty times had obviously left a scar. Ember's face contorted in pain as he glared at Han Xiao furiously.

Every single attack that Han Xiao shot out was aimed at his head, and Ember had to focus all of his attention to control his Esper abilities. Thus, he was forced to endure a head splitting headache, which affected his ability to control his Esper powers. He was not able to perform any meticulous control and could only expand the range of his carbon wave.

In the sky, a couple of mercenaries gasped in disbelief. "That Calamity Grade Super is severely injured!"

They had personally witnessed Ember's strength, and there was even one of them who had personally experienced it. However, Black Star was actually not on the losing end and had severely injured this Grade A Super who was considered a powerful figure in the galaxy.

He was truly formidable!

The gazes of those in the surroundings were very quickly drawn to Ember. In truth, it was difficult for them not to notice such a large black snake.

This looks bad. Han Xiao knew that things were no longer in his favor. For him to achieve such a battle result, it was because of his meticulous set up of the battlefield ahead of the event. While he had severely wounded Ember and affected his battle prowess, Ember was still far from death. Since they were on the outside, Ember would be able to make full use of his abilities, and it would be difficult for him to injure Ember any further. There would not be a chance like before.

A thought flashed through Han Xiao's head. His attention is fully on me. As long as I can hold him back, when Nagakin succeeds on the other side...

He would not lose his cool just because he had the upper hand. He was very clear that he would be the one suffering if the battle continued.

He did not continue battle, and the thrusters of his Void Dragon mechanical suit began spewing fire. Han Xiao shot into the sky and began to flee.

"Don't think of escaping!" Ember roared furiously, and the python under him shot into the sky to chase after Han Xiao.

Escape? This is a strategic retreat!

Numerous black spears shot over, and Han Xiao avoided them nimbly in midair. Turning around to take a look, Han Xiao heaved a sigh of relief. Thankfully, Ember gave chase. That fellow was indeed infuriated.

Avoiding a head on confrontation and letting Ember chase him would allow him to buy the largest amount of time. Han Xiao did not feel that it was necessary to fight him head on.

With one person escaping and the other chasing, both of them weaved through the buildings. Humungous black python charged forward recklessly, and its size was constantly increasing. All the aircrafts along the way hurriedly avoided the python, and those that were not able to get out of the way in time were quickly reduced to shreds. Even the buildings that the python merely brushed past had large chunks taken out of them.

The commotion was shocking!

Compared to the black snake, Han Xiao's figure was like a little bug.

Woo...

The ringing alarms could be heard from afar, and the Public Security Squad rushed over at high speed. The destruction that Ember had caused had affected the peace of the city, and the Public Security Squad would not ignore it.

"Di di di... You have an incoming call request..."

A notification sounded in his helmet, and Han Xiao accepted the call request. Nagakin's face then appeared in front of him.

"Alvin's doppelganger has been brought to safety. Anur destroyed two streets, but thankfully, a passing Calamity Grade tourist was dragged into the fight and decided to help out. However, Anur's speed was too fast, and we could only force him back..."

A passing Calamity Grade Super‽

This piece of news was truly out of his expectations. Han Xiao had thought that he would have to stall for a while longer, and his face could not help but cramp up. At the same time, he lamented about how Noriosse was truly full of hidden dragons and crouching tigers.

He could not help but think about the first time that he met Alvin. This fellow's luck was probably even better than Herlous', and he had truly gotten lucky this time.

"Black Star, hang in there. We will come back and reinforce you immediately!"

Nagakin's voice was filled with anxiety. The way he saw it, it was far too dangerous for Han Xiao to be delaying Ember alone. He had been afraid that Han Xiao would already have beaten before he called.

Turning off the communicator, Han Xiao's eyes glowed. With Nagakin fulfilling his part of the plan, there was no need for him to entertain Ember any further. He then turned around and turned on the speaker in his helmet.

"Do you really think that you can get rid of me? Have you forgotten about my other ability?"

As Ember heard that, his face turned color.

He suddenly remembered that when he was on Floating Dragon Island, Han Xiao had once displayed the ability to recover fully in an instant.

This meant that this battle would not end any time soon!

"The Public Security Squad is rushing over, and the Grade A Super hired by Noriosse will not allow you to act so unbridled. My comrades have already forced Anur back and will be here to reinforce me soon. If you still want to continue playing with me, I shall accompany you," Han Xiao said in a tone filled with delight.

Ember had a look of hesitation on his face and was extremely reluctant. He was stuck in a dilemma where he could not advance or retreat.

Continuing the battle would only be a waste of time. Not only would he be unable to get rid of Black Star, he would end up being surrounded. However, he was reluctant to retreat like that! After being beaten up by the enemy, he had not settled the score with the enemy and still had to retreat! This was too much!

The sound of the sirens grew nearer, and Ember realized that Han Xiao had already reduced his speed, looking as though he had no fear. Ember's expression was ice cold with a sharp pain coming from his wounds and the dizziness reminding him of the condition of his body.

The pride and arrogance that he had after entering the Calamity Grade had vanished during the battle.

Black Star's name was even more deeply imprinted in his heart. Together with the pain, this impression had seeped into his bones.

"It is my mistake. I underestimated you too much. Next time, regardless of your strength and the machines around you, regardless of whether you are in your prime or severely injured, I will not be careless."

He then calmed his anger with a complicated look in his eyes.

After one last glare at Han Xiao, Ember resolutely turned around. The black snake crumbled into a dark cloud and escaped with him like a black mountain demon.

"I'm finally safe."

Han Xiao stopped moving and heaved a sigh of relief. While he seemed to be extremely relaxed on the surface, he was feeling a great deal of stress in his heart. If he did not fight Ember in a place that was to his advantage, he would definitely be on the losing end. If all of his machines were destroyed, even Aurora's Character Summon Card would be completely useless. At the very most, he would only be able to make use of it six times, and he had already been forced by Ember to use it once.

He did not wait for Nagakin to return and surround Ember but warned him to escape. If Ember truly wanted to escape, it would be difficult for them to stop him. On the contrary, all of the other mercenaries would have to face the risk of being annihilated.

Looking at the incoming Public Security Squad, Han Xiao did not wish to be interrogated, so he hid from them.

At the same time, Nagakin arrived with the mercenaries. The moment that they saw the destroyed building, those hired mercenaries were completely dumbfounded.

Along the way, all of them had been extremely pessimistic about Han Xiao's chances of survival. For Black Star to delay a Grade A Super alone, they all felt that he would definitely be trampled upon and were extremely worried.

However, they witnessed the rubble created from an intense battle, and everyone, including Nagakin, was dumbfounded.

Just what had happened‽

Where did Black Star go‽

Chapter 489: Anur

As the mercenaries who had stayed behind saw the returning Nagakin and the others, they hurriedly landed, and both parties met up. The hundred or so mercenaries who had gone out to rescue Alvin then heard those few mercenaries excitedly describing what had happened.

Apart from Herlous and those from the Black Star Mercenary Group, looks of disbelief could be seen on the others. Black Star was actually able to fight a Calamity Grade Super evenly and had even severely injured his opponent. This was completely different from what they had expected!

Everyone was shocked into silence.

Even Herlous was in a slight daze. "Is he so powerful?"

Nagakin was immediately overjoyed. He had not felt confident, and never had he imagined that Black Star would be such a reliable ally.

At that moment, Nagakin received a message. Han Xiao asked them to dig out all the machines buried under the rubble before meeting up with them at another place. He also reminded them not to attract too much attention.

Nagakin turned around and realized that more and more people were gathering over to watch the show. The Public Security Squad and construction team were also rushing over. Too many regions of Noriosse had been damaged by battles recently, and the Noriosse Financial Group was probably extremely frustrated. Nagakin did not wish to be tied down by them and hurriedly instructed everybody to quickly dig up all the machines before they escaped.

After waiting for a while, Han Xiao arrived.

The hired mercenaries looked at Han Xiao with more respect in their eyes and made way to let him in.

Walking over to the middle of the crowd, Han Xiao slapped Herlous on the shoulders and said with a smile, "Ember was injured by me, and he is definitely suffering a headache right now."

Herlous was stunned for a while, and he stroked his mechanical arm. Every time that he thought about Ember, the nerve connection to his mechanical arm would begin to ache dully. Hearing that, Herlous broke out in a wide smile and felt his anger vented.

"Good brother, fantastic!"

After chatting casually for a while, Han Xiao collected all the recovered machines back into their compressed orbs. After counting all of his machinery carefully, Han Xiao concluded that he lost about thirty machines, and many of his machines had dropped in quality. Apart from injuring Ember, he did not receive any material gains. The biggest gain would be completing their mission objective and saving Alvin's final doppelganger.

"We meet again, friends." Alvin greeted everyone. His complexion was pale, and his lips white. It was obvious that he was not very healthy.

"Seeing a mixed blood Godoran again, nothing good will happen for sure." Han Xiao shook his head. "Where is the Grade A Super who helped?"

"He left."

"Leaving without leaving his name behind, he is probably a Superhero."

Han Xiao did not find the matter strange. The more powerful someone was, the greater their responsibilities. At the very least, there were some who still adhered to such principles. Superheroes were a common occurrence, and there were many powerhouses who did not mind playing the role of a hero occasionally.

After saving their target, Han Xiao and the others began discussing their next move.

"If DarkStar want to have any progress, they only have two choices. First, search for Alvin's main body, which will be like finding a needle in a haystack. Second, snatch his final doppelganger from us. Thus, we have the initiative, and DarkStar is on the passive side. They will be anxious. Nagakin, how much longer will it take for your reinforcements to arrive?"

"The War Bureau sent the fleet nearest to us, but even if they make use of the stargate, they will take twelve days at least."

"DarkStar won't ignore the incoming reinforcements and will definitely send their fleet to hide near Noriosse. I have a few ideas, but we should first find a new base before discussing them in detail."

...

On the other side of the city, the injured DarkStar troops found a concealed location to rest and recuperate. While the battle had been short, it had also been extremely intense. The number of Grade B Supers on both sides added up to about fifteen, and with the mercenaries being well trained, the battle had been intense.

Herlous' Battleship Slicing Blade and Sherman's cannon had clashed with each other ferociously. Wilsander had also joined the battle and found the most powerful enemy, Forsyth. Sylvia's strength was far too weak, so she had not entered the battle. Since Feidin was only a customer, he was not willing to be dragged into the battle.

Anur's expression was extremely ugly, and his mood was very bad. The battle had initially been in their favor, but another Grade A Super had jumped in from nowhere and resulted in all of his efforts going down the drain. How was he to know that a Grade A Super would suddenly pass by that region? He had already tried his best to reduce the collateral damage.

For the majority of Calamity Grade Supers, as long as they went all out, they would definitely have the ability to change the very geography of a planet. For their strength to grow to such a level, they could be considered a walking weapon capable of wiping out a civilization. However, they had to restrain themselves when fighting someone of the same level. The more restrained they were, the more concentrated their attacks would be, and the more easily they would be able to break through the enemy's defenses. If they only tried to spread out the range of their destructive abilities, it would not threaten an opponent of their level.

Furthermore, Anur did not wish to create too much damage on this planet and provoke the Noriosse Financial Group.

If Ember had rushed over in time, they might have had a chance in a two-on-two battle. However, who knew what Ember was doing? He had not arrived even after a long time. It was truly difficult for Anur to understand. With the majority of the enemies in battle with him, there should not have been too many men left behind in the base. Just what had taken Ember so long‽

With Anur being surrounded, he had been able to escape injury only because of his speed. Finally, seeing Alvin escape and being unable to wait for Ember's arrival, he could only retreat.

One could only imagine how frustrated Anur was at Ember.

Not too long later, Ember returned to the base. The blood had clotted and formed scabs. The injuries all over his neck were extremely frightening, and everyone was shocked.

Seeing that, Anur began to frown. "How did you get injured? What did you meet? Could it be that Nagakin found yet another Calamity Grade Super?"

Ember waved his hands and said with his teeth clenched, "It was Black Star. He stayed behind to deal with me."

Anur's eyes widened in disbelief. "You mean to say that you were delayed by a Grade B Super and were beaten by the other party to this state‽"

Ember nodded.

Anur took a few seconds to regain his cool. "Since you dragged the battle on for so long, you must have gotten rid of him, right?"

"The situation was urgent, and I retreated."

Anur immediately let out a curse.

He had placed a great amount of hope in Ember, but at that moment, he could not help but wonder if he groomed the wrong person.

Ember could feel the change in Anur's gaze and knew that his respected teacher was extremely disappointed in him. His face contorted, and he wanted to explain himself. However, he felt that he would only embarrass himself even further and thus chose to remain silent.

Anur had decided that he must lock Ember up for another year after their return. He did not wish to see the face of this fellow and said to Forsyth, "The situation isn't in our favor. Do you have any suggestions?"

Forsyth thought for a moment before saying, "We have three choices. We can either use the three doppelgangers in our hands to find Alvin's main body, snatch the doppelganger from them and kill Nagakin while we're at it, or... do nothing at all."

Chapter 490: Sharp Contradiction

"What do you mean?"

"We are hidden in the dark, and Alvin's main body won't dare appear," Forsyth explained. "Thus, the other party is definitely waiting for the Godoran reinforcements. Our fleet is already awaiting their orders near Noriosse, and we can apply for more motherships to be sent out. When the reinforcements of the other party arrive and attempt to collect Alvin from Noriosse, our troops can launch an ambush and destroy the enemy's fleet. Not only will we be able to get rid of a traitor, we will also be able to get rid of a Godoran fleet."

"You are right," Anur said. "The port is a place that they have to pass, and it is easy to track their whereabouts. This can be a layer of insurance, but we cannot ease up. Continue to search for Alvin's main body and give the other party pressure."

Han Xiao and the others found another base. After settling down, he looked for Nagakin and Alvin to discuss their plans. However, before their discussion, a question surfaced in his mind. Why did Alvin choose to betray DarkStar? There was no information on this character from his previous life.

"Betray? I do not feel that this is a betrayal." Alvin shook his head. "I have golden colored skin and am a Godoran. This is abandoning the darkness and entering the light. I joined DarkStar once, but it does not mean that I have to be a member of DarkStar forever.

"There are many mixed blood Godorans who are treated with prejudice and scorn. Thus, when the members of DarkStar appeared before me, I left without any hesitation. DarkStar's hiring process is extremely strict, and it would be almost impossible for any Godoran spies to sneak in. I am naturally not a spy either."

Han Xiao's brows then furrowed, and he asked, "So, why have you chosen to side Godora now?"

"Because I noticed that Godora's problem with DarkStar isn't so simple. DarkStar has always brainwashed their members with hatred and described Godora as an extremely evil entity, as though they wished to wipe out all mixed blood Godorans. Reinforcing hatred is the same as reinforcing loyalty to them. The members of DarkStar have begun to hate Godora more and more over the years, but news of the true situation in Godora has always been restricted."

Alvin raised his head up and sighed. "Godora's attitude toward the mixed blood Godorans isn't so extreme, and the government is very open. They only treat DarkStar as their enemy, and to ordinary mixed bloods, the government has always been extremely fair to protect their rights."

Han Xiao nodded and said in a teasing tone, "I am waiting for you to say 'but'."

Alvin laughed bitterly as he heard that. "Alright. But... the government's stance and policies aren't sufficient to change the views of the Godorans. The purebloods' disdain toward the mixed bloods is deeply rooted in tradition. While the government is able to give us the assurance of material objects, discrimination is one's free will. The government isn't able to control the thoughts of its people. The Godoran government wants to accept the mixed bloods, but the enemies of this policy are their own citizens and the millions of years of tradition.

"DarkStar's presence incited greater contradiction between the people and made the purebloods discriminate against us even more. Even though terrorists like DarkStar have nothing got to do with ordinary mixed bloods, that isn't enough to change the views of the majority. After all, not everyone is able to act rationally.

"Compared to the dangerous DarkStar, the mixed bloods living in Godora are targets for them to vent their frustration. While DarkStar claims that they are fighting for the lives of the mixed bloods, their unscrupulous means haven't given the mixed bloods a better life but have turned it into a greater torture. As such, even more mixed bloods have been forced toward DarkStar's side.

"This is a knot that is extremely difficult to untie. You cannot expect the purebloods to suddenly end their discrimination in a single night, and you cannot expect the mixed bloods to not have any thought of retaliation when being discriminated against. This is the fact that DarkStar is exploiting. If not for DarkStar, would the mixed bloods suffer from so much discrimination?"

Han Xiao tapped on the table with his finger and looked at Nagakin. "What do you think?"

Nagakin let out a sigh. "He is right. I do not discriminate against the mixed bloods, but I do not represent everyone. The policies of the upper echelons have always been to treat the mixed bloods with kindness and give them a fair chance to seize opportunities. However, because of DarkStar, those on top are also afraid that the mixed bloods may betray them. Thus, it is impossible for any mixed bloods to climb to a high position. You can treat it as a solidification of social class."

"While policies may be good, a good plan may not be feasible, especially when it involves the benefits and survival of an entire race." A thoughtful expression lingered on Alvin's face. "Thus, I am willing to defect to Godora. Perhaps the lives of mixed bloods will only become better with DarkStar being eliminated."

"Your ambitions are extremely noble," Han Xiao said with respect.

"Thank you." Alvin smiled. His tone then changed. "However, even if you praise me, I will not hand over any intel before I am completely safe."

"Don't say that to me; it isn't my concern," Han Xiao said with a smile. "You should say that to the Godorans. My mission is only to protect you."

He then retracted his smile and said in a serious tone, "We are unable to predict DarkStar's plans, and we currently have a few options. First, hide ourselves and observe any changes while waiting for our reinforcements. This will be the most passive plan. Second, take the initiative to attack DarkStar. Distract them so that they won't have the energy to find your main body.

"The third option requires the agreement of you, Alvin. We can hide your main body far away from this place, and it would be best if it was on the other side of the planet. This way, your doppelgangers will all disappear. While you will suffer some injuries, DarkStar will lose all clues. I know a Teleportation Mage who lives on Noriosse, and he can help us. If not, he will definitely be beaten up by me again.

"Fourth, find a chance to leave Noriosse secretly with your main body. However, this plan is extremely risky. There is a ninety percent chance that DarkStar's fleet is currently hiding outside the atmosphere, and leaving rashly would only cause us to fall into their net."

Nagakin and Alvin looked at each other with hesitation.

Han Xiao then said with a deep voice, "If the two of you don't have any other suggestions, which plan will you pick?"

With Nagakin's personality, he leaned toward taking the initiative to attack.

However, Alvin did not want to take the risk and preferred to wait and watch.

Bang!

Before they could come to a decision, Aroshia's body suddenly swayed, and she crashed onto the table with a loud bang.

The few of them turned over to take a look. She was currently holding onto her head with her eyes in disarray and brows furrowed as though she was in great pain.

"What's wrong"? Han Xiao got up immediately and held onto Aroshia's shoulders.

Aroshia rubbed her temples. "It is like... there is a voice calling out to me in my head. It seems to be getting closer to me. I can feel its position..."

Han Xiao's brows were raised, unsure of what was going on.

At the same time, a black spaceship finally came out from dark space and was floating among the stars.

It had arrived from a distant star field. It had jumped through numerous stargates, almost been caught in a black hole, witnessed the explosion of a new planet, driven past an asteroid belt, escaped the chaotic tides of space, met a radiation storm, and also traveled through the most silent part of space without a single organism or planet. After a whole series of dangers, it had finally stopped.

The shiny mirror-like exterior of the spaceship reflected a planet that looked like an iron fortress.

Chapter 491: Welcome Back

Because of Aroshia's sudden outburst, the meeting ended abruptly. In the end, they followed Alvin's thought and chose to lie in wait while waiting for their reinforcements. While Nagakin displayed his worries toward the DarkStar troops who were chasing after Alvin, Alvin seemed to be extremely confident in the situation of his main body and was certain that it would not be found. However, his lips were tightly sealed and not even the slightest bit of information could be discovered.

Alvin was the core of the mission and they had to respect his wishes. Thus, they could only choose to stay behind in the base and raise their guard while monitoring the actions of Anur and the others. Very quickly, three days passed.

The three days were extremely peaceful, and both parties were completely unharmed.

DarkStar was only interested in finding Alvin's main body but did not have any clues. They ran around the place randomly, and the anxious mercenaries became at ease. During this period of rest, Han Xiao repaired the machines that had been damaged in his battle with Ember and regained some of his combat strength. He did not think that this mission would end so simply. After all, it was a mission with more than a million experience points, so something else would probably happen before or after the reinforcements arrived.

This mission did not create any chaos, but another incident attracted the Great Mechanic Han's attention. In the past three days, Aroshia had found the calling in her head to be more and more obvious. Using her words, it was as though there was a voice recorder being broadcasted on a never-ending loop in her mind. The volume of the playback got louder and louder, and she had a strong feeling that the other party wanted to lead her somewhere.

Han Xiao had always known that Aroshia was filled with secrets. She was virtually undying and indestructible. Even Ames was not able to destroy her thoroughly, and her origins were extremely mysterious. Furthermore, she even had a rank A chain mission, and he had not even seen her in his previous life. Did this mean that the players did not find this hidden character? Han Xiao then thought about the outcome of Floating Dragon in his previous life. Because of Ames' fooling around, Floating Dragon had ended up being destroyed in his previous life. At that time, had Aroshia still been on Floating Dragon Island? If not, where did she revive?

As a captain who cared for his subordinates, Han Xiao began asking Aroshia about her situation in detail. After knowing that the call was coming from the sky and not too far away, after a series of questions and investigation, it was very likely that the location Aroshia was referring to was an empty port in Noriosse.

With the distance so near to him, Han Xiao could not help but feel wary. When they first arrived in Noriosse, Aroshia did not have such a feeling, which meant that there was a possibility for this feeling to be the result of a party chasing after Aroshia recently arriving at Noriosse. Thus, the other party had the ability to determine Aroshia's location. If Han Xiao chose to ignore the other party, it was very likely that the other party would continue bothering them. What made Han Xiao the wariest was the fact that he did not know the other party's intentions.

Aroshia was not able to recall anything related to this sensation and decided to personally check this matter out. Han Xiao naturally did not want her to run around on her own. Since Alvin was currently acting in a low-profile manner in their base, Han Xiao decided to follow Aroshia.

After considering for a while more, he called Feidin over as well.

It was probably akin to bringing out a peace talisman on the way out.

The three of them sat in a space elevator and arrived at the port that Aroshia's instinct was pointing toward. This was a port that had its exit facing the outside of the Shattered Star Ring. Only those who come from other Star Fields would stop in this port.

"Which direction is your instinct pointing toward?"

The large hall of the dock was full of people walking in all directions to the different docks. Apart from the endless supply of passersby and tourists, there were also the Noriosse guards and staff of the dock. The ceiling of the empty port was transparent, and the scenery of the universe could be seen. The three of them were currently on a travelator, travelling slowly and casually.

"Over there." Aroshia pointed in front.

"What clear directions." Han Xiao was helpless.

"It's a pity that my abilities are still weak," Feidin said with a smile. "If not, I would be able to use my Psychic abilities to treat Aroshia's brain and help her to regain her memories."

"You will have to first research on the memory storage methods of energy lifeforms. She does not have a brain for you to search."

"Really?" Feidin looked at Aroshia. "Even when her body is solidified?"

"Her Esper abilities aren't activated only when in use. When she awakened her Esper abilities, it remodeled her entire body. Her brain, bones, muscles, skin and so on are all no more than an emulation. While she doesn't seem to be any different from an ordinary being, what will flow out if you crack her head open won't be brain fluids."

Han Xiao paused for a moment. Looking at Feidin's face full of curiosity, he frowned. "You can't be wanting to give it a try, right?"

"You know that I would not do something so violent..." Feidin waved his hands before laughing bitterly. "However, that lady living in my head does not think so."

"Chen Xing probably feels as though she is always being suppressed by you in your body. If I was a lady, I wouldn't have a good impression of you either," Han Xiao joked. "However, feelings are born with time. Perhaps after being suppressed by you for a long time, she might enjoy such a feeling and no longer be willing to come out."

"What f*cking bullsh*t. This lady here will slaughter you the moment I come out." Feidin pointed at this head and chuckled. "These are the original words which she said."

Han Xiao bent forward and leaned toward Feidin's face. With his eyes staring deeply into Feidin's eyes, it was as though he could see Chen Xing's consciousness. While Chen Xing was not able to control the body, she was able to share Feidin's senses. Han Xiao then clicked his tongue and said, "No, even if you are able to come out, you definitely won't want to meet me."

After having a casual conversation, the three of them arrived at the source of the calling. This was a storage compartment, and the door was sealed. They needed a passcode or access card before they could enter.

"The thing calling out to you is inside. It seems like it is really something alive. We have to find a way to go in and take a look."

Han Xiao's expression turned solemn. At this moment, the member of staff in charge of this region walked over.

"Do you guys recognize the person inside the warehouse?"

The three of them turned around and Han Xiao asked, "What's the matter?"

"It's like this, the spaceship inside landed in the warehouse three days ago. However, no registration was made, and the fees haven't been paid. All of our requests for communication were rejected, and the person on the spaceship did not disembark either. If you guys know him, please pay the fees."

Han Xiao's eyes glowed. The other party did not leave the ship and did not make an appearance. It was truly mysterious.

"Wait a moment, why didn't you chase him away even when he didn't pay?" Feidin asked.

"Because his spaceship is a reconnaissance ship of the Federation of Light. This is the symbol of his status. Our Noriosse Financial Group won't chase away such a high-grade ship so easily." The staff's words were extremely reasonable.

"In truth, I am also not sure if we know him." Han Xiao pointed at the door. "Can we go in to take a look?"

"I'm afraid not. I don't have this authority. According to the regulations, only the temporary owner of the warehouse can allow any guest to enter." This was to prevent people from stealing the spaceship.

"Let us make an application then, since he is still in the warehouse." Han Xiao pressed a button on the warehouse's communicator. Since the other party was there for Aroshia, it was unlikely for him to reject them.

After sending out an application and waiting for a while, time seemed to inch forward extremely slowly. The communicator suddenly turned green, and the door parted slowly. The owner of the spaceship had opened the warehouse without even saying anything to them.

A black spaceship over a hundred meters long was currently parked in the warehouse. This small sized spaceship was extremely nimble and was the normal size of a reconnaissance spaceship. Its shiny black exterior reflected the view of the warehouse's interior.

How could the Great Mechanic Han not recognize the spaceship? He immediately knew that this was the BlackLight Stealth. Not only was it expensive, its build quality was exceptional. In his previous life, whenever a spaceship like this appeared in the market, it would quickly be purchased by the large guilds or wealthy players.

Han Xiao immediately felt some pressure. A figure who owned such a spaceship definitely would not be a simple character. If the person was hostile, it would definitely be very troublesome.

Swoosh!

There still was no communication, and the hatch to the BlackLight Stealth opened up as though the owner was inviting them in. However, the pitch-black entrance seemed to be emanating a cold air.

"Not even showing his appearance and acting so mysteriously." Han Xiao looked at Aroshia. "Are we going in?"

Aroshia nodded and said with uncertainty, "I can feel someone calling me from inside. He is extremely anxious. Furthermore, this spaceship gives me a feeling of familiarity, and I think that I have spent a long time inside the spaceship before. I may even have experienced something extremely important... but I cannot recall anything."

Han Xiao's interface suddenly displayed a notification. The second part of [Reboot] had one extra point in mission progress. It seems as though this spaceship was an important location in Aroshia's memories.

"Then let's go up and take a look. Don't worry, I'm right behind you," Han Xiao said.

The three of them walked into the spaceship and were greeted by a dark alley. After taking a step into the alley, the lights lit up on both sides.

Whoosh.

At this moment, the hatch behind the three of them closed up and restricted their retreat.

"The owner of the spaceship wants us to walk forward," Feidin said.

Without bothering about the closed hatch, the three of them walked along the alley and arrived at a fork. The light toward the right was lit up, but the left was completely dark. The three of them understood that the light was their guide.

The cold and pale light glow seemed to carry an eerie atmosphere along with it, and the three of their faces also looked pale under the light.

"In truth, I would have preferred to go toward the left, but let's first follow the light. For the owner of the spaceship to not reveal himself until now, this owner reminds me of that annoying Aesop who likes to act mysteriously." Han Xiao stroked his chin and was even more curious about the relationship between Aroshia and the other party.

Following the light, they walked down a winding hallway before finally arriving at the cockpit of the spaceship. The cockpit was completely empty at the moment, and the control panel was glowing with a yellow light. The most eye-catching item was an accessory being hung above and to the right of the pilot's seat. This was a transparent glass cover with a ball of golden light flickering inside it like an unstable light bulb.

Aroshia was stunned for a moment before walking forward to touch the glass cover as though she was possessed.

Hum!

All of a sudden, a strange scene occurred!

All the lights in the spaceship lit up at the same time, and the cockpit was suddenly brightly illuminated. The golden light from within the glass cover merged together with Aroshia's palm from where she touched the glass cover as though the golden light had originally belonged to Aroshia.

At that moment, the sound of the spaceship's system could be heard.

"Authority verification complete. Welcome back, Captain."

Numerous flashing lights began to fly all around the cockpit before a figure of light was condensed in front of the three people. The figure of light immediately spread his arms and hugged the stunned Aroshia.

"I've finally found you, comrade!"

Chapter 492: Aroshia's Origins (1)

"You recognize me? Who are you?" Aroshia reached out to touch the man made of light. However, her palm phased through. Han Xiao observed that there was no physical sensation in the person with narrowed eyes, confirming his suspicions that this man in light was a holographic projection.

The hologram of the man slowly looped once around Aroshia, akin to a fish swimming in the air. His tone was dispirited as he muttered to himself. "I guessed correctly. Your memory circuit has malfunctioned. You were supposed to rest and recuperate after completing your task, allowing your thoughts to get used to this new body. Otherwise, it will result in sequelae such as a loss of emotions or memories and will require recalibration."

The minds of the trio present were at a loss.

Han Xiao was suddenly jolted, and he blurted out, "Are you called Risda?"

The hologram turned around with a weird expression. "How do you know my name? Did she tell you that? No, that's not right. She has already forgotten me. Just who are you?"

In the mission [Reboot], the reward of the mission mentioned Risda's name. Successful completion of the mission would raise the favorability of said person toward himself. Thus, Han Xiao guessed that this person would not be an enemy.

Upon listening to Risda's tone, it was clear that he was aware of Aroshia's origins. Han Xiao was eager to hear Risda's explanation—to think that this spaceship actually belonged to Aroshia, and Risda actually called himself her comrade, speaking about certain procedures and migration details.

He had a hunch that all of this pointed toward the final goal of the [Reboot] mission.

Seeing that Risda was wary of him, Han Xiao explained his identity and briefly described the circumstances in which he met Aroshia. Strictly speaking, he was the one who had saved Aroshia.

After hearing his story, Risda floated in front of Han Xiao before giving a deep bow. He gratefully replied, "Many thanks to you for helping AL51004. If it was not for you helping her to recover a portion of her memories, the sensor would not have been able to locate her whereabouts."

"What does the serial number mean?"

"It was her original name." Risda turned back to Aroshia. "Do you remember it?"

Aroshia shook her head in response. "I can't remember. I only know my name should be Aroshia."

"It seems like the memory loss is more serious than I thought. The turbulent flow of the wormholes could have torn your memory circuit into numerous bits and pieces, requiring more time to properly recalibrate. However, you need not worry. Our memories will at most be buried deep within our subconsciousness and will never be destroyed. Sooner or later, you'll be able to regain them." Risda immediately abandoned Han Xiao, floating back to Aroshia and speaking with a warm, encouraging tone.

Han Xiao coughed dryly, reminding Risda whom he was originally speaking to. "Just what sort of life form are you? Are you an energy-based life form?"

"No, I'm in fact an AI life form."

"You're an Artificial Intelligence?" By the side, Feidin spoke up. "So, are you the core system of this spaceship?"

"You're wrong. An AI life form is not a system, nor is it limited to one body. We're a type of life form, and this spaceship is merely a temporary tool for me to move around in the world."

Risda pointed at Aroshia, his tone full of nostalgia and familiarity as he spoke. "She was originally supposed to be the same as me. We upgraded our programs together as we grew up and supported each other in many difficult situations. We could be considered confidants who would share data within ourselves and also war comrades that fought side by side. She's very important to me."

An AI life form?

A lot of memories flashed by Han Xiao's mind. The universe was full of surprises, with evolution being the representative of disorder and chaos. There were countless possibilities, and those who were restricted by the physical sense organs could hardly imagine the vastness of the number of life forms present.

For example, the Great Mechanic Han had once read of a resource file describing a certain 'Named life form'. When someone called out their names, they would truly exist, but if no one knew of their existence, they would also fade out of existence. Their 'Names' were the keys to summoning them.

This sort of thing, however, mainly appeared only in the magical civilizations, only that the knowledge of such was in shambles. As such, when he came across the resource file in the past, the Great Mechanic Han, being the guy who deemed it his responsibility to share all kinds of knowledge, had immediately scanned through the document, memorizing it in detail.

As for an AI life form, simply put, they were Artificial Intelligences that had gained independent thinking and become 'alive'. The details were complicated, but if compared to ordinary Artificial Intelligences, they were as different as the heavens and the earth.

Compared to material life forms, the AI life form was a special type of life form. They lived in a virtual network, just like fish required water to live in. Through this network, they could constantly upgrade themselves and install different modules in themselves. In addition, their way of communication, reproduction, social structure, and civilization were all extremely special.

"Is she also an AI life form?" Han Xiao's expression was one of surprise. This was out of his expectations. Aroshia did not look like an AI life form at all; she clearly had a body made of flesh, and she had even awakened an Esper ability!

"I can't tell you the specific details regarding this," Risda solemnly said. "While I'm extremely grateful to you for taking care of her, we have an important mission to carry out. Hence, I'll be bringing her away. I hope you can understand."

Han Xiao kept his expression, narrowing his eyes in response.

Are you trying to steal my people‽

Are you kidding me? I took great lengths to nurture Aroshia into one of my capable officers, and with just a sentence, you wish to sever our relationship? Do you not feel guilt at all‽

So what if you two are childhood sweethearts? Your father here is the current male lead![1]

Han Xiao's eyes gleamed as he replied, "I believe you should ask Aroshia for her opinion. Don't decide for her."

The two of them then turned to look at Aroshia, whose expression appeared a little hesitant.

The entire scene went quiet in an instant.

This scene made Han Xiao think of a scenario where the child was asked to choose which parent they would follow after the couple divorced. Whatever it was, it was a strange scene.

Only three seconds passed before Aroshia stepped toward Han Xiao, stating, "You may be right, but I really cannot remember you right now. I only remember that Black Star saved me.... so I won't follow you."

"You..." Risda was helpless.

If the other party was unwilling, how could he take them away‽

He had no other ideas. Since he could not persuade her, he could only compromise. No matter what, he had to ensure that he stayed by Aroshia's side.

"I understand," Risda said in a depressed tone. "I'll stay behind and accompany you until you regain your memories."

Hearing this, Han Xiao secretly let out a smile. Because of her amnesia, all Aroshia could remember was himself. Thus, she definitely would not choose someone else. This was a situation where he could not lose. Wait a minute, why did it feel as though he was the old man next door who was taking advantage of the wife while the husband was out‽

Shaking his head, Han Xiao threw away this strange feeling. "Don't be overjoyed. I haven't allowed you to stay. And I won't, not unless you tell me what happened in its entirety. Maybe I can also be of some help."

Risda was left in a predicament. He was not able to take Aroshia away, but he did not have any misgivings toward Han Xiao. After all, it was Han Xiao who had saved her.

"Alright then, I'll tell you everything. This matter has to be explained from the beginning..."

The three of them shared a glance, finding a place to sit comfortably before Risda began his story. As he narrated, Han Xiao finally got a clear view of the situation and suddenly realized the origins of how Aroshia came about.

Way back in the past, a spaceship had crash landed on a desolate planet, with all its passengers having died from the impact. Only the Artificial Intelligence of the spaceship was left, repeatedly sending out distress signals to outer space again and again, according to the last instructions of the captain. However, no one came in the end. After a long period of time, the Artificial Intelligence began to get bored of this repetitive work that bore no results. It developed independent thinking, and with continuous upgrades and changes to its own program frameworks, it was no longer a tool that followed commands blindly. It had evolved from an artificial intelligence to an actual life form.

The AI life form manipulated the wreckage of the spaceship, using the equipment provided to construct a few simple robots. It began exploring the planet, tapping into its resources to create a factory. Through that, it started to mass produce work robots, all of which were manipulated by it to build up an empty base on the barren planet.

On one of the days, the AI life form suddenly felt lonely. Thus, based on its own program framework, it created another AI life form, simulating a different personality—this was the reproduction pattern of the AI life form, self-proliferation.

The two AI life forms began to converse, and slowly, they created more of their kind, which in time became the ancestors of the entire race. They all existed in virtual networks but were able to manipulate tools and robots in the real world through their programs. Robots began to extensively harvest resources under the control of the AI life forms, and since their manufacturing base could run continuously without a need for rest, the base constantly expanded.

In time, they finally broke free from the planet, beginning to migrate to other planets to create bases. Thus, the number of AI life forms also increased exponentially.

Millions, dozens of millions, hundreds of millions....

And thus, a brilliant AI civilization was born!

[1] Basically, what the author is trying to convey is something akin to a drama series, where the main character (Aroshia, in this case) has a childhood sweetheart but meets another man that she may or may not have feelings for while she's separated from the original sweetheart. Back

Chapter 493: Aroshia's Origins (2)

An AI civilization did not have any cities and only had ice cold mechanical bases. Not a single living being would be inside, and it would be cold and silent. However, the virtual net would be an extremely prosperous sight. In the virtual world that they constructed, every formless member would be able to have their own body.

To them, the virtual world was their home. As for the bases, cities, and mainframe system in reality, those are only constructs created to protect their home.

Risda and Aroshia were both citizens of such a civilization and were both AI life forms.

AI life forms had almost no physiological desires—unless a simulation module was installed—and did not have any productivity constraints. Thus, there was no hierarchy in the civilization, and everyone was equal. Living in an AI civilization was almost like a utopia. Their method of communication was the exchange of data, and it was many times more efficient than using speech, writing, or pictures. In an instant, a large amount of data could be sent, and only a mind reader would be able to match such efficiency.

When Risda described all that, Han Xiao came to a realization.

For an AI life form to evolve to such an extent, it can be said to be equivalent to a soul.

Ordinary beings would first have a physical body before having a consciousness, but an AI life form was the complete opposite. It first had a consciousness.

The story that Risda had described afterward confirmed Han Xiao's predictions. This AI life form was indeed coveted by others, and the one who coveted them was a beyond Grade A Mechanic!

This person had broken through all the defenses of the AI civilization, locked down their virtual homeland, cut off all their connections to the net, and captured all the AI life forms in the civilization. To him, those AI life forms were probably materials to create weapons.

He locked up all of the AI life forms in a mainframe system and suppressed the solitary will of the AI life forms through a program. He enslaved them all and only left them with their high-speed calculation ability and learning ability. That person then treated the AI life forms as 'souls' and placed them into empty shells to transform the way they lived. They turned into weapons that listened to orders and formed a huge army.

This process was similar to Mind Possession of a Psychic.

Aroshia's current state was one of the 'weapons' that could be mass produced. Her 'soul' had been injected into a ball of energy through some special means, and the AI life form had been transformed into an artificial energy life form.

After being turned into a weapon, the shell would no longer be a 'tool' that could be casually swapped out but a 'body' that the consciousness could not separate from. It was like a lock that locked up the freedom of the 'soul'. It was almost like the majority ordinary organisms.

The moment that the body was destroyed, the lock would be shattered. Because of the special characteristic of the AI life form living in the virtual world, it would not die together with the body but return to the mainframe system of that Mechanic through the ever-present net regardless of distance. With a backup copy of the body's data, that Mechanic made use of a top-notch skill to allow the data to automatically reform the weapon's body and draw energy from the main base through a psionic channel.

This was the reason for Aroshia 'undying' body. However, it was not controlled by the system, and thus, there would be an error in her data whenever she was reborn. Under normal circumstances, a weapon that was reborn would not lose their memory like Aroshia.

That beyond Grade A Mechanic had created a powerful army that could be recycled ceaselessly! Every single weapon was a standalone warrior!

Magic and technology made use of different means to achieve the same result. Such technological skills were almost like magic.

In order to kill those weapons completely, one had to wipe their AI life form out in the virtual world.

Ordinary people would develop technology, and when technology went out of control, they ended up being wiped out by artificial intelligence. However, this time, the opposite had happened, and numerous AI life forms had been enslaved.

Aroshia and Risda were both fish that had escaped the net and were extremely lucky to have escaped the process of being enslaved. The two of them wanted to save their brethren, but that required them to destroy the main system so that they would be able to activate the consciousness of their entire kind.

As such, Risda found an opportunity to control the assembly line that had created such weapons to give Aroshia a body. However, the alarm was sounded before they had a chance to take action, and they ended up being chased by countless of their kind. The two of them had no choice but to escape, and Risda had managed to snatch a BlackLight Stealth to escape with Aroshia. However, they could not defend against the numbers of the enemies and fell into a wormhole, and the two ended up being separated.

The changes to one's body would also cause one's thinking to be changed. Aroshia originally needed time for her consciousness to meld together and get used to her body, but being chased afterward gave her no time to rest at all, resulting in her memory loss.

...

Hearing Risda's story, the three of them had looks of disbelief on their faces.

"Undying army‽ A Super strong Mechanic‽"

Han Xiao almost spat out a mouthful of blood.

These two labels were far too unique, and he almost thought that the other party was describing him. Of course, this was not possible. The Great Mechanic Han knew who this Mechanic was. This Mechanic was far too famous, and it would be impossible for him not to recognize that character.

This beyond Grade A Mechanic had been the highest-grade teacher of the Mechanic class in his previous life!

Furthermore, he was one of the main characters in the main storyline [Calamity of the Supers] of the later version. He had naturally formed a faction of his own!

To think that this would be related to the main storyline in later versions. Just what kind of a person did I save?

Han Xiao rubbed his temple and felt a huge headache.

My goodness! Version 2.0 hasn't even started! Can we still play properly?

Without even thinking, Han Xiao was able to guess what the final target of [Reboot] would be. It would definitely be to reactivate the independent consciousness of those AI life forms and save them from the demonic hands of a beyond Grade A bigshot. Could this mission be any more dangerous‽

Do you think that I am a sh*t digger who loves to find sh*t‽

"I have already told you the truth," Risda said. "Regardless of whether you are willing to help, I must stay behind to wait for her to recover her memory."

The three of them looked at each other and Aroshia was in a daze. Such a feeling was like an ordinary nine-to-five working Chinese adult being told that she was actually a South African citizen.

You are actually African—you only look a little bit more yellow. All of your countrymen are being controlled by an alien with a flying saucer. I am going to pull you back to get rid of the aliens and save our country...

Such a feeling was truly awful!

Aroshia was thrown into confusion.

Han Xiao regained his cool and thought about the pros and cons of this matter.

Actually, let's forget about the cons. Whether or not I want to do this mission is a decision for another day. There is a very obvious pro right now. If Risda stays behind, does this mean that we will be able to use this BlackLight Stealth temporarily?

Han Xiao's eyes lit up immediately. The BlackLight Stealth was a high-grade spaceship that was worth tens of millions of Enas. From activation to hyperdrive, only a couple of seconds were required. It was the Maserati and Bugatti in the spaceship world. Piloting such a spaceship would give him a great deal of face, and it would save him the trouble of renting spaceships from everywhere!

This is the best!

Because of Alvin's mission, Han Xiao rejected Risda's idea of moving out immediately. He got Risda to wait in the warehouse, and they would return after completing their mission. Risda had no choice but to agree with Han Xiao.

The three of them said goodbye to Risda and left the spaceship. Along the way, they slowly digested the large amount of information that they just received and gradually calmed down.

Han Xiao had not expected Aroshia to have such a background. However, she would not bring him any risks at the present moment. Patting Aroshia on the shoulder, he said, "Don't worry too much. Regardless of how things turn out in the future, you are still yourself at the moment."

"Hmm..."

Walking over to the elevator region, Han Xiao's communicator suddenly rang.

Opening up his communicator, Herlous' anxious face could be seen.

"Black Star, bad news. DarkStar found Alvin's main body!"

Han Xiao's expression changed immediately.

"We're on our way!"

Chapter 494: Emergency Plan

In the DarkStar base, a bruised Alvin collapsed in the middle of the room with three of his doppelgangers tied up in the corner.

Sherman carried his cannon while saying, "There are a total of five Alvins. Four doppelgangers and one main body. Godora saved a doppelganger, so this should be the main body. He hid himself extremely well, and Sinesa managed to break down his mental fluctuations to grasp the thoughts of his doppelgangers. After a carpet style search, we found the traitor's main body in a very well concealed location."

By the side, a skinny man called Sinesa nodded in agreement. He was a Grade B Psychic part of the pursuit force. The doppelgangers were exactly the same as the main body, and even their mental fluctuations were the same, resulting in outsiders being unable to tell them apart. However, this also became the clue for their chase.

Anur nodded in satisfaction. "Very good, your efficiency has brought pride to the organization. Our mission can be completed early. Ember, take action."

Ember nodded, and with a raise of his finger, Alvin's main body was reduced to dust.

Everyone was expressionless and completely used to the feeling of killing their enemies.

Just when they wanted to pack up and retreat, all of them froze in place. Their gazes were filled with shock as they looked at the corner.

Alvin's three doppelgangers were still around, and a look of mockery could be seen on their faces.

"With the main body dead, why aren't the doppelgangers disappearing‽" Anur's expression changed, and he looked at the pile of dust on the ground. "Could it be that this isn't the main body‽"

"Hahahaha...." The three doppelgangers burst into laughter.

This wave of laughter immediately infuriated the DarkStar warriors. After searching for such a long time, had they actually been fooled‽

Anur's face cramped up, and he roared, "Kill them! One of them must be the main body!"

Swoosh!

The three doppelgangers turned to dust. Even when the first two died, the last doppelganger was still alright. Even when the third doppelganger died, DarkStar could not know if it was the main body. However, they already had a guess.

"The Alvin in Godora's hands is the real main body! He is truly bold! He actually used his main body to misdirect us and take the risk to seek Nagakin's protection! If we'd caught him earlier on, he would have been dead by now!" Sherman flew into a rage.

Bang!

The more Sherman thought about it, the more furious he was. Perhaps it was just his paranoia, but he could feel the blaming gazes of the comrades around him and smashed his fist heavily on the chair—because he could not reach the table.

Anur's expression was dark. "For the four doppelgangers to die together, Alvin will definitely have suffered severe injuries from the backlash. We cannot delay things anymore. Everyone, move out and kill the final main body hiding with Nagakin!"

Since the four doppelgangers had already been killed, their target was obvious. As long as they could kill the real Alvin, their mission would be a success. Anur did not wish to waste any more time and was prepared to lead all of his forces to quickly finish the mission!

...

After receiving the news, Han Xiao hurriedly returned to the base with the other two. He then saw the solemn expressions on the faces of everyone in the base. Walking over to the conference room, he saw that the main battle force was present in the conference room at the moment. He then saw Alvin, who was seated at the end of the table, and was stunned.

Had his main body not been captured? According to DarkStar's impatient character, they definitely would have executed the main body immediately. Since Alvin was still sitting there alive and the mission had not failed, Han Xiao immediately guessed what was going on.

"You should have told us earlier that this is your main body."

"Sorry, I was afraid of a leak. Information that only I know will not have the risk of being exposed to the enemy. Cough cough..."

Alvin covered his mouth and began coughing. Blood could be seen seeping through the gap of his fingers, and bright red spots were left behind on the table. His eyes were listless, and his complexion looked pale. The senses of his doppelgangers and main body were connected, and for the four doppelgangers to perish in a short amount of time, it resulted in a heavy blow to his body and mind. His current situation was extremely poor.

He had already taken a huge risk. He had swapped his main body with a doppelganger and accepted the protection of Nagakin and the rest. He had supported the idea of lying in wait because the 'main body' that DarkStar was looking for was actually his doppelganger. Thus, he had been confident. He did not like being on the passive side. Rather than hiding himself and praying that DarkStar would not find him, he might as well seek protection, and he would be safer that way.

"However, DarkStar has already seen through my little trick, and their next move will be to take the initiative to attack and get rid of me," Alvin said weakly. "I can only rely on all of you to protect me. Please."

Han Xiao's eyes glowed. This mission was not so easily completed. The actual flow of the mission was probably for them to escape DarkStar's attack while protecting Alvin. However, it would be impossible for them to fight forever, and Han Xiao guessed that he only had to delay the enemies until Alvin created a new doppelganger. They would then be able to mislead DarkStar and stall for enough time.

Han Xiao had not heard about Alvin's name in his previous life, and Alvin should have died on Noriosse, successfully assassinated by DarkStar. Apart from the ground forces giving chase, DarkStar would certainly have sent out a large fleet of spaceships to wait outside the atmosphere. To Alvin, this was a hopeless situation, and he could only struggle for his life.

With a large fleet lying in wait outside the atmosphere, they would definitely be surrounded if they attempt to escape in a spaceship. They had to make use of the small instant before DarkStar's fleet launched their attacks to escape. However, this was almost impossible as it demanded a lot from the spaceship.

However, there was a spaceship that could complete this high-level requirement at the moment.

Risda's BlackLight Stealth!

With just a short charge up, the BlackLight Stealth would be able to jump into dark space. If they installed anti-tracking and anti-screening equipment, this high-grade reconnaissance spaceship of the Federation of Light would be able to pass through the majority of the danger zones and escape from DarkStar's ambush.

If I help Alvin survive, what kind of influence will this result in? Han Xiao suddenly thought about the ranked S mission, [Bloodline]. He had a feeling that Alvin could become a key to helping him in his mission.

While he still had a [Mission Completion Card] in his hands, he would only be able to obtain the lowest reward. Han Xiao would naturally try to aim for a high accomplishment rate for these high ranked missions. It would be a waste for him to just end them with a Mission Completion Card. Han Xiao was still prepared to hold onto the Mission Completion Card in case of any disgusting missions in the future.

"DarkStar won't hesitate, and they will arrive soon." Han Xiao's voice was resolute, and he slammed the table to draw everyone's attention. "We do not have much time to prepare. Listen to me, I have a plan to send Alvin out of Noriosse."

Everyone was shocked when they heard that.

"We have to split our forces into two. Nagakin and the majority of us will stay behind to delay the enemy forces. Aroshia will take Alvin to find the Teleportation Mage to send them to the port. Not only will it be able to save time, they will also be able to throw off their pursuers. You will then find Risda to leave Noriosse with Alvin."

Han Xiao's gaze was solemn. While the plan sounded simple, it was actually full of risks. DarkStar had two Calamity Grade Supers, and one of them was Ember, who had a large AOE skill. The most important point was that they did not have much time to prepare and could only rush their actions.

His side only had Nagakin and Han Xiao who could attract Ember's firepower and ensure that Ember did not have the energy to harm others. Thankfully, Ember had been severely injured a few days ago, and Ember's combat strength would definitely be affected. However, even if that was the case, dealing with two Calamity Grade Supers at the same time was past their limits. Even with him in the picture, Han Xiao did not think that they would be able to deal with Anur and Ember without making sufficient preparations.

They only had a single choice. Split up the battlefield to split the enemy forces up. Thus, they had to let the enemy know that Alvin was escaping. That way, they would be able to split the enemy forces in two. It was akin to splitting up the risky elements... even though the plan was still extremely risky.

However, they had no choice but to take the risk.

Time was tight, and Han Xiao hurriedly handed out the missions. Everyone anxiously got to work, hoping that they would be able to speed up their actions.

After preparing for less than ten minutes, an explosion erupted.

Boom!

A powerful wind pressure attacked the building, and everyone lost their footing from the powerful gust of wind. However, they had all been mentally prepared and jumped out of the building and onto the streets.

In midair, Anur looked down at them with wind pressure circulating around his body. Ember was also in midair and was currently standing on a hundred-meter carbon tornado. All the other DarkStar warriors charged over from the ground with their killing intent overflowing.

"Their attack came so quickly."

Han Xiao's expression was solemn. Nagakin was beside him, covered in flames and ready to battle. All the mercenaries in the surroundings got ready for battle with many of them revealing looks of anxiety. Not everyone was able to maintain their cool in the face of the enemy.

A powerful pressure descended from the skies, and everyone felt their hearts tighten.

The collapse of the building caused a huge dust cloud to be formed. The commotion was huge, and there were many spectators in the surroundings with looks of exasperation.

Not again‽

Can you guys stop your destruction‽

Chapter 495: Battle of Noriosse (1)

With the two Calamity Grade Supers letting out their energy without any restraint, Han Xiao could feel a sharp pain at his brows as though it was an alarm going off crazily. In his helmet's energy scanner view, every single inch of Anur and Ember's body was oozing with energy like a bright sun. At every single second, they were exploding with energy as they burnt through every last bit of energy that their cells provided to activate their Esper abilities.

The energy reaction of a Grade A Super far exceeded all of the Grade B Supers present. The difference between the two was like a bright, burning campfire as compared to the flame coming out from a puny lighter. Presently, only Nagakin was able to match that kind of energy output, and even Han Xiao's own energy reaction was far from being a match for the three Calamity Grade Supers. This was a difference in grade.

The collapse of the building turned the surroundings into a complete mess. Han Xiao took a slow, deep breath, calming himself down while his brain rapidly thought of the best way to react.

Our situation isn't good at the moment. DarkStar has sent out all of their forces, and if the two Calamity Grade Supers decide to work together and wipe us out first, while we will be able to buy some time for Alvin, there will definitely be many who perish here.

Although I will be able to escape intact, Herlous, Sylvia, and the others will be in danger. They will probably end up dead by Ember's hand, and the losses will be immense. Alvin is already escaping, and DarkStar's main motive is to kill the traitor. Upon seeing that the traitor isn't here, there is a fifty percent chance that they will split up their forces to give chase...

Alvin shouldn't have escaped too far, and the enemy should still be able to see his escaping figure. We need to make the enemy think that we are afraid of them chasing after Alvin...

Just as Han Xiao had expected, Anur first glanced over the area, and upon realizing that the traitor was not around, his expression darkened. He then began to look around, and with his altitude, he saw an aircraft escaping at top speed. The one riding it was Alvin.

"I saw them!"

The tubes on Anur's back let out a sharp shriek, and just when he wanted to speed up to give chase, Han Xiao let out a loud roar. "Stop them!"

Bang!

Nagakin jumped up into the air and intercepted Anur's figure. The wind pressure shield was instantly shattered, and the both of them shot in two different directions like arrows.

Anur was instantly delayed.

On the ground, the mercenaries clashed together in a fierce battle with the DarkStar forces. Bright balls of explosions could be seen all around, and the sound of fighting could be heard everywhere!

Hum!

Bolts of lightning exploded forth from Han Xiao's body, and a mechanical army of beasts pounced forward valiantly. There were black leopards, cavalry, and spiders. They sped into the chaotic battlefield and aided the other mercenaries in battle. One hundred and seventy-eight cannon towers were also unleashed, and dense layers of laser nets were shot out. Phillip also controlled three unmanned mechanical suits to enter the battle.

The next instant, Han Xiao's mini army displayed their full firepower!

He raised his head to look at Ember and activated a compressed orb in his hand.

Kacha...

Numerous thick grayish alloys opened up and fixed themselves onto various parts of the Void Dragon mechanical suit. Han Xiao's body size rapidly expanded, and he turned into a five-meter-tall, mid-sized armor. The armor was extremely thick, and all the weak links of the armor were covered in armor. He was like a heavy infantry soldier and gave the impression of an unshakeable mountain. The Halo Array and Sonic Spheres floated behind his mid-sized armor and formed a large and small halo.

Siege Mode. Second upgrade!

After obtaining High-End Knowledge, Han Xiao had strengthened the energy source of the exoskeleton attack armor. This had resulted in the functions of the armor increasing greatly, and with more functions being added, the size of the armor had grown as well. His own body was in the middle of the armor, and he could control the exoskeleton armor through a connection to his body.

The thrusters on his back, calves, and feet activated at the same time, and the armor shot toward the sky. Han Xiao threw a punch, and the metal fist carried a powerful wind pressure with it.

"You again." Ember's wounds were still hurting. With a face full of rage, the black cloud turned into a rock-solid shield.

Boom!

The metal fist collided with the shield, and the vibration mechanism in his wrists diverted the shockwave of the blow into the shield. The next moment, Ember's shield began to crack up in all directions and turned back into carbon particles.

Ember's eyes were cold, and just when he wanted to launch an all-out attack, Anur, who was fighting with Nagakin, roared, "They want to stop us from chasing the traitor. The traitor should be our target! I will hold them back myself. Don't get tangled up with them—give chase!"

Hearing that, Ember's expression changed, and he glared at Han Xiao hatefully.

"You are lucky that I don't have the time to play with you. Scram!"

His mission was the most important, and Ember suppressed the killing intent in his heart. With the black cloud transforming into a snake, his figure shot out of the battlefield and gave chase to the escaping Alvin. A large building that was in his path had collapsed as a result.

The ruckus did not stop, and dust clouds rippled all over the place. Tremors came wave after wave without end.

The destruction of the battle had begun to spread, and the affected regions expanded rapidly. All the pedestrians fled for their lives. With similar destructive events happening so often recently, the Public Security Squad was on full alert at all times. At that moment, more than two hundred Public Security Aircrafts appeared right in front of Ember. Without enough time to avoid him, all the aircrafts were swallowed up by the black cloud and turned into piles of scrap metal in a matter of seconds. All the Public Security Personnel within the aircrafts were squeezed to death like a dumping with a metal skin crushing the fillings.

More than two hundred aircrafts had been destroyed instantly!

Han Xiao acted as though he could not stop Ember and shot a couple of mini homing missiles for show before stopping his pursuit. Looking at Ember's departing figure, Han Xiao heaved a sigh of relief. Letting both the Calamity Grade Supers of DarkStar separate would reduce their risk greatly. As for Alvin, he can only rely on himself.

With his gaze sweeping the ground, Han Xiao noticed the complete destruction of the entire region. The mercenaries were engaged in an intense battle with the DarkStar warriors, and a small battlefield had been demarcated. In the sky, Anur and Nagakin were enjoying their battle. Their figures shot through building after building, and the light rings that were created from their clashes showed their movement routes.

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

With Ember giving chase to Alvin, and the speedy Anur being delayed, the situation isn't so bad. At the very least, Alvin won't be caught so quickly. While Anur may be able to escape from the entanglement, the other DarkStar warriors won't be able to do so. The moment he leaves, Nagakin will be able to kill all these DarkStar warriors with ease. Thus, Anur won't do that!

The only problem is that Anur is extremely powerful, and his abilities are difficult to deal with. He is practically invincible when facing us, and no one will be able to keep up with his speed.

Han Xiao frowned and knew that Nagakin needed his help.

Thinking about that, Han Xiao took out an ordinary laser rifle and moved toward Anur while shooting.

...

Boom!

The collapsing buildings behind him were like the alarm bells of death. Alvin was drenched in sweat all over and continued to increase the speed of his aircraft. The speed of his aircraft was already at Mach 1.3 and was far above the safe speed of the aircraft. The transparent windscreen of the cockpit vibrated violent, looking as though it would shatter at any moment.

An ordinary aircraft to be used in a city would have a safety limit installed and could go up to 350 kilometers an hour at the very most. However, in the short preparation time that they had before DarkStar's attack, Han Xiao had displayed the might of a Mechanic and removed the safety limit. On top of that, he had installed a turbo booster to change this aircraft into a getaway vehicle.

"Ember's speed isn't slower than mine, but he does not need to avoid the buildings. If this carries on, he will catch me in fifteen minutes!" Alvin gritted his teeth. "Do you have any ideas?"

Aroshia did not reply, and her arm turned into an energy shield to protect their aircraft. She did not care about Alvin's life or death and was only following Han Xiao's orders.

"The time is too tight," Alvin said. "You said that the Teleportation Mage is in City 8. If we maintain this speed, we should reach it in fifteen minutes. However, Ember will catch up to us around that time..."

Aroshia ignored him completely and fell into a daze.

From afar, Ember still did not give up the chase.

Amid the tall, towering buildings, a black snake charged straight through rapidly, chasing after an aircraft that was constantly changing its route.

...

The recent destruction had drawn the attention of the Noriosse financial group. The commotion of this battle was extremely huge, and the upper echelons of Noriosse immediately received news and convened an emergency meeting.

"... the ones creating trouble are mostly Godorans. Our system identified one of the Grade A Supers. He is a high-grade officer from Godora's War Bureau, Nagakin. His opponent is currently unknown, and he must have used a fake identity when landing. However, since he is an enemy of Godora, we guess that he is probably a member of DarkStar. Apart from these two parties, we also noticed Black Star's figure. He is also taking part in the battle and is standing on Godora's side."

All the upper echelons felt a huge headache. None of them were characters that they wanted to provoke.

"They are still in battle, and the radius of destruction is constantly expanding. We have to stop them immediately. I recommend we make use of emergency plan three. Let the fleet outside of the atmosphere interfere with the battle!"

"I object. If both parties do not surrender, the Grade A Supers will attack the fleet, and our losses will be magnified. I recommend we send out the Protector. Incidents like this should be handed over to Supers to take care of. Let him aid Godora to get rid of DarkStar's Grade A Super. We cannot stand on the side of terrorists. At the same time, I recommend we activate the protective shield of the city and reduce our loss."

"I agree with the majority of the recommendations, but something small needs to be changed. After the Protector arrives, he cannot interfere in the battle between both parties and will only serve as an observer to control the damage between both parties.

"Our Noriosse will remain neutral; siding with Godora or DarkStar will only bring us trouble. Let them decide victory and defeat on their own, and the Protector will only interfere right before a Grade A Super is killed. Also, we cannot let Black Star die either. I do not wish to see Ames throwing Floating Dragon Island at us.

"Consider it our bad luck that they chose to fight on Noriosse. Losses cannot be avoided, but we don't want to bring ourselves trouble. Mark out a region for them to fight. In any case, this planet is insured already."

"I agree."

"Seconded."

All the upper echelons nodded.

"Carry out the plan immediately."

Chapter 496: Battle of Noriosse (2)

Bang bang bang...

"Don't avoid me if you dare!" Sherman cried out with a malicious expression. Lifting his cannon up, he shot out another large ball of light. The ball of light penetrated through the walls of the building, and it gave chase to Herlous' escaping rabbit-like figure.

"Stop firing if you dare!"

With a loud roar, Herlous dragged his Battleship Slicing Blade, and with the buildings as cover, he avoided Sherman's attacks. By making use of the complicated battlefield, he went around Sherman.

The instant that the battle erupted, Sherman had immediately picked Herlous as his opponent. He still remembered this mercenary who had injured him and planned to settle the grudge.

The chaotic battle between DarkStar and the mercenaries formed many mini battles scattered all around the region. The sound of killing, explosions, and firing could be heard all around, and the battles between the Supers caused more and more damage to the region. Flames could be seen burning everywhere.

Herlous was hit by Sherman's cannon fire a few times. The attack of this dwarf Cannon Master was powerful, and it did not feel good for Herlous to receive those attacks. His Shattered Light armor was charred in many different areas, and as they ran and battled, they gradually strayed further and further away from the main battlefield.

The opponent was an elite DarkStar warrior and also a Grade B Super. Herlous had no choice but to concentrate fully and did not have the attention to spare to bother about anything else. He only knew that the others had also met powerful opponents. Wilsander was in an intense battle with Forsyth and had also left the main battlefield. The three Volga brothers had joint hands and engaged the DarkStar warriors by relying on their teamwork.

Feidin should be hiding somewhere with Sylvia, but with the battlefield spreading over such a large area, Herlous was worried that the two of them would not have a place to hide and end up being spotted by the enemy.

Pew!

A ray of laser brushed past his shoulders and hit a building far away with a loud explosion. Herlous let out a curse and hurriedly focused on avoiding the incoming attacks.

At that moment, a powerful gust of wind blew over, and Herlous was not able to resist it. He was blown away by the gust of wind and flung more than ten meters away. Out of the corner of his eye, he saw another figure that was being blown away. Sherman had not been spared by the gust of wind either.

Raising his head to take a look, he saw Wind Demon Anur circling around the skies while dragging a mini cyclone that covered a radius of one square kilometer. Everywhere he went, the buildings and streets would be thrown into complete chaos.

The tall buildings that had originally blocked one's view had been completely torn down. Their field of vision was much larger than before, and they could see Nagakin and Black Star fighting Anur in the sky. However, because Anur's speed was too fast, the two of them were engaged in a bitter battle.

Bang!

A wind pressure cannon sent Black Star flying toward a tall building.

Herlous grabbed his weapon tightly and sprinted toward Sherman. While he wanted to reinforce Han Xiao, he had to first get rid of his current opponent, Sherman.

...

"Ah! My old back!"

Han Xiao flew out from a large hole in the building and took a breath of cold air.

His armor was heavily damaged, and the situation of the battle was displayed on his battle interface by Phillip. Currently, the battle between both parties was extremely intense, but he had no choice but to place his attention on Anur. Looking at the Wind Demon who came and went as though he was mocking them, Han Xiao felt a great headache.

"This fellow is the veteran high-ranked expert of DarkStar. His ability is really too troublesome, and being unable to catch up to him puts us at a huge disadvantage."

Han Xiao's expression was solemn. In the ranked A mission [Godora's Ally], there were a few dozen requirements, and the majority of them were to either kill or capture DarkStar members or battleships. These required a certain quantity for the requirement to be met. There were some other requirements with higher rewards with the target being specific important DarkStar personnel. Anur was one of those targets.

The size of the reward was a good way to estimate the difficulty of the mission. The reward for getting rid of Anur was the sixth highest among all the other requirements in the mission. This was an indication of Anur's strength.

The majority of my normal battle methods are useless against him. His speed is too fast, and he is even able to turn invisible. It is very difficult for my weapons to hit him, and he does not even need to touch us. As long as he flies past us, the wind pressure that he generates will attack us.

Furthermore, he can control the wind pressure to form a shield, and his defenses aren't weak. Nagakin isn't able to match him in terms of agility in the sky. Even if Nagakin's fists and Shockwave Blast are powerful, it's useless if they cannot hit the target. He will only end up being toyed with.

Han Xiao analyzed the situation calmly as he fired his weapons. Anur's abilities were very well rounded, and of all his skills, only a few were capable of dealing with Anur. The most powerful one would naturally be Ames' Character Summon Card. Restricting Anur for ten seconds was extremely fatal to an enemy who relied on speed. However, the Character Summon Card could only be used once and was very precious. Even if he wanted to use it, Han Xiao would wait for a better opportunity.

Perhaps Chen Xing's Character Summon Card can be put to use... maybe to seduce the enemy or something...

Just as he was observing the enemy, Anur was also observing him.

So, he is Black Star...

Anur studied Han Xiao carefully. This was the first time that he met Han Xiao personally. In the past, he had only understood Han Xiao from the intelligence reports and Ember's description. Anur was truly curious about this fellow who had been able to make Ember suffer multiple losses.

He did not understand why Ember always suffered losses at Black Star's hand. It was as though Black Star was his nemesis.

The organization had groomed Ember so that he would be able to play a more important role. Ember's ability was capable of accurately and quickly massacring a large group of enemies without causing collateral damage. This was an important weapon for them to wipe out all the pureblooded Godorans. A weapon should not be allowed to malfunction.

When DarkStar discovered Ember's talent, they had already decided to turn him into a large killing weapon that belonged solely to DarkStar!

Allowing Han Xiao to live would only affect Ember's mental state and the benefits of DarkStar. Now that he had a chance, Anur felt that he should get rid of Black Star lest Ember got obsessed over this mercenary.

"Since that useless student of mine is unable to get rid of you, let me do it instead," Anur muttered.

Rumble!

Right at this moment, the ground began to shake.

In the surrounding few kilometers, the ground of the city began cracking up, and a mechanical base under the city was revealed. All the buildings that were still intact were retracted underground for protection, and twenty-meter-tall mechanical poles rose up from underground and surrounded the entire battlefield.

Hum!

Those mechanical poles lit up at the same time, and a large blue concave protective shield was formed. It looked like an upside-down bowl and had a diameter of twenty kilometers. It separated the battlefield from the other regions of the city.

Every city was equipped with a large number of facilities underground, and this was the protective shield. Noriosse had taken action to cut their losses and restrict the battlefield to this region, which was already unsalvageable. They wanted to stop the battlefield from being spread further to protect the other regions of the city.

This action of theirs was equivalent to giving up on that region of the city, but in comparison to losing the entire city, which spanned a few thousand kilometers, this was a wise decision.

If it were any ordinary people creating trouble, they would have caught the perpetrators without any hesitation. However, the battle between Calamity Grade Supers was not so easily stopped, and Noriosse only had a single Grade A Protector. Furthermore, this Protector had been hired with a sky-high salary, so he might not stop the battle alone.

Forcefully intervening in this battle would only increase their losses, and the background of these individuals was not something that could be ignored.

Help Godora? While the Noriosse Financial Group was not afraid of DarkStar, they were businessmen and did not want to be on the hit list of such a frightening organization.

Help DarkStar? They would only do so if they were dreaming!

Thus, the upper echelons of Noriosse were also very helpless. They were not politicians, only the managers of this planet. Profits were their only goal. If the price of maintaining peace was too high, they would consider watching from the side. It had already been many years since Grade A Supers last fought on Noriosse, and this was probably the largest commotion that DarkStar had created in the past ten years.

The upper echelons felt that it was best for them not to interfere in the matter to avoid any risks.

Chapter 497: Battle of Noriosse (3)

All the pedestrians in the sealed region were sent out, and they gathered outside the protective shield to watch the battle. Alvin and Ember, with one running and the other chasing, had long left the region and were not locked in the protective shield.

Even more Public Security Squads waited outside the protective shield, and there were at least a thousand aircrafts. The Protector who had been hired by the financial group was also inside the protective shield, monitoring the battle from the sidelines without any intention of interfering.

Upon witnessing such a scene, the expressions of the DarkStar warriors and mercenaries changed. They felt as though they were being locked up in a cage.

"They locked down the region? It seems like we created too much chaos."

Anur's eyes narrowed. With such a big commotion created, they would not be able to stay on Noriosse for too long. The moment that Alvin died, they would have to retreat from Noriosse immediately. The DarkStar fleet was already waiting for orders outside the atmosphere and was ready to aid them at any time. Would they end up in conflict with Noriosse's fleet? However, that was nothing to be afraid of.

Anur then thought of the embarrassing result that Ember had produced a few days ago.

It is probably best for me to stay behind and delay the enemies. Ember has already failed once, and I doubt he will be able to deal with the combined attacks of Black Star and Nagakin. When the battle ends, it will also be easier for me to leave this place, and I am virtually undefeatable with my speed.

On the other side, the appearance of the protective shield made Han Xiao worry.

While the lockdown of the region seemed to be restricting Anur's movement range, it was actually extremely disadvantageous to them. It was as good of freeing Anur from his wariness.

In the locked region, Anur could unleash all of his strength without any restraint and turn the entire region into a cyclone of destruction!

Furthermore, the protective shield separated them from the passersby, and Han Xiao's plan to make use of Anur's destructive force to drag them in could not be accomplished.

Boom!

With just a slight moment of distraction, the wind pressure cannon smashed into his chest. His armor was immediately dented, and Han Xiao was sent flying.

The situation is extremely bad. I wonder how my officers are doing.

Far away from the center of the battlefield. Feidin and Sylvia were retreating from the battlefield. They had originally been hiding somewhere nearby, but as the battlefield expanded, they had no choice but to change their location in order to prevent themselves from being spotted by the enemy.

"Let... let go of me! I want to go back and help!"

Sylvia's tone was anxious, and her face had turned red from exerting too much strength. She was trying to break free from Feidin's grip.

Feidin held onto Sylvia's wrist tightly and dragged her along with a sigh. "Stop being a fool. You won't be of any help, and any one of the enemies will be able to kill you. Can't you see the battle in the sky? As long as you get dragged into that cyclone, you are dead for sure."

"I..." Sylvia did not have anything to say in response. After a while, she said angrily, "But you can help them!"

"I don't wish to be involved in your mercenary group's mission. This matter has nothing to do with me." Feidin shook his head.

Sylvia was furious and she bit down on Feidin's hands, hoping that he would let go.

Feidin squirmed in pain, and he looked down at his bleeding hand. With a sigh, he said, "No matter what you say, I will not allow you to charge into your death."

Right at that moment, footsteps could be heard from in front, and a DarkStar member blocked their path.

"Ah, two lost fish who escaped the net."

Sinesa sneered coldly. She had just gotten rid of a hired Grade B mercenary and noticed some movement. Thus, she had decided to block their path.

Feidin and Sylvia's faces blanched.

Sylvia immediately took out her alloy sword, and her hands began to tremble. While she wanted to control her hands from trembling, in the face of a Grade B Super, a Grade D Super like her felt an instinctive sense of fear.

At that moment, Feidin pushed Sylvia behind him.

"Run away quickly. I will block her."

Feidin's tone was calm.

Hu!

A formless pressure then gushed toward the both of them and interrupted the words that were about to come out from Sylvia's mouth.

Feidin opened his mouth, and music drifted out. His psychic energy formed a shield to protect the both of them, but it was quickly shattered the next moment. The two of them were sent flying and collapsed onto the ground.

"Only Grade C?"

Sinesa was a little disappointed. She had thought that she had caught a big fish, but they were only two small shrimps.

Sylvia felt her bum aching from the fall but realized that she was not injured at all. This attack was only a probing strike from Sinesa. While Feidin's psychic shield was broken, it had blocked the majority of the attack. Furthermore, Feidin had absorbed most of the damage for her.

Standing up, Feidin felt a warm sensation in his nose. Wiping his nose with his hands, his hands were immediately covered with blood. At the same time, his head felt as though it was being stung by needles.

Bearing the pain silently, he maintained his calm expression and turned to look at Sylvia. With a forced smile, he said, "I am alright. Don't stay here, or I will have to divert my attention to take care of you."

As Sylvia heard that, she gritted her teeth, took up her sword, and ran away resolutely.

She knew that her strength was lacking, and staying behind would only create trouble.

Feidin turned back around to meet the enemy. Tidying his clothes, he took a deep breath and began channeling his psychic energy.

"You aren't going to escape?" Sinesa said with excitement.

"We are both Psychics, and it won't hurt to have a spar." Feidin forced a smile.

Sinesa's eyes widened, and she asked doubtfully, "A Grade C Psychic like you wants to spar with me?"

"In truth, this is my first time fighting with my psychic abilities," Feidin said with a serious tone. "I do not like to fight. If you can spare me, I will be very thankful."

Sinesa could not be bothered to continue talking and unleashed her powerful psychic energy. She was prepared to get rid of the fellow in front of him before killing the little girl who had run away.

It would not take too much time anyway.

Boom boom boom!

The space between the two of them began contorting, and a series of attacks exploded.

Plop...

A few seconds later, Feidin collapsed onto the ground with his every orifice bleeding.

"Overestimating yourself," Sinesa sneered before walking over Feidin's body.

Just as she was about to give chase to Sylvia, Feidin's weak voice sounded from behind.

"Cough cough... battling is truly difficult. I am indeed unsuitable for such violence..."

Feidin stood up shakily with his face full of blood. Blood was dripping down from his elegant face and onto the ground.

Sinesa turned around with a frown. She had unleashed her psychic energy without any restraint, and the other party's head should have turned into mush.

Forget it, another few attacks won't be that big a deal.

Feidin coughed out a mouthful of blood and said with a bitter smile on his face, "I shouldn't have forced it. I am indeed not suitable for this... Yes yes yes, I am trash. Stop scolding me, I already have a headache.... Er, I also know that you are hurting. Be good, don't make any noise. Alright then, I shall promise you. Just don't let my body die... Jeez, I am truly reluctant."

"Who are you talking to?" Sinesa was bewildered. Turning back to take a look, she realized that there was no one else beside her. She then came to a realization... This person must have been beaten up by her to the point that he went crazy.

"You are truly unlucky to have met me." Sinesa unleashed her psychic energy again. She would never hesitate when killing the enemy.

Boom!

The next moment, Sinesa felt a loud ring by her ears as though a bell was constantly being rung in her head. It was as though her brain was being constantly hammered time and time again. Feidin remained still, and she was the one to fly backward instead.

With a loud crash, Sinesa collapsed onto the ground and spat out a mouthful of blood. After falling into a daze for a while, she looked at Feidin with shock.

Just what is going on‽

Feidin seemed to have transformed into a completely different person with his charisma being transformed. His actions became gentle as he wiped away the blood stains on his face like a girl. At the same time, a look of delight could be seen in his eyes.

"Why do I feel as though you are the one with bad luck? I was just worrying about not having a target to vent my anger!"

Feidin... or rather, Chen Xing circulated her psychic energy, and the might of her psychic energy displayed was more than ten times greater than before.

Seeing that, Sinesa's expression dropped.

"You like to fight, right?" Chen Xing gnashed her teeth. "This old lady will accompany you to have some fun!"

Chapter 498: Battle of Noriosse (4)

"Huu, huu..."

Sylvia panted heavily as she ran while avoiding all the enemies that she could. A battle of this level was still too much for her, and she was not able to do anything at all. Feidin was still delaying the enemy, and she did not dare to waste the opportunity that Feidin had created for her.

After running for a long time, Sylvia felt her lungs burning, and she could no longer run. Bending over, she panted heavily with her hands on her knees.

Boom!

All of a sudden, a violent gust of wind blew over, and the wind pressure being sent out by Anur was becoming more and more powerful. A look of fear could be seen on Sylvia's face. With such a large radius, it was impossible for her to escape. She stood on the spot in a daze and raised her head to see the storm getting nearer and nearer to her.

Right at that moment, a mechanical Amphiptere charged out from nowhere, and with its chest and helmet region splitting open, it swallowed Sylvia up. The next moment, the cyclone swept over, and the mechanical Amphiptere was swept away.

Sylvia was hidden within the mechanical suit, and apart from being dizzy from the impact, she was safe. After escaping death, she cried out in surprise, "Phillip‽"

"Master asked me to protect you, hum... He said that the cyclone is expanding, hum..."

She then looked up at the sky, and through the field vision of the mechanical suit, she realized that the sky within the protective shield had formed a large cyclone with numerous items being swept up into it. The cyclone was still expanding, and Anur was currently flying in a clockwise direction like a ray of light stirring up the atmosphere.

The protective shield was only so big, and Anur was prepared to go all out and create a cyclone that could fill up the entire protective shield. In a sealed area, his cyclone would be able to very quickly achieve a destructive power capable of flattening the entire place.

In the sky, Anur's speed was too fast, and neither Han Xiao nor Nagakin could even touch him. Anur could only be bothered with flying in circles, and the other two were completely helpless.

"If we allow him to continue, when the cyclone is completely formed, everything within the protective shield will be destroyed, and even his subordinates will not be spared. Is he treating his subordinates as chess pieces to abandon?"

Nagakin's tone was heavy. With his experience, he could already foresee the ending. Since they could not catch up to the other party, there was no way for them to stop Anur. If the Noriosse Protector who was watching on the side could help them, they might be able to stop Anur. However, the Protector did not not seem to have any intention of helping.

The battle on the ground quickly shifted away from the center, but there were still many who ended up being swept up and turned into a bloody mess by the violent wind pressure. Many of Han Xiao's machineries had not been spared. His mechanical beasts struggled helplessly in the storm, and the cannon towers whose foundations were underground had been uprooted in the wind.

Looking in from the outside, it looked as though a grayish cyclone formed of many random objects was expanding rapidly, and the protective shield would occasionally be scratched by the objects in the cyclone, creating sparks in the collision. It was like a spinning washing machine.

The sky was spinning, and the earth was shaking!

In the storm, Han Xiao's attack armor had long been destroyed, and his Void Dragon mechanical suit was also riddled with holes. All of his energy was diverted toward the mechanical wings and thrusters, and he was only able to barely stabilize himself in the storm. Seeing the situation getting from bad to worse, he knew that if he did not stop Anur, everyone would die for sure.

A Grade A who went all out was far too powerful. Han Xiao had even used [Life Return] once in the battle. However, the mission progress bar had thankfully begun to move. If not, Han Xiao would definitely have been driven mad.

Han Xiao truly looked forward to having such powerful strength. Han Xiao was currently level 116, and he had more than 200,000,000 EXP on the interface. If not for the fact that he had an advancement, he would have to probably use [Life Return] another one or two more times. Currently, the majority of his abilities were useless. After all, DarkStar's attack was far too sudden, so he did not have much time to prepare. Furthermore, Han Xiao had not had many opportunities or much time to build new machines since his advancement.

Thankfully, I have Ames' Character Summon Card. Without it, my only option would be to escape. At least I still have a trump card up my sleeves.

Han Xiao made a decision in his heart before shouting out to Nagakin in the communication channel, "What is your most powerful attack?"

"What do you mean?" Nagakin asked with doubt.

"I have a way to make Anur stop. I should be able to restrict him for ten seconds or so. He will not be able to move or use any of his abilities during that time. This is the only chance that we have to severely wound him," Han Xiao said with a deep voice.

The situation of the battle was ever-changing, and despite them being disadvantaged, Han Xiao remained calm. Even though he had a trump card up his sleeve, the resistance of a Grade A Super was extremely high, and even if Anur did not specialize in defence, it would be impossible for him to destroy his opponent's combat capability with his damage alone. He had already tried this once on Ember.

Only Nagakin, who was also a Grade A Super, would be able to deal a fatal blow and not waste this precious Dragon Emperor Character Summon Card!

"Ten seconds or so? Are you really able to restrict Anur‽" Nagakin asked with disbelief and thought that he heard incorrectly.

Ten seconds to someone of their level was no longer a 'chance' but the difference between life and death!

However, how would the Grade B Black Star be able to restrict a Calamity Grade Super for ten seconds‽

"Just believe me," Han Xiao replied. Anur was an Esper who specialized in speed. No matter what, it should be impossible for his Strength to exceed 1,800 points, right?

"... Fine."

Nagakin took a deep breath. Black Star had been able to make Ember retreat and had never disappointed him before. Perhaps Black Star was truly capable of doing so. Nagakin decided to trust Black Star once and immediately began to circulate his energy. His entire body was instantly covered in pugilist flames, and Nagakin seemed to have turned into an inextinguishable ball of golden fire. The storm was unable to extinguish this ball of flames but instead made it grow even more powerful as the wind blew.

He did not need ten seconds. Stopping Anur for a single second was enough. A storm of combo attacks was his most powerful technique, and he was only afraid that it would not hit the enemy.

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and fixed his gaze on the Wind Demon, which was moving at a high speed. Raising his hand up to target the Wind Demon, Han Xiao concentrated fully.

Victory and defeat would be determined in an instant!

"What is he trying to do?"

Anur also noticed Han Xiao's actions, and he could still clearly see every detail in the storm.

He did not understand Han Xiao's actions but was truly surprised at the fact that Han Xiao had been able to survive in the most violent region of the storm until now. For a Grade B Super, Han Xiao's life force was truly too stubborn.

However, he should be at his limits. Anur then directed his gaze at the periphery of the battlefield. The Protector had also made his move and was currently moving toward Black Star. He seemed to have felt that Black Star was in danger and wanted to take Black Star away. The next instant, Anur understood the intentions of the Noriosse Financial Group.

"Trying to save Black Star because you don't want to provoke Ames? Humph, fat chance!" Anur sneered coldly and controlled a gust of wind to attack the incoming Protector. After delaying the Protector slightly, Anur's body charged forward toward Han Xiao, carrying with him a frightening wind pressure capable of destroying a mountain!

Anur wanted to get rid of him right there and then!

"Sh*t!" the Protector gasped. The upper echelons had asked him to intervene in emergencies and prevent the high-grade battle strength of both parties from being killed. He had originally wanted to move Black Star away from the battlefield, but never had he expected Anur to attack Black Star instead. Even with the risk of angering the Protector, Anur wanted to kill Black Star! He was truly fearless!

Right at that moment, a frightening energy signature burst forth from Han Xiao's body.

The entire atmosphere seemed to have been frozen in place.

Hum!

A woman's hand appeared behind Han Xiao and stretched out her palms toward the incoming Anur.

"That's... Dragon Emperor Ames!"

Nagakin, Anur, and the Protector were dumbfounded!

Chapter 499: Battle of Noriosse (5)

The next instant, a terrifying might that shook the three Calamity Grade Supers descended and launched toward Anur.

"What‽" Anur's expression changed drastically.

Boom!

The speeding Anur was stopped instantly without any form of retaliation. The surrounding atmosphere seemed to have been frozen in space and Anur was like a bug trapped in amber, completely unable to move.

You used [Character Summon Card—Ames]!

[Force Field—Gaze of the Dragon] is currently determining the target's STR. Target's STR: 466 points... Judgement complete.

Anur has fallen into [Trapped] status for 14 seconds.

How is this possible‽

Being caught completely off guard, Anur was thoroughly shocked.

Such a frightening restriction ability. Could it be the Dragon Emperor's strength‽

While it's true that Black Star is the Dragon Emperor's subordinate, why is he able to use the Dragon Emperor's strength‽

Anur had not felt panic for a very long time. At that moment, his calmness was completely destroyed. No matter how much he tried, he could not move an inch or say a single word. Looking at Nagakin, who was charging over blazing brightly, fear could finally be seen in his eyes.

Bang!

As though a golden bolt of lightning had been smashed into his chest, Anur's weak wind pressure shield was shattered, and the sound of Nagakin's fists smashing into Anur's body sounded like thunder in the clear sky.

Nagakin had been accumulating the force of this strike for a long time, and its might could shake the mountain and blow cities away. Those fists of his were sufficient to destroy an entire district. However, Anur's body was fixed in place, and he could not fly out anywhere. The entire force of the attack could only be borne by his body.

A mouthful of blood was spat into the violent winds!

Bang bang bang!

Nagakin let out a roar and unleashed all of his frustrations. An endless afterimage of fists and kicks could be seen and every single attack of his hit Anur squarely in the chest. Anur was like a living target board who could not move. He had no choice but to endure the storm like attacks with his body's shape being visibly contorted!

"Too violent." Han Xiao's brows twitched as he watched the scene. At the same time, he could hardly resist the temptation to add in some sound effects to complement the show. However, Han Xiao did not remain idle and raised his High Frequency Strike Cannon to attack as well.

This is a rare opportunity! The higher the damage, the better!

The two of them trapped Anur in the middle and gave him a good serving of their attacks.

Without the wind pressure shield, Anur could only endure the attacks with his physical body and was beaten up to the point his bones were shattered and his flesh was mashed up.

His broken bones protruded out from his skin, and blood gushed out like a fountain!

The Protector did not have time to even be shocked. His mission was to stop both parties from being killed, and Anur was also one of his protection targets. Previously, he did not think that there would be a need for him to help Anur, but the situation suddenly changed, and the target that he had to protect was Anur.

However, Anur had released a wind pressure cannon to delay the Protector's footsteps right before he was restricted and caused the Protector to be unable to save Black Star in time.

Fourteen seconds of crazed attacks. When the control time ended, all the accumulated force from Anur's body exploded forth.

Boom!

A bloody firework went off in midair!

An Esper who was not able to use his abilities would be far more vulnerable. For example, a defensive Esper might be able to block a nuclear explosion with their shield, but they would not be able to block a nuclear explosion with their own body. Anur did not specialize in defense, and by restricting his speed, Han Xiao and Nagakin had been able to quickly whittle down all of his HP.

After a series of violent attacks, Nagakin had finally vented all of his anger. He had been surrounded by Anur and Ember last time and suffered pretty severe injuries. This time, he had finally gotten his revenge. Usually, when he fought an enemy of the same grade, the enemy would pull away after a couple of blows. How would he get the opportunity to beat his target up to his heart's content?

Even if an ordinary person was violently beaten up by another person without avoiding any attacks, if the one attack had the desire to kill, this short time would be sufficient to beat a person to death.

However, Anur still had a single breath left.

Bang!

The badly battered Wind Demon landed on the ground and reverted to his human form. Injuries could be seen all over, and his entire body was covered in blood. He was like a broken gunny sack, and the bleeding would not stop.

Anur spat out a mouthful of blood and breathed weakly. He was already nearing his end and could not even stand up. He glared at Han Xiao fiercely with the look of shock and anger in his eyes.

"To think I... I would actually die here..."

Nagakin rubbed his fists, and the storm in his heart had not settled. Black Star indeed did not go back on his word and was worth trusting.

Han Xiao heaved a sigh of relief but was also exhausted. Thankfully, his trump card had been extremely successful. However, he had never expected to use up the Ames Character Summon Card so shortly after obtaining it. Only by killing Anur would he be able to regain all of his losses. There was still the last strike left, so he raised his hands to stop Nagakin.

He had to deal the final strike himself so that he would be able to gain the experience points from killing the enemy.

Anur turned to look at the Protector who was nearby. This was his final hope.

However, the Protector suddenly slowed down and pretended as though he could not make it in time.

Han Xiao did not hesitate and raised his High Frequency Strike Cannon. Looking at Anur's furious eyes, he smashed it down toward Anur's chest.

Puchi.

A blade penetrated through Anur's back but not much blood flowed out. At this moment, almost all of Anur's blood had already flowed out.

Anur's body shook, and he grabbed onto the blade. His eyes became listless as he looked up at the sky.

His lips parted, and he said his final words in a voice that no one could hear.

"DarkStar... forever."

The next moment, he released the blade, and his hands collapsed onto the ground.

Life had left this body.

Han Xiao heaved a sigh of relief, and at that moment, a notice appeared on the interface.

You killed Anur (LVL 173).

You have received 24,700,000 EXP.

You have jumped more than 10 levels to slay the target. You will get 280% additional EXP bonus. Your personal damage is 13%.

You have received an additional 8,990,000 EXP.

Han Xiao was not surprised that his damage output was so low. Nagakin was the one who had dealt the truly fatal blow, and it was more accurate to say that Nagakin had killed Anur while he picked up benefits from the side.

Of course, without his Character Summon Card, Nagakin would not have been able to kill Anur.

He had received over 33,000,000 EXP from killing Anur, and this was his greatest reward so far. It could be said to have replenish his EXP pool.

The biggest harvest was that he had completed an extremely difficult target in the ranked A mission [Godora's Ally]. Han Xiao had never imagined that he would be able to get rid of a Calamity Grade Super.

[Wind Demon Anur] has been completed.

You have received 18,200,000 EXP, +1,200 Godora favorability, and [Character Summon Card - Anur].

Godoran Civilization: Friendly (2,340/3,000)

Your [Godora's Ally] mission grade has been increased. It will be displayed after calculation.

The violent winds began dispersing, and smoke filled the air.

Looking at Anur's corpse, be it the enemies or mercenaries, everyone was dumbfounded.

They had never imagined that this Calamity Grade Super would die.

Even Anur himself had never imagined it.

"For a Calamity Grade Super to die in battle, DarkStar will probably go crazy from anger. Because of a traitor, they lost two high grade combatants and suffered a huge loss. I will probably enter their sights and face a far greater risk than before."

Han Xiao let out a sigh. Killing Anur would probably affect him in the future, but the previous scenario was already one where it was either Anur's death or his. Han Xiao would not show any mercy to Anur because of that and let the dying Anur off.

There was still just under a year to Version 2.0, and Han Xiao was planning to make his preparations in the upcoming year. As for DarkStar placing their attention on him, Han Xiao was not too anxious. Once Version 2.0 arrived, he would have to solve the Mutation Disaster and come into direct conflict with DarkStar.

DarkStar was an enemy that he would have to deal with eventually in the Main Storyline of Version 2.0, and this is only a matter of time.

Han Xiao looked around at his surroundings. With Anur dead, the morale of the DarkStar warriors collapsed. However, the protective shield had sealed off all their routes of escape.

"The situation here is already safe. I wonder how the situation on Alvin's side is..."

Chapter 500: Return

At the same time, a few hundred kilometers away, Ember was still chasing after Alvin, and this chase had been going on for more than ten minutes. Both parties were already far away from the main battlefield where Han Xiao and the others were, and they were about to arrive at the Teleportation Mage's location.

After Anur's death, the situation on the battlefield had turned around completely, and the DarkStar warriors had become the prey that was being hunted. None of them had a chance to send any messages, so Ember was unaware of what was happening on the battlefield. In his mind, Anur was definitely still toying with those bothersome mercenaries.

He was not worried about Anur's safety at all. When he entered DarkStar at a young age, Anur had already been a Calamity Grade Super in the organization. He had received Anur's training from a young age and was extremely clear on how powerful his teacher was.

Since Anur had taken the initiative to stay behind and delay the enemies, he definitely had absolute confidence in himself. While his teacher had recently been disappointed by his failures, these little details were not important, and Ember had full confidence in Anur. With Nagakin's speed, Nagakin would not even be able to catch the edge of his teacher's clothes. How could his teacher possibly lose?

Even if he could not win, running definitely would not be a problem for his teacher.

Not sending any news meant that everything was in his grasp and that there was nothing to inform him of.

In order to prevent himself from being too eye catching, Ember dispersed the gigantic black cloud and only let the carbon particles revolve around him. Alvin's aircraft was still escaping, and there was still some distance between the two.

Alvin looked back and said with a face full of sweat, "We will arrive soon. When we stop, we will only have ten seconds or so before he catches up. If we cannot complete the teleportation within this time, we will be dead."

Aroshia looked at Alvin, and after thinking for a while, she corrected, "Not us, only you will die."

"Thank you for the reminder..." Alvin gnashed his teeth.

How infuriating!

The shop of the Teleportation Mage was already in sight. Aroshia seemed to have thought of something and said, "Right, after beating him up the last time, he may have shifted away from here."

"..." Alvin.

Bang!

The aircraft performed an emergency brake and crashed head on into the wall of a bookshop. A large hole was immediately created in the front of the bookshop, and the shelves along the way were all destroyed. Torn up paper exploded into the air like fireworks and drifted down like snow.

Both of them jumped out of the aircraft halfway and landed in the destroyed bookshop. They did not have the time to park the aircraft properly before knocking on the door.

The counter by the door was also sent flying, and Yi Xuan was currently leaning back on a chair, reading a book. He stared at the scene before him in a complete daze and had a look of complete confusion on his face.

My shop is destroyed‽

Aroshia pointed at Yi Xuan. "He's the one."

"Thankfully, he's still here." Alvin heaved a sigh of relief. He then raised his head up to look at the large hole. "At least it's very airy now."

Yi Xuan looked at Aroshia and said, "I recognize you. You were with the mercenary who beat me up the last time."

"I need your help. Please send us to the northern port quickly. Money isn't a problem." Alvin did not dare delay and immediately stated his intention.

Yi Xuan fell into a daze and looked down at the shredded paper all over the floor. He finally reacted to the situation and felt a sharp pain throughout his entire body. The book in his hands slipped and fell to the ground. It was as though there was a dagger being plunged into his heart. He felt that even breathing was becoming difficult, and he cried out in despair.

"My treasured collection!"

Alvin was getting anxious. This was not the time for him to bother about those broken books, and he pressed, "We are currently being chased by someone who belongs to DarkStar, and he won't even blink when killing. If you don't leave together with us, he will also kill you. We are Godorans and will give you a high fee for your services. Furthermore, we will also compensate for your losses. We are running out of time! Hurry up and teleport us!"

Looking through the large hole and into the sky, Ember's figure was approaching them rapidly. In another two seconds, they would be within his attack range. At that time, he would be able to kill Alvin with a simple snap of his fingers.

Cold sweat trickled all over Alvin as he looked at the hesitating Teleportation Mage. They did not make any arrangements beforehand, and Alvin did not know if the Teleportation Mage in front of him would help. This was the only hope for them to escape.

At this moment, Aroshia said, "My friend said that he will come for you if you don't help."

As Yi Xuan heard that, he did not say another word and immediately opened the teleportation door. A whirlpool-like blue glow surrounded them, and the glow of magic dyed the surroundings blue.

Alvin was overjoyed. He rushed into the teleportation door quickly, and Yi Xuan did not dare hesitate either. He did not wish to stay behind and use his weak mage body to endure the rage of the enemy.

Hum!

A brilliant glow flashed, and the teleportation door closed. The three of them had disappeared without a trace.

Ember, who had just charged in, saw this scene, and dark clouds could be seen on his face.

He had actually lost them!

He had originally thought that Alvin was already at his wits end, but never had he imagined that a Teleportation Mage would be hidden in this place.

If not for Aesop, the Great Mechanic Han would not have known that there was a hidden Teleportation Mage in this place. This was something that could not be realized with strategy but intel. At that time, Han Xiao also did not imagine that he would be dragged into the battle between DarkStar and Godora.

Ember looked at the empty room and clenched his fists. Only a mage who was proficient in teleportation would be able to track their whereabouts. At that moment, the traitor had already escaped with all clues being lost, and Ember was not able to give chase.

He truly wondered if he was having a streak of bad luck recently. All kinds of unexpected scenarios seemed to have been happening to him, and even a mission like this that should have had a ninety percent success rate had failed. It seemed like his teacher Anur would be angered to death.

Ember let out a depressed sigh and took out his communicator to contact Anur. With his mission failing, he needed to send news back immediately so that they can plan their next move.

Buss!

Anur's face appeared on the communicator, and he said with a frown, "Have you succeeded?"

Ember shook his head and described the situation.

"Trash!" Anur flew into a rage.

Ember felt his body freeze up, and he was a little awkward. This was the first time that his teacher had cursed him. It seemed like his teacher was truly angered to death.

"Where do you think the traitor has escaped to?"

"I don't know. There weren't any clues," Ember replied.

"If they try to escape in a spaceship, it will save us a great deal of trouble," Anur said.

Ember nodded. Their DarkStar fleet was already on standby outside of Noriosse and ready to block the traitor from escaping. The moment that the traitor attempted to leave by ship, he would be surrounded by their fleet.

"How's the situation on your side?" Ember asked.

"Humph, the battle is a stalemate. Hurry up and return. I have delayed the enemy, and if you can get back in time, we can work together to get rid of the Godoran and those mercenaries. Since you can't catch the traitor, let's wipe out these enemies first."

"Sure!"

Ember's eyes lit up, and he returned to where he had come from. Upon thinking about the possibility of getting rid of Black Star, his mood instantly lifted.

...

The protective shield had served its purpose to seclude this region, and the battlefield was already becoming one sided. The DarkStar warriors all began to fall one after another.

In the middle of the debris, 'Anur' ended his call with Ember. After turning off the communicator, he tapped his cheeks lightly, and an electrical current ran across the face. The next moment, Han Xiao's face was revealed.

Taking off the Facial Simulator, Han Xiao rubbed his cheeks and looked at Nagakin with a smile. "He's coming back, and I have a piece of good news. Alvin succeeded in escaping."

Nagakin burst into satisfied laughter and cracked his knuckles. "Great! My fists are still hungry."

Han Xiao nodded and heaved a sigh of relief. It was truly tiring for him to act. With Anur dead, the communicator had been picked up by him, and he had instantly thought of making good use of it.

DarkStar only had a single Calamity Grade Super left, and the difference in strength had finally been even out. While the Ames Character Summon Card had already been used, Nagakin was also extremely powerful. Together with him, the chances of them surrounding Ember would be extremely high. The only problem was whether or not Ember knew about the present situation. If he found out about their situation, he would definitely retreat.

Right at that moment, Ember had actually called Anur on the communicator. Han Xiao had immediately taken out the Facial Simulator and scanned Anur's corpse to pose as Anur. At the same time, he had tested Ember with his words.

When he was acting, Han Xiao had truly been nervous. He did not know how Anur usually talked to Ember, and after observing Ember's reaction, Han Xiao concluded that Ember was extremely respectful toward Anur.

Ember did not suspect Han Xiao in the slightest, and he did not even notice the small discrepancies. Thinking about it carefully, this was extremely normal. After all, someone would only be able to use Anur's communicator if he had died.

In Ember's eyes, that was impossible.

"Not just that, his reaction allowed me to confirm something. There is indeed a DarkStar fleet waiting in the atmosphere." Han Xiao took his own communicator and tried to contact Aroshia while saying to Nagakin, "I never thought that we would be able to get rid of a Calamity Grade enemy. Since that's the case, we now have more breathing space. With most of the ground troops wiped out, there isn't a need for us to take the risk and send Alvin away."

Nagakin thought for a while and felt that it made sense.

It was best for them to adapt to the changes.

At that moment, the Protector also walked forward. Looking down at Anur's corpse, he let out a sigh and said with pity, "You guys actually killed him. Jeez, if I didn't suffer from his attacks, I wouldn't have been a step late."

Both of them were dumbfounded.

This person was truly vengeful!

How wonderful!

After pretending to feel pity for a while, the Protector then looked at the two of them with his gaze focusing on Han Xiao. A look of unconcealed amazement could be seen in his eyes.

After pausing for a while, he did not say another word and retreated far away. The members of DarkStar were already at their wit's end, and he did not have any intention of interfering.

He had previous witnessed Anur's death, and if he intervened at this moment, Godora might think that he was interfering with them on purpose. Thus, he gave up any idea of saving them.

Is it truly so difficult to remain neutral?

Nagakin then looked toward Han Xiao and commented, "That ability of yours... it seems to be related to the Dragon Emperor."

This doubt had been in Nagakin's heart for a while, and he had finally found a chance to ask about it. He knew that his senses were definitely not mistaken, and the might of that attack was definitely at the beyond Grade A level. However, why was Black Star able to make use of the Dragon Emperor's abilities? Just what was their relationship?

If this matter was reported to the War Bureau, the intel division would probably have to re-estimate Black Star's position in Floating Dragon Island.

"Nothing much, I only performed a small role." Han Xiao waved his hands humbly.

Nagakin could not help but value Black Star even more now. A few days ago, he had felt that this mission was completely hopeless. Even when he secured Han Xiao's help, it did not reduce the hopelessness that he had felt. However, Han Xiao's abilities had far exceeded his imagination.

If not for Anur's corpse lying down at the side, he would never have thought that even after facing a situation where he was surrounded by two Calamity Grade Supers, he would not be severely injured and actually be able to get rid of one of them.

With two of them fighting him alone, he was actually able to kill one of them!

The sound of the surrounding battles began to die down, and this meant that the DarkStar warriors were getting fewer and fewer.

"Let's stop chatting," Han Xiao said in a deep voice. "The battle isn't over yet, and there are still members of DarkStar alive. Before Ember returns, we should get rid of them quickly and not leave a single one of them alive."

...

Swoosh!

The Battleship Slicing Blade cut through flesh, and Sherman's shocked face was cleaved into two.

Herlous panted heavily and sheathed his weapon. After a long battle, he had finally gotten rid of this dwarf Cannon Master. With the enemy's morale being destroyed, their courage had also been destroyed, and Herlous had killed the other party in one fell swoop.

Just as he wanted to leave, his footsteps suddenly paused, and he turned back to Sherman's corpse. Picking up the cannon that had landed on the ground, Herlous muttered to himself, "Black Star should like this spoil of war."

Carrying the cannon on his shoulders, Herlous left the battlefield happily.

...

Bang!

Sinesa's brain was reduced to mush, and she collapsed onto the ground with her body contorting.

Chen Xing rubbed her throat, which had turned hoarse from singing loudly. Shutting her eyes, she recuperated from the damage that the other party had dealt. The other party had not been weak, and she had exhausted a great deal of energy.

"Feidin, I saved your life, and your body shall be treated as the reward," Chen Xing said.

Feidin laughed bitterly in the head but did not respond.

Chen Xing then looked up at the protective shield and muttered to herself, "Since I cannot leave now, I can only pretend to be Feidin and interact with those mercenaries. As long as they don't see through my disguise, I will be able to escape during our free and easy time."

It was not too difficult for her to pretend to be Feidin. Her senses were connected to Feidin's, and she was extremely familiar with Feidin's habits. She was definitely confident in mimicking him completely.

Thinking about the source of all her trouble, Han Xiao, Chen Xing's mood became terrible.

As long as she could trick that fellow, she would regain her freedom.

She was extremely confident in her acting skills. After all, she was an actress!